so you want to make your first million
but let me take a guess of what your day
looks like you wake up you grab your
phone you open Tick Tock and start
scrolling for 30 minutes before you
convince yourself to go downstairs you
then spend 20 minutes deciding and
preparing what you want to eat for
breakfast you then sit at your desk and
proceed to spend the next three hours
watching self-help podcasts thinking
that maybe if you just watch one more
that maybe you'll finally be successful
that is absolute or maybe
you're one of those self-help junkies
that's a step above so you wake up at
6am and you start your 15-step morning
routine that lasts four hours and by the
end of it you're so tired you need a nap
ladies and gentlemen both of these are
totally wrong so in today's video I'm
gonna reveal to you the seven
productivity hacks you need to make your
first million dollars now I want you to
know that I'm coming up on my 10th year
as an entrepreneur so I have tried
everything whatever Routine Morning
Routine all this BS supplement
biohacking ball like I've tried it all
so I can genuinely from ball my heart
tell you what works and what doesn't
work now the first productivity hack is
something that I publicly talked about
in 2021 when I uploaded a free module
from one of my paid programs back then
but I've actually been using this tool
for many many years and the tool is
called unhooked now here's the thing
YouTube is entertainment it is not
education and you need to view it that
way because in life you get ahead by
applying not learning listen it is
incredibly incredibly important to learn
learn as much as you can but it's far
more important to apply that information
even my videos I want you to view my
videos when you watch one of my videos I
don't want you to go away and think oh I
accomplished something look at me I'm so
happy with myself I want you to view my
videos as an interesting Viewpoint and
interesting perspective from someone who
has walked the path very publicly I've
been documenting everything for eight
years now on YouTube that has walked the
path that you want to walk but none of
it will have any effect whatsoever
unless you apply it now the thing is
YouTube is a very very smart platform
and it can be a very dangerous platform
because sure you have interesting
educational but remember view my content
as entertaining and by the way I want
you to view most books out there in the
exact same way because most books what
it is it's 15 pages of gold and then 300
pages of fluff because they can't sell
you a 15-page book and people will pay
12 for that even though it's really only
15 pages that are valuable but listen
that's just the way the world goes so as
long as when you watch my YouTube videos
when you read a book you look at that as
entertainment as downtime stuff really
the only thing that I would consider
proper learning is when you know exactly
what you need to do and you're educating
yourself on how to do it let's say
there's an aspect of your online
business or your Online Career that you
know you need to work on in order to get
ahead well then immersing yourself in
that specific topic that's education
just watching a podcast or reading a
book because you think that it might be
useful to you that is very dangerous and
you need to look at that as
entertainment and not education so
getting back to YouTube there is some
amazing information here on YouTube and
in fact some educational content here on
YouTube that will help you fix a
specific problem in your life you know
let's say for example you're running a
marathon the best thing you can do of
course is get a coach that's going to
work with you maybe even get a paid
program that's going to go hey here's
the plan in month one you do this month
two you do this month three you do that
but if you don't have the funds to do it
well then you can learn a lot on YouTube
but that is real intentional education
you're going on YouTube and you're going
hey I want to learn the scaler or I want
to complete this thing how do I do it
can I get as much information about this
thing that is intentional whereas when
you go on the YouTube home feed that's
not intention at all all that the
algorithm is doing is just trying to
pull you in and try to grasp and try to
take your attention so that's why I've
been saying for years and years that
people need to download Chrome
extensions or applications like unhooked
what it does is it hides a lot of the
things that are unimportant to you here
on YouTube so on the settings I want you
to turn on hide home feed so that way
when you go on YouTube you won't see
your home feed I want you to turn off
the side recommendations so to hide the
video sidebar and I also want you to
hide the comments so the only thing that
is left is your subscription box because
once again you need to be very very
intentional with that of the people that
you subscribe to and once again your
subscription box can be a place for
light entertainment but I don't want you
going on the home page and now all of a
sudden you're recommending a video that
you think is going to help you but once
again it is not intentional education
now I also want to make something very
clear I am literally shooting myself in
the foot by telling you this but I don't
care I want you to get ahead in life and
by the way if that means that you watch
less of my content or what happens for a
lot of people I've noticed is maybe my
content is beneficial to you at a
beginning stage in life and then you get
to more intermediate and my content is a
little less applicable and the funny
thing I've seen is once you actually get
to an exceptional stage of life my
content becomes relevant again because
you start to look at what I'm saying in
the Viewpoint from a much different
perspective of someone who's already
made it and now you can kind of start to
understand why I say the things that I
say so really the reason that I want to
make all of this clear to you is that
you need to be extremely diligent with
where you put your attention so the
first productivity hack is I want you to
download unhooked and get rid of any
stupid recommendations no stupid
comments no sidebar reclaim your
attention and your focus now real quick
before we get into the next part of the
video I get so many people asking for
specific Q A's about business about how
to start your online career and I'm
gonna be honest here on YouTube I don't
really speak to people's specific
situations and on my personal Instagram
like for me that's just like a joke that
that's just where I post like Photo
dumps from trips and holidays and life
basically but that's why I created a
separate private Instagram page called
talk with Iman it is entirely free and
that's actually where I aim to do a q a
so answering your guys's questions once
a week as I said it's free so a lot of
weeks I miss it I'm human I have a lot
of things going on but I try my best to
do weekly so if you ever had any more
business specific or making money online
specific questions go ahead and follow
that account so the second and probably
most important productivity hack is that
I want you to plan the day the night
before now I know it sounds too simple
to be true but that's why most people
don't do it you know there's something
very special that goes on overnight but
when you have set your intention you
know when you go into the day with true
intention when you set your intention
the night before something very special
happens while you're sleeping I've
definitely noticed that now it can be as
simple as three tasks three main things
for the day now back in the day from
2016 to around 2019 2020 when I was
really driving the business for it I
didn't have the leadership that I have
in my different companies and the
business partners and the CEOs that I
have in my different companies I used to
plan my day hour by hour so literally
hour by hour what am I doing these days
of course I've got my calendar I've got
my assistant and things are penciled in
but apart from that I like to free flow
for me the most important thing is
looking at my calendar knowing what I
have the next day put in place whether
that be important business calls
important meetings certain duties that I
need to tend to and for me it's as
simple as writing down three to five
things I need to accomplish that day
it's that simple but I promise you it
works so try it tonight tonight just
very simply write three to five things
down tonight before tomorrow starts and
you'll see your brain starts working
overnight and you go into tomorrow with
real intention now the third
productivity hack is to wear the same
outfits now hear me out I believe that
when you leave the house or let's say
you're doing uh you know you've got a
meeting or you've got some recording or
something like that I believe in
dressing the part now by the way
dressing the part can mean different
things to different people I like to
dress smart casual so when I leave the
house a lot of times I've got a Blazer
maybe Blazer trousers you know some
smart casual shoes sometimes I'm even
wearing suits you know for meetings and
stuff like that now I feel like if I
came and recorded YouTube videos and I
was wearing a suit people would just
find that a little stranger you know
when I've got my zoom meetings I feel
like that would be a little strange
because I don't have a physical office
that I need to go to every day so
dressing the park can mean different
things to you and I definitely believe
that in my early younger years dressing
the part and actually over dressing I
used to overdress pretty much to
everything really helped me because when
you're young some people will already
try to discredit you in business so if
you're there with a you know a hoodie
and big graphic tees and this and that
you're not doing yourself any favors so
definitely especially when you're
younger overdress but when you're home
you know when I'm home and I know that
all I have is some Zoom meetings I've
got calls all day stuff like that I
pretty much wear the same thing every
single day now variations of it most of
the time I don't wear big crazy colors
when I'm at the home for me it's simple
it's the same few pairs of jeans
trousers pretty much the same shoes and
the same brand t-shirt in various
different colors and this really just
makes your life a lot easier and we're
gonna get to another point that I want
to talk about a little later on another
productivity hack but it's just
something that you no longer need to
think about when you've just got a
simple brand of shoes that you wear at
home and by the way I know this sounds
funny but I personally prefer to wear
shoes in the house I wear shoes in the
house and the reason that is is because
because I I don't go to an office I feel
like when I'm wearing shoes I know that
okay it's time to be serious because for
me to walk around the house with like
flip-flops or sandals or shoeless I feel
like that's stuff I like to do when I'm
not working or I'm in my off time or
whatever but when I'm in flow when I'm
in the zone I like to wear shoes in the
house because for me it just means that
okay I know I'm doing some serious work
here make sure it's not sweatpants and
make sure it's not sloppy clothing you
know take yourself seriously now when
you have external meetings or even if
it's a zoom call then you can kind of
dress up a little bit more depending on
the situation but when you're just at
your computer for eight hours working
grinding on a singular task or a few
tasks and you know you're not really
interacting too much with the outside
world just have sort of your plain
uniform that you go to every day now the
fourth productivity hack Falls in line
with the same philosophy as the last one
you know this whole philosophy of
consistency so the fourth productivity
hack is to meal prep at the beginning of
the week and what you want to do is you
want to have the same meals for the
entire week now I'm in the fortunate
position where I have a full-time Chef
in pretty much every single one of my
homes you know obviously if I'm
traveling sometimes and I'm staying in a
hotel in a different country it's
different story but apart from that I
have that luxury and that was something
that I was always really looking forward
to once I started making serious money
but well before that when I was first
starting out my businesses at the
beginning of the week I would meal prep
the same breakfast lunch and dinner for
the entire week in fact actually back
then I didn't even eat breakfast I was
doing intermittent fasting for a few
years now what I would do to keep it a
little bit more interesting is each week
I might cycle a different thing so like
each week the breakfast or the lunch or
the dinner would be different so I would
cycle that week to week but day to day
within that week it was all the same now
I generally think way too many people
look at food as Leisure or some fun
thing but listen to me unless you're on
holiday you're retired or you are rich
as
food is fuel that is it food is
literally just there to fuel you nothing
else nothing more and from day to day
for me when I eat food because I still
don't really eat exciting food I pretty
much just lots of meat fish healthy fats
lots of avocado day to day when I'm
eating that all I see is fuel now when I
go to restaurants it's a totally
different story then you can eat for
enjoyment when you're on holiday once
again totally different story but day to
day all it is is fuel and maybe this is
kind of my Russian side coming out you
know I'm from a place in Russia called
Dagestan and I grew up there for the
early part of my life and I guess in
Russia and that you sound like food is
just fuel like we don't we're not very
romantic about food I don't know if
you've ever had Russian food maybe some
Russian people would disagree but it's
not very tasty it's just it's just
practical that's all it is so just make
sure food does not take up a crazy
amount of your life meal prep at the
beginning of the week and just make sure
it's the same food for the entire week
and then the next week you can cycle to
something different now the fifth
productivity hack is another one where
I'm shooting myself in the foot and that
is I want you to delete Tech talk right
now unless it has a direct correlation
to your line of work listen if you're a
short form editor let's say you know
you're an affiliate marketer for a
certain product and the way you do that
is through short form content on Tick
Tock or let's say you get leads through
your business through Tick Tock which
very few people do so let's say you are
the one in 50 people that actually makes
money through Tick Tock then of course
don't delete it but if you're anyone
else you know 49 of those 50 other
people just delete it there's no point
for it whatsoever this is just another
thing that is here to Rob your attention
and that's it that's really it and
listen you may even be following me on
Tick Tock and the funny thing is I think
I got to 1.5 or 2 million followers on
Tick Tock without ever having downloaded
the app in my entire life my team just
posts a bunch of stuff if right now if
you wanted me to create a tick tock I
wouldn't even know how to do it like I
only downloaded it three or four months
ago because I'm like okay this is crazy
we're getting like 200 million views a
month on short form between Tick Tock
and uh insta reels and what's the other
YouTube shorts so I was like you know
maybe I should download it at least
every once while check in and kind of
understand the platform and what people
are posting but once again that is
related to work so listen I am deeply
honored if you follow me on Tick Tock
but like just don't the small benefit
that you get from short form Clips on
Tick Tock because as I said That's
Entertainment more than anything I mean
the wisdom is great but the issue is the
little upside that you get isn't worth
the complete downside because you know
maybe you see one of my tech talks and
it's great and you get a new perspective
but that's one Tick Tock out of maybe 10
BS ones and 10 BS Tech talks that take
you into a mental spiral that you don't
want to be in nor should you be in so
that's number one the other thing is I
want you to mute everyone on Instagram
now I understand for a lot of people
Instagram is sort of like their social
CV whether that be dating whether that
be career listen I'm not gonna lie
Instagram is important in today's day
and age but that doesn't mean you need
to watch everyone's stories or everyone
posts like I pretty much have I would
say 90 percent of people muted on
Instagram because to be honest I just
don't give a sh like unless it's like a
close friend of mine or like c-suite
level of one of my companies like really
top managerial people in my companies
the CEOs or CMOS or whatever like I just
I don't need to know what you're doing
day to day I'm gonna be honest and you
need to have that exact same focus and
that exact same protection around your
attention now the next productivity hack
is to create a simple three-step morning
routine listen most morning routines are
absolute BS and by the way I was one of
those people who used to have that
10-step routine that would take four
hours so by the way when I say all of
the stuff I'm not judging because I've
been there like I told you I'm coming up
to my 10th year as an entrepreneur when
I first made my first penny online I
have done everything I've tried
everything so I'm not sitting here
judging you I'm just trying to relay
really what actually works and what's
fluff so when you see all these 15-step
morning routine blah blah and by the way
when you see all these morning routines
where they wake up at 5am it's all Bs
wait wake up whatever time you want to
wake up it doesn't matter trust me now
here's the thing if you have work or you
have school then yeah you should be an
early riser I'm sure most of you guys
know I dropped out at 17 because I was
already making crazy money I had an
employee like I had a proper business so
I dropped out of school at 17. I also
had to take care of me and my single mom
so you know my life story was a little
different but before that when I was
still in school I used to be an early
riser I hated it I'm not really a
morning person I hate it but for me it
was getting those early hours of working
before school and those early hours of
exercise a lot of times before school it
really helped me make sure that I got
important things done so if you fall
under that category then yeah of course
maybe waking up earlier makes a lot of
sense to make sure you get everything
done always but listen if you're not in
that category wake up whatever time you
want I've used to wake up at 5am I used
to wake up at 6am I used to wake up at 7
30 am now I wake up at 8 30 because I
also spend majority of my year in Dubai
and most of my employees and most of my
team are in America and Europe so for me
it doesn't make sense to wake up at 5 30
knowing that I have calls most days up
until 9 pm most of my leadership calls
start at 5 30 and end at 9 between the
different companies so find a simple
three-step routine you know my old
routine in London let's say for example
three years ago I would wake up at 6 30
I would do a little bit of journaling
while drinking a coffee and then my
personal trainer would show up at my
doorstep we'd walk two minutes to the
gym and I would start my training
session for the day that was my
three-step morning routine now my
morning routine is a little different I
wake up and the first thing I do is I go
jump in the cold plunge so I go down to
my home gym garage I jump in the cold
plunge after that I have a shower and
get ready and the third thing is I make
myself a coffee and I sit down at this
desk and I just have 30 minutes of me
time I just jot down ideas vision for my
companies I look up my overall corporate
structure my investments where my
investments fall into within my
different entities within my different
holding companies and my different
trusts and as I said it's a lot to
manage these days and then
I get started with the day so whatever
fits best in your life now I'm very
lucky where I train at 4 P.M every day I
like that that works for me but back in
the day really the only practical time
to work out was first thing in the
morning so just find whatever works for
you but just make sure it's a three-step
morning routine no 10-step or 12 step
and nothing that takes four hours it
really generally should take you no more
than an hour hour and a half from the
moment that you wake up to the moment
that you get to your desk and you're
getting to work now last hack may seem
simple but once again that is the beauty
of it and that is that I want you to lay
out your clothes the night before the
worst thing in the morning that you can
have is the decision fatigue of deciding
okay what am I going to wear today now
I've already told you you should have
your sort of homework uniform which is
just very simple very easy to put
together but still nonetheless you
should lay it out the night before and
you especially want to lay out your
clothes if you're working out in the
morning now for me I'm gonna be honest
it's more difficult not training than it
is like I love training whatever it is
whether that's running whether that's
boxing whether that's functional
CrossFit training whatever it is like I
just enjoy it but nonetheless you want
to lay out your clothes especially if
that's something that you struggle with
in your life or especially if you
struggle to wake up in the morning trust
me it takes two minutes a night but it
makes the morning so much more seamless
so ladies and gentlemen I say all of
this with love because as I said I have
tried so much stuff and especially in my
early days I saw so many things that I
thought were important to success and
they just weren't so this is just me
being honest of what has worked for me
over the last 10 years and what hasn't I
hope it was useful to you and as always
I'm watching from afar and I'm rooting
for you