you are young I'm 17 years old you're
ambitious I worked my face off and you
want to make it big early in your life
so in today's video I'm going to reveal
the seven principles for teenagers and
people in their early 20s to become
millionaires now I made my first million
dollars at 18 years old and no matter
what you see on Tick Tock I want you to
know that that is not normal it is not
normal in any shape form or fashion but
it is because I followed these seven
principles so what I'm going to reveal
to you today not only helped me make my
first million dollars at 18 years old it
has helped me to amass a net worth of
tens of millions of dollars by the age
of 23. so I'm speaking from experience
here but I do want to make it clear that
no matter what anyone says I will hold
my hand up and say that a very large
portion of why I'm in the position I am
today is because of luck or the grace of
God in my opinion and timing so just
factor that in now real quick before we
get into today's video I've had tons of
people over the years ask me to do like
q and A's on Instagram or even here on
YouTube where I answer questions to
people's specific cases you know their
particular question and I'll be honest
my main Instagram is just a stupid place
where I post photo dumps from trips
business trips what's going on in my
life stuff like that but earlier this
year I created an Instagram account
called at talk with Eman so you can just
pull up your phone and request to follow
that account I usually tell my team to
let in a thousand or two thousand people
a week I try my best okay I'll hold my
hands up sometimes I do miss it I try my
best to do a weekly q a just answering
all of your guys's business life
questions so go ahead and follow that
account if you want a little bit more
business advice but apart from that
let's get back into the video the first
principle you need to learn if you want
to be a millionaire in your teens or
your early 20s is that in order to be a
king you must first be a pawn and this
is really the issue with this generation
and I say this generation even though I
am included in it but I grew up with
very traditional principles around
respect I come from a background that is
a mix between Eastern European and
Middle Eastern so like growing up you
have no option you learn respect and you
learn the pecking order and I learned
from a young age that you respect your
elders and that's why still to the state
I still sit across the table from people
that I'm gonna be very honest with you
are far less successful than I am but I
shut the up and I listen because
for me in my culture you listen to your
elders now that doesn't mean you need to
take everything that they say on board
but you at least listen and because I
grew up in this environment of learning
respect I learned that hey you can be a
king one day but in order to be a king
you first need to be a pawn you first
need to be able to earn your stripes and
by the way I earned my stripes from a
very young age I started my first
entrepreneurial Ventures when I was 14
and I learned what it was like to work
with clients and quite frankly for a
lack of a better word be their little
boy I learned what it was like to
pay my dues no matter what it's kind of
like listen when you're young and you
join a football team you're going to be
the one who's the ball boy at the end of
training you're going to be the one who
is expected to carry all of the
equipment to and from and you need to go
through that to one day become the
captain you don't just come in
especially as someone who is Young and
become the captain all of a sudden and
that is the issue with today's social
media Society they look at
things and they look at people and they
go okay I'm going to jump from here to
here and I deserve that for some reason
and I even get this to this day people
say hey man why do you recommend
business models that you used to do why
don't you recommend what you're doing
right now do you realize how stupid that
sounds do you realize why I may suggest
business models I did when I first
started my entrepreneurial Ventures or
within three years into my
entrepreneurial Ventures not now that I
am coming up to my 10th year as an
entrepreneur do you not realize why I
would suggest businesses that I started
as a pawn as someone with no resources
no connection no money nothing do you
realize why I suggest those businesses
rather than the businesses I have now
with millions of followers subscribers
tens of millions of dollars like I'm
sure you can kind of see why I think
this is better than this but this is
what I'm saying the younger generation
they look at things and they're like no
I want to jump straight to the Finish
Line you have to earn your
Stripes so just remember to be a king
you must first learn to be a pawn and
there is an nothing wrong with that by
the way there is honor there is no
ability in starting from the bottom of
the pecking order being quiet respecting
the process and understanding that you
will eventually work your way up the
totem pole now the next principle for
teenagers to become millionaires is
dressed to elevate and here's what I
mean by that when you are young people
are going to automatically discredit you
you don't want to make it worse by the
way that you dress so here's the thing
you can have a 30 year old that dresses
in big labels Gucci Balenciaga where's
the funny shoes and all that stuff and
listen I mean I'm not against it
sometimes when I'm feeling comfortable I
dress in streetwear but if I'm going to
an important meeting I can guarantee you
I'm not dressed like that and my point
is that you can get a 30 year old that
dresses like that that looks like a 20
year old whereas you can get a 18 or 20
year old that dresses very traditional
very classic and you can get an 18 or 20
year old that looks like they're 30. so
the point is don't spend crazy amounts
of money to have all these labels and
this and that and I don't think that's a
good idea ever unless you really can
afford ordered you have a full wardrobe
and sometimes you just want to be a
little playful my best recommendation is
just go for clothes that have no
branding No Label and I'm not saying
that you need to dress in three-piece
suits listen even if you just go in a
simple black T-shirt simple trousers
that aren't too baggy and definitely no
skinny jeans and just some classic
Timeless shape shoes listen you're not
dressing incredibly well but the point
is you can kind of hold your own in any
room sometimes less really is more so
first learn how to just dress classic
and Timeless and then later down the
line you can start incorporating some
suits you can start incorporating some
double-breasted suits maybe before you
go to the suits just get some nice
Blazers and you compare the Blazers with
trousers it doesn't need to be a full
suit you know a lot of times I'm just
very comfortable with a nice round neck
t-shirt not like this this is a lot more
you know it's a Sunday today a very home
comfortable shirt so not something as
casual as this just a nice fitted white
T-shirt or black T-shirt and smart
Blazer over the top some trousers and
some smart shoes and you have a very
classic Timeless look that's not overly
formal and you're never going to be too
overdressed in any situation and then as
I said later down the line you can get
into your double-breasted so you can get
into your three pieces whatever you feel
comfortable in really but the point is
that you really need to learn how to
dress to elevate especially if you're
going into the world of business at a
young age because I'm being honest with
you I experience this firsthand people
will try to discredit you because of
your age so don't give them any excuse
or Reason to make it an even bigger
thing than it needs to be so dress older
than you are now the third principle for
teenagers to become millionaires is have
something external that humbles you and
here's what I mean by that there's a lot
of people who are young with a lot of
ambition in their life but the issue is
there's nothing in their life that has
humbled them things that will humble you
Combat Sports business will humble you
because no matter how good you are when
you get in the world of business the
market will tell you how good you are
I'll give you a perfect example I
remember when I was 17 years old I had
gone up to I think 15 or 20 grand in my
business at that point I dropped out of
school the month prior and I hired my
first employee full-time employee fifty
thousand dollars a year which by the way
for a first employee was like at 17 that
was big for me and I'll never forget it
this person even moved country to join
my company AKA just me and within three
to four days he quit packed up his stuff
and went back to his country and was
like I do not enjoy this work and I
remember it was one of the very few
times I've ever cried in my life I
remember talking to my mom and just
crying and just being like wow I feel
like a failure your business is taking
off and you're hiring your first
employee and they leave because a the
work isn't enjoyable enough or
potentially and this is something I had
to face at the time maybe I just really
wasn't an inspiring leader maybe I
wasn't a sort of leader where my team
was like I would follow you into war and
things are very different now that I
have 150 employees we get 40 000 people
a year applying to work at one of my
companies because I was humbled when I
was 17 that hey maybe you're not as good
as you think you are maybe you think
that you're this little child prodigy
are you sure about that let me humble
you so whether it's business whether
it's Combat Sports you need something
external in your life to Humble you and
put you in your place because the thing
is especially if you earn a lot of
success at a young age you're gonna
start to think you're hot and if
you don't have anything to Humble you
you will end up becoming your worst
enemy the next principle you need to
follow is no casual dating either
something serious or nothing at all
listen if you are in your teenage years
or your early 20s either you go for
something serious no casual dates no
casual flings stuff like that listen you
are a man in your early years make
something of yourself and either have a
partner early on they will support you
through that as something serious or
none of this casual hinge Tinder blah
blah all this none of this casual dating
because let me tell you something it is
taking you away from your best years
your best years to build and the other
thing is we live in a very brutal dating
culture I'm gonna be very honest with
you so why b19 trying to navigate this
crazy difficult dating culture where
there's successful men all around the
world that through Instagram and all of
these other mediums have access to all
these women why would you at 19 try to
compete with that either you have that
serious girl that holds it down for you
or don't try to casual date if you want
a casual date and have your fun and
listen I'm speaking to someone who has
had both sides of the equation into the
state I still like to have my fun
there's nothing wrong with it but I put
my head down and work like a dog for
years and years and I remember even
being 19 20 and being a
multi-millionaire and I said to myself
what's the point of me really focusing
on women and having fun and enjoying
myself with all these women when girls
don't want guys for 19 or 20 and you
need to understand this as a guy you
become most attractive once you get past
the age of 25 really from 25 to 35 is
when you're most attractive to women and
it really only starts at 25. so I
remember even being 19 or 20 and I'm
like yes this is great I'm a
multi-millionaire I'm all these things
but like let me just keep working like
I'm on a roll like all momentum let me
just keep this going rather than trying
to have the most fun and date girls and
Bubba and all this crap so as I said no
casual dating either you are dating
someone serious that you're like this
woman could be that day one for me and
by the way that day one girl listen
please take this coming from me there is
nothing on Earth nothing on earth that
is more viable than that if you've got a
day one girl and you managed to get a
day one girl you know all these girls on
a y'all private job I have done and
still do all these things but I
understand that that does not come
remotely close to a day one girl who is
there from you from the jump from day
one so either aim for that because by
the way that is the most valuable thing
you could ever get in life I'm telling
you this so either you get that or just
don't casual date because you are in
your building phase you have so long
especially as a man and I know I keep
talking to men and I understand that
there's a I think 10 of my audience is
women and I always do say I make content
specifically for men because I grew up
without a dad I had to learn all this
myself so that's why I speak to the
young men out there but I know a lot of
women still watch my videos and take
lessons from it and stuff like that so
as I was saying keep your head down keep
focused no casual dating and
then once you've made something of
yourself pop your head up and and then
you can have a little bit of fun before
eventually hopefully one day you find
your actual Queen principle number five
is keep your circles small but your
influence large and here's what I mean
by that there is nothing wrong with many
people knowing you or with you having
many acquaintances but you should have
very few friends and here's the thing
most people in this fake life
don't know the difference between an
acquaintance and a friend because most
people don't understand what true
loyalty is they are around people that
they don't like they're around people
for clout or money and this and that and
that's why by the way it's so important
to get yourself strong first so this way
people later down line can't throw money
or women or clout at you and you're
impressed by it you need to make
yourself strong you need to make
yourself a fortress but back to the
point keep your circle tight but you're
influence large many people can and
should know of you and I'm not talking
about having a massive social media
following or this or that I just mean
even in the industry you're in never
unnecessarily burn Bridges always be
very polite and courteous to people but
always understand that you can probably
only have a select handful of true
friends true Brothers in Arms true
people that will love you and do
anything for you that's a very very
small circle so your circle of influence
can and should be large but keep your
actual Circle solid and full of good
people the next principle you need to
follow is that God will always test you
to see what you can handle and if you
can't he will take it away from you and
this is very very important because
becoming successful and making your
first million in your teens or your
early 20s that's great congratulations
can you keep it now and not only can you
keep it can you multiply it because
that's a lot of pressure listen if you
make your first million dollars when
you're 18 or you're 20 or you're you
know even 23 that's great but that's a
lot of pressure every year after that
can you hold that same standard so you
need to understand that God If He
blesses you if he gives you that million
at a young age he's gonna see if you can
handle it he's gonna see if you can
humble yourself that's why earlier I
told you have things external in your
life that will constantly humble you
business martial arts setting challenges
for yourself and seeing if you can
accomplish things that really make you
dig deep because here's the thing if you
don't have these external things to
Humble you if you don't humble yourself
God will humble you and when God humbles
you it's with a ferocity you can't even
imagine because you're not ready for it
yet as quickly as it's given it's taken
away and you need to understand these
things so as long as you go into it with
a mindset that when you make your first
million you're not going to be driving
around in the G-Wagon and you're gonna
go to the bank like a idiot and take out
thirty thousand dollars in cash so that
way you can do an Instagram story where
you spread all the money in your hands
and now all you do is listen to little
baby in your rented G-Wagon and pop
bottles at the beach club and now your
business is just on autopilot God will
put you in your place so before that
happens put other things in place I've
already given a few but even if you can
get an older Mentor an older Confidant
to look at you and be like you ain't
doing it once is nothing special you're
only a legend if you can do it back to
back to back that's when you're a legend
now the last principle to tie it all
together is invest early and invest as
much as you can here is the thing if you
make money at a young age try to get
away from you as soon as possible I'm
talking about property I'm talking about
maybe even buying some physical gold I'm
talking about things where the money can
get away from you and it's not easy to
sell here's the issue sometimes and I'm
not totally opposed to it here's
sometimes the issue with crypto or
stocks you can buy and sell very easily
you can't buy and sell real estate very
easily so buying things that aren't
actually very liquid at a young age I
think later down the line once you're
established that can actually be a
detriment actually makes things a little
bit more difficult but when you're a
young age you are your worst enemy
you're the probably the biggest reason
you're gonna this up so what you
want to do is once you make money push
it away as quick as possible because
here's the other thing and once again
I'm talking from experience when you are
young and you make a lot of money you
know what people think people don't
think oh well done people think you got
lucky so there's no point being 19 years
old driving all these supercars and blah
blah all this stuff because you're not
impressing anyone people just think
you're lucky that's it you're better off
taking the money investing it and when
you're 23 you're 25 you get to an age
where people can kind of believe this
has happened a little bit more maybe you
know you're 22 but you're dressed apart
and people think you're a little older
and that's when you can enjoy and you
can live it up and you can do these
things because when you get out of your
Supercar people will actually think that
you bought that but when you're 19 and
you look young people will either think
you got lucky they're going to think you
invest in some pump and dumb coin or
they're gonna think Daddy's money so
while you're trying to flex and let's be
honest if you're young and you're buying
these supercars you're probably trying
to flex it's not even having the
intended effect so just tell yourself
you know what any money that comes in
I'm gonna invest as much as I humanly
can I'm gonna make myself solid and I'm
gonna enjoy these things a little later
down the line so ladies and gentlemen I
present to you these principles as
someone who can speak to you more
realistically because let's be honest a
lot of these YouTube videos you watch
online are some 50 year olds that lived
in a different generation and don't
understand that hey there's nothing
wrong with wanting beautiful women
around you there's nothing wrong with
wanting money having nice cars all these
things there's nothing wrong with that
but there's a way to do it there's a
time and a place so I'm just coming here
and speaking to you guys from experience
and trying to meet you guys of where you
are which is not trying to shame you for
the things you want in life but just
telling you there is a way to do it and
there's a right timing to do things so
as I said I hope this has been a value
to you as a reminder I'm a little bit
more active on that talk with Iman for
actual sort of business q and A's so go
ahead and follow that account and as
always I'm watching from afar and I'm
rooting for you