tired of speaking maybe don't want to do
your own speech
well there's an app for that so in this
video we're going to be taking a look at
how you can take
text and convert it to speech also known
as text to speech now you're probably
wondering
why the hell is he wearing this hat well
in this case what we're going to be
taking a look at
is how to convert text from different
languages as well as english
to be able to generate speech so we'll
actually be taking a look at how to
convert
french to french speech let's take a
look in a little bit more detail as to
what we're going to be covering so this
video is going to be a bit of a crash
course on text-to-speech conversion so
the first thing that we're going to be
doing is converting a simple variable
from
python into a speech file so we'll
output it to mp3
we'll then take a look at how you can
pre-process text documents so say you've
got a bunch of files that you want to
convert
we'll be able to convert that to speech
as well last but not least we'll also
take a look at how we can convert using
different language models so we'll take
a look at all the different languages
available
and we'll specifically convert using one
of those
we'll also cover all the setup that you
need to go through so in this case we're
going to be using watson
text to speech so we'll cover all of
that as well now in terms of how we're
going to be doing it we're going to be
working inside of a jupyter notebook so
we'll capture all
of our content or our corpus using
python
we'll then send that text to the watson
text-to-speech service so that will be
allow us to perform that conversion
and then from there we'll output that as
an audio file so it'll be an
mp3 file that will be able to convert
you can do it in a bunch of other
formats but we'll use
mp3 in this case ready to get to it
let's do it
so the first thing that we're going to
do before we start converting our
text to speech is lay out our jupyter
notebook so there's
four key steps that we want to go
through inside of our python jupyter
notebook
those are installing our dependencies
setting up our speech to text server so
authenticating
then we're going to convert a basic
model read a file from text
and convert that and we're also going to
use a new language model
all right so we've got the basic layout
for our jupiter notebook setup so again
as we said we're going to first up
install our dependencies then
authenticate
convert a string read from a file and
convert that and then last but not least
we're going to convert with a different
language model
so this allows you to convert with a
chinese language model an arabic
language model
there's a whole heap of different
language support so let's go on ahead
and first up install our dependencies so
in this case there's one key dependency
and that's ibm watson
now in order to install our dependency
we're just going to use the pip install
command
so that's now done so you can see we've
just used an exclamation mark and then
we've typed in pip install ibm watson so
that's our key dependency
now installed now the next thing that we
need to do is authenticate so because
we're using
the watson text to speech service we
need to go and set up a text-to-speech
service first
so in order to do that all we need to do
is go to cloud.ibm.org
forward slash catalog and then from
there all you need to do is hit
services so if we zoom in so select
services
scroll on down to ai slash machine
learning and choose that
then from here you can see there's a
whole bunch of different services the
one that we're looking for
is text to speech so this one down here
so if we select text to speech
so you can see from here that we've got
a light plan and that's going to give us
10 000 characters of conversion per
month
and it'll be deleted after 30 days of
inactivity so in this case when we're
just getting started out this is more
than enough to to go and convert our
text to speech so let's choose that
light plane and hit create
so our text-to-speech service is now
being created you can see it's called
text to speech dash
wk now what we need from our text to
speech service are our api key and
our service url so to grab that all we
need to do is go to manage and you'll
have your api key here
and your url here so both of those
details are just
under the credentials box now what we'll
do in order to store those in our
jupyter notebook is just create
two new variables so we'll create one
for our url and one for our api key
so now let's go ahead and copy over our
url and api key
into these variables
so those are the core components that
we're going to need from our speech to
tech service so you can see here that
we've got our url
and we've also got our api key so those
are the core things that we're going to
need
now what we want to do is actually start
authenticating now in order to do that
we're going to need to import some
dependencies from the ibm watson sdk
that we just installed
what we've done is we've imported two
key dependencies so we've imported the
text to speech
class so this is going to allow us to
work with our text to speech service
and we've also imported iam
authenticator so that's just going to
allow us to authenticate to our text to
speech servers
now what we want to go and do is
actually go and create a new instance of
the text to speech class and go and
authenticate against it
so that's our service now set up now
what we've done is three key things so
we've gone
and imported our authenticator and
passed through our api key
we've also gone and created a new
instance of the text to speech
service and pass through our
authenticator and then last but not
least we've set our service url so
that's basically where our server sits
in the world wide web
so that's really our service done now
now what we can actually go and do
is go and convert some speech to text so
in this case we're going to start off
with a basic conversion
and what we'll do is we'll just convert
hello world
now when we go and convert we pass
through a string or a body of text
and this is going to output a file that
we'll then be able to read so when we're
going to be outputting
our speech what we'll do is we'll just
output it to the folder that we've got
our jupyter notebook in so you can see
here that this is our jupyter notebook
and we've also got a text file which
we'll convert in a second as well
so let's go on ahead and just convert
the string hello world first to see how
it works
so what we've gone and done is we've
created a new
speech.mp3 file so this means that we're
going to use this file object to go and
write out our file
then we've gone and used our
text-to-speech service which we created
up here
and we've synthesized the words hello
world so ideally our speech should come
out saying hello world
we've also passed through a couple of
keyword parameters so in this case we're
just saying that we want to output an
mp3
and we've also chosen the voice that we
want to use or the language model
so the text-to-speech service has a
bunch of different language models i've
just used
a u.s one and in this case it's a female
us voice
by the name of allison and then the last
thing that we've done is gone and
grabbed the result
then we've gone and written out that
file so if we go and take a look inside
of our folder we should have a file
called speech.mp3
and you can see that we've got a file
now available so what we can do is play
that file hello world
and you can see that we've now gone and
generated our speech so we've gone and
taken
hello world and we've converted that to
output hello world
what we can do is we can change this so
in this case i might say hello youtube
and test that out hello
youtube and you can see that we're now
able to really really quickly convert
our text to speech what happens if we
wanted to go
and convert a text file for example
rather than just
inputting a keyword so say we wanted to
productionize this and we wanted to pick
up text files and convert those in real
time
well we can do that pretty easily all we
need to do is just read in a
text file so here i've got a bit of a
speech
from winston churchill now what we can
do is actually go and read in this text
file
and convert that
so we're going to follow a similar
manner to what we just did here the only
difference is that we're first going to
read up our text file
okay so we've now gone and read in our
text files so if we take a look
you can see that this is all the text
that we had within
our document so in this case what we did
is we opened up our file and then we
just read the lines from that
now you can see that we've got a slash
enter a new line indicator on each one
of these different lines what we want to
do whenever we pass our text to the text
to speech service
you have one single block of text so
what we'll do is a little bit of
pre-processing so to convert
this entire array and number of strings
to one single block of text
so what we've gone and done is replace
that new line indicator with a blank
space so that's just going to strip that
out and then we've gone and concatenated
all of them together so what we've done
is we've used a list comprehension so
four line in text
to allow us to loop through each one of
those and then ideally
what we should get out is a single
block of text which you can see here now
what we can do is follow
a similar process to what we did up here
so we can just copy this block
now what we're going to do is rather
than having hello youtube
all we need to do is pass through this
text block here so let's go and replace
that
and we're going to call this file
churchill instead
so ideally what we should now have is
another file which is just exported
called churchill.mp3
now this might take a little bit longer
because again our text is longer now so
it's going to have to convert
a whole lot more but again it shouldn't
take too long perfect so that looks like
it's completed now if we go and take a
look we
indeed do have a churchill.mp3 file so
we can play that we shall go on to the
end
we shall fight in france we shall fight
on the seas and oceans
we shall perfect you get the idea so
we've gone and now
read in a text file and converted that
to mp3 so now the last thing that we
want to take a look at is using a
different language model so rather than
just converting to english
what happens if we wanted to convert in
chinese or dutch or arabic or one of the
other amazing languages
that the entire world uses well the
great thing about our text-to-speech
service is that it supports a number of
different languages
so if we actually go to the
documentation you can actually see that
there are a
whole heap of different languages
supported so we've got brazilian
mandarin dutch a whole bunch of
different others
now what we're going to do in this case
is convert
using french because i'm a bit of a
frenchie
now let's go and do that so rather than
the core thing that we need to do
whenever we're converting in a different
language is just pass through the
different voice
so if we take a look at our different
voices you can see in french we've got a
few different ones there
so what we'll do is convert using this
one down here so renee v3
and we'll just create a new variable and
then all we need to do is again
grab our text block so i've got a
lullaby that my grandma actually used to
sing to me so it's called freya jacka
i'm probably butchering that
of jacques so let's go and paste that in
so in this case all we need to do is
copy our conversion block
paste that in and this time we need to
replace two things so we're just going
to
because our text is contained in a
variable called freya
we're just going to grab that offrair
and replace
the text here we'll call this french
conversion
and the last thing that we're going to
do is change our voice because that's
the core thing that we need to change
whenever we want to use a different
language model because we've got our
voice contained in a variable here we
can just copy that
and just set this to this variable
that's now done so if we go and take a
look we've got a french conversion
block as well
and you can see we've now gone and
converted now you can see that that's a
little bit fast and that's because we
don't actually have full stops here
and that's because it's going to read it
so it can ideally convert our text to
speech exactly as it's written so if we
actually add full stops here
you can see that we're going to get a
bit more of a pause between each one of
these sentences
so that's now converted now if we go and
take a look at that
freya foreign
so you can see there's a little bit more
of a pause between each one of those
sentences now so it's replicating how we
speak
that about wraps up how to convert text
to speech in a nutshell so just
recap so what we've done is we've gone
and imported out or installed our
dependencies so we installed ibm watson
we then authenticated against our
service converted
a string converted a file and last but
not least
we used a new language model but again
keep in mind there's a whole heap of
different language models
if you want to get started thanks so
much for tuning in guys hopefully you
found this video useful if you did be
sure to give it a thumbs up hit
subscribe and tick that bell so you get
notified of any future videos
let me know what text you were able to
convert in the mentions below and let me
know if this video helped you
again if you've got any questions at all
be sure to drop a mention in the
comments and i'll get
right back to you thanks again for
tuning in peace