here's how you get ahead of 99% of
people in the next 6 to 12 months times
are changing and we are about to
experience one of the greatest wealth
transfers in history and if you want to
be on the receiving end of it there's
one thing that you must do implement the
five lost principles of The Outsiders in
order to become an outsider yourself and
unlock a life of freedom and today I'm
going to show you how I rescued these
principles myself and implemented them
in my own personal life which ultimately
led me to the success I have today and
how you too can rescue them in your own
life this is the
rescue let me ask you a question do you
have the false belief that money equals
Freedom you see the first step I ever
took in my journey was to establish what
truth would guide my way because
ultimately the truth that you choose to
subscribe to will determine your path
and from very early on I I was able to
see through the lies and the
manipulation of the conditioning Factory
and really see the education system for
what it actually is a factory that's
only purpose is to turn you into a
product of the system and I simply tried
to evaluate from a rational standpoint
what was the outcome of the people who
went through the system which was they'd
go to college then they'd study slave
like hours for 4 to six years only then
to graduate and continue to work slave
like hours somewhere else usually in a
job they hate that doesn't pay well and
even in the rare cases that it does they
have no time or location Freedom
whatsoever to enjoy the money they make
and back then I didn't know much but I
knew one thing that's not the life I
wanted for myself and I vividly remember
the day I decided that that was not
going to be my truth I must have been 14
at the time and I was taking the tube in
rush hour in London it was one of those
classic rainy London days but that still
felt so humid and sticky and everything
just looked gray the tube was packed
with people coming from work those days
where you can smell the sweat mixed with
that terrible smell of wet dog that
people have from walking in the rain and
listen that was one thing but worse was
that I'd look in the faces of every
single person coming in and out of the
tube and I remember I could just see the
pain and the frustration in their faces
how you could clearly notice that none
of them wanted to be there but they
simply had had no choice but to be there
because that's the only truth that they
knew that was the truth that they had
been conditioned to believe and I just
remember how depressing it felt to be
there amongst those people and
ultimately how when I grew up I never
wanted to be like that and it was on
that day when I was 13 years old on the
tube that I made the decision that was
not going to be my personal truth and
for the longest time I actually used to
have a photo of the London Underground
the London Tube as the background of my
trailer board where I had my daily to-do
tasks and to me that was really just a
reminder that that wasn't the truth that
I had chosen for myself and back then I
decided that it didn't matter how long
it would take or how much it would cost
I would find a way to live life on my
own terms a life where I would be able
to make Fu money and to me Fu money
means more money than you realistically
know what to do with and without having
to sell my soul to the system or slave
away in a corporate job until I was 60 I
mean after all I knew it was possible
because I saw other people doing it it
it's funny I remember I always used to
show my mom episodes from Ryan sir hence
million dooll listing and I always used
to tell my mom look you know I can do
this it's possible to make millions
without going to school and if I saw
other people do it in my mind I could do
it too there was nothing that they did
that I couldn't do myself listen they
weren't building Rockets they weren't
programming a machine Learning System
they were selling houses and I knew I
could do that too and obviously you guys
know the story I didn't end up going the
real estate path that's not how I made
my money but what matters is that I knew
that there was an ocean of opportunities
out there that could provide me with
financial location and time freedom and
without me having to slave away at a
corporate job for decades to achieve it
and that was my truth and the craziest
part of this entire story is that 10
years later a decade later Ryan Siran
ended up reaching out to me because he
wanted to feature me in his new book and
then we also ended up meeting up and
collaborating on a YouTube video
together so I ended up just being one of
those crazy full circle moments you know
from watching this guy at 13 and being
like I can do something and obviously I
didn't end up going the route that he
went but I made so much of myself that
someone that I used to look up to ended
up wanting to feature me inside of his
book so the world really does work in
crazy ways now it's very important for
me to be nuanced here because as I've
mentioned multiple times already the
truth is a very subjective and personal
concept at the end of the day it changes
from person to person and what's the
truth for me might not be the truth for
you for example if you truly want to
become an engineer a doctor a lawyer and
and that's what you want to do because
you've clearly experienced what it's
like to be an engineer a doctor or a
lawyer not because you've been
conditioned to want these professions
because their Prestige or because the
conditioning Factory brainwashed you
into thinking you'd make a lot of money
and become free through these
professions if you truly want to follow
one of these paths because that's what
you're truly passionate about so be it
then that is your truth and no one can
tell you otherwise and obviously I can't
help you in those cases because that's
not where my exp ertes and that's
totally fine there's still a lot of
people out there who can help you follow
those paths now what is important to
attain yourself is why you chose that as
your truth if the reason you want to
pursue those careers is so that you can
achieve the outcomes that the system has
sold you on them that the reason as to
why you want to become a doctor a lawyer
an engineer is because those are the
safest and most Surefire ways to get
financial location and time Freedom you
might really want to question where do
those beliefs come from are they
actually based on cold hard facts or are
they simply based on what the
conditioning Factory has told you are
those beliefs making you free or are
they making you a product of the system
again you need to truly stop and reflect
on what truth actually means for you
because the truth you choose to
subscribe to will determine your path
and your path will determine your
results maybe going to college is your
truth maybe it's not it all depends on
your answer answer to the
question this is how I unwired my
limiting beliefs growing up we're fed
with dozens of limiting beliefs that if
not taken care will affect us profoundly
through our entire lives at this point
you already know that but there's
usually a problem getting rid of them is
a hard thing to do and the reason why
it's such a hard thing to do is when
you're first starting out you have no
references to base yourself on you don't
don't know how successful people operate
because respectfully you probably have
never spent time with successful people
in the first place growing up majority
of us spend our time with our parents
our teachers our friends who usually
come from a family with very similar
economic backgrounds to our own so what
ends up happening is that these people
just reinforce those already existing
limiting beliefs that's inside of us you
know I'll even tell you a little story
about this my first tattoo here it says
my cup runneth over it's written in the
Old Testament and I actually got this
tattoo when I was 16 years old you know
I was definitely a very naughty teenager
and obviously with all areas of my life
I grew up very quickly so I definitely
don't recommend you go getting a tattoo
at 16 but the reason I got this my cup
runneth over it basically means that I
have more than I need I'm overflowing
I'm abundant and the reason I got this
tattoo and the reason it was very
important to me as a constant reminder
to myself was growing up my mom always
used to tell me take as much as you can
because you never know when you're going
to get anymore and that was her truth
and I told totally empathize with that
truth because listen when you are the
youngest of seven children growing up in
the Soviet Union that statement is true
you really don't know when you're going
to get anymore so if something's in
front of you take as much as you can and
this what I'm saying beliefs can get
passed down to your parents even if they
don't serve you so between that and also
a lot of the financial struggles that we
had growing up you know me and her my
mom almost used to tell me take as much
as you can because you don't know where
you're going to get anymore and that
just didn't serve me that was my
attitude growing up even though I still
a young kid I would always think like
how can I get the better end of this
deal or if there's a certain amount of
something how can I get the most of it
or even just down to small things I
would always overeat even if I was full
I would force myself to eat more because
my mom's voice was always in my head
that belief system was always in my head
and one of the things I will give myself
credit for was working through that
limiting belief system you know I ended
up getting the tattoo and said I'm not
saying you should get a tattoo but the
rest of my life ever since I was 16
years old I have been so abundant even
when I had nothing I I acted so
abundantly I gave so much I was so
generous with the people around me if
they deserved it obviously and weren't
just there for the ride and it just
broke this belief so this is stuff that
I've had to work through over the years
many things in my life that's just one
example now getting back to you again
you really can't address or get rid of
those beliefs if these are the only
beliefs that you know you know the way I
like to explain it is this the amount of
colors that our eyes can see is actually
very small compared to the amount of
colors that's out there in the entire
light spectrum for example there are a
few birds that can actually see
ultraviolet light which obviously we
can't see and that means that they can
see millions of colors that we don't
even imagine exist you know if they were
to look at the most colorful TV screens
that exist today you know they'd
probably think to themselves what
horribly unrealistic colors but from our
perspective the 6K or 8K TV it looks
extremely photorealistic and that's
because we judge things for what we can
see and the same happens with our
beliefs and our experiences we all
experience the world based on our own
limiting realities that are based on the
things that we know know and we see
however that's not the full reality
because there are a lot of things that
you don't know or you don't get to see
or you don't get to experience and
that's why you might have dozens of
limiting beliefs that you're not even
aware of because you're not even aware
that different realities exist and
unfortunately the average person has no
idea on how different rich people think
and approach things compared to broke
people let me give you a very concrete
example most people operate from a place
of scarcity especially when it comes to
money which also makes them very
emotional towards money they're always
afraid that they won't have enough or
that the process of making money is
always hard miserable and stressful
because that's what they've always
experienced or the classic example of
someone who operates from that mindset
and just started a business and is
afraid to charge higher prices because
he thinks that everyone else has the
same view on money that they have and
that if something costs more than $200
no one's going to buy it because it's
too expensive all while the same time
there's competitors selling the same
product or service for two times five
times 10 times the price and this really
all comes back to their limited
reference towards money listen I can
tell you from firsthand experience you'd
be surprised how indifferent rich people
are towards money and by the way that's
usually why they make so much money in
the first place because they're not
emotional about it they're not afraid of
charging more they're not afraid of
investing heavy amounts of money knowing
very well that they could lose it all
now the point I want to get to here is
this the only way to truly get rid of
your limiting beliefs is by having more
references and that is observing how
successful people specifically think
approach and act on things and what type
of beliefs they hold compared to what
you currently hold and the only way to
do that is by spending time with
successful people now obviously the
problem is where do you find those
people and how do you get them to spend
time with you in the first place well
that's the question I asked myself when
I was 13 you see back then I didn't know
any successful people that I could spend
time with to learn from it and
understand how they think and what
beliefs they hold so I found a solution
to that books back when I was 13 14 15 I
would spend entire afternoons at Brixton
book mongers in London reading
secondhand books they had there and I
used to literally just read the books
there because I couldn't afford to buy
more than two or three books a month so
I used to go there and just try to read
as many books in an afternoon as
possible you know I was reading so much
that if you really thought about it
majority of my time was spent with
extremely successful individuals not
physically but in the world of ideas
which according to Plato as we mentioned
in episode 2 is technically the real
world anyways Jokes Aside by doing that
I really started to share the same
beliefs and World Views that these
successful people had and by doing so it
really started to unwire all of the
limiting beliefs towards money and
success that the conditioning Factory
had deeply injected into my brain I was
essentially hacking my way into spending
time with successful people who were
completely inaccessible to me back then
now that doesn't mean that you need to
read hundreds of books like I did
Growing Up but you do need to learn from
people who are more successful than you
which led us directly to our next
principle of the
outsider just like with all things they
come with positive and negative sides
and reading books is also one of them
here's the thing books are a great
source of knowledge especially when it
comes to the belief side of things but
this is only one part of the equation
the other part is that you need to know
how to take the knowledge you have and
break it down into an actionable plan
that you can Implement in real life and
the problem with books is that they're
written in a way so that they're
relevant to a mass audience which means
that the author needs to give advice
that's going to be relevant to people
from very different ages very different
backgrounds and most importantly
in very different fields of work and
career stages which in turn means that
their advice has to be somewhat Broad
and non-specific and that's really the
big problem with books their advice is
not tailored to your specific situation
which means that even if you do read
hundreds of books like I did you'll
still have to figure out a bunch of
things by yourself and that's usually
when people fail because the devil is in
the details and that's why having a
mentor is of such importance they can
really analyze your situation from their
perspective and since they're so much
more resourceful than you are they can
pinpoint exactly what you need to do or
what you're doing wrong and it's usually
something that if you were to try to do
yourself it would take you months of
failing and bumping your head against
the wall in order for you to figure out
how to do it on your own sometimes even
years and that's why it took me so long
to achieve success and most people get
very confused when I say that because
they see me achieving a lot of success
at a young age so they just assume that
I got here quickly but the reality is I
just got so successful so young because
I started so early on not because I
succeeded fast per se as I said back
when I was 13 I was already reading
dozens of books trying to figure out how
to be successful something that most
people only start doing in their mid-20s
so the reason I'm 10 years ahead is just
because I started 10 years earlier now I
could have achieved success way quicker
if I had mentors from the Geto because
if you really evaluate my progress it
took me around 5 years to achieve what
most most people who follow the right
advice tend to achieve in one or two and
I knew that and I also knew that a
mentor could help me FasTrack my way to
success but there was just one big
problem I couldn't afford a mentor and
this is really the Paradox of having a
mentor a person is only a qualified
Mentor if they have achieved success
themselves which means they probably
already make a lot of money so an hour
of their time is going to be pretty damn
expensive and that's the Paradox here
having mentors is one of the most
Surefire ways to success but having
mentors is expensive and you can only
really afford them once you're
successful already so how do you do it
if you're a beginner who can't afford to
drop tens of thousands of dollars a
month on mentorship but you still want
to have a mentor and that was the
problem that I personally faced and
that's why I resorted to using books as
my mentors so if you're in a position
where you don't have a single penny in
your bank account you have no job or no
income coming in you have no access to
money whatsoever if that is the case
then I'd recommend you start doing the
same thing that I did use books as your
guide but let's not sit here and
ourselves and say that you're
mentored by Elon Musk because you've
watched a YouTube video of him or you
read his biography because you're not
it's simple if you cannot ask him
questions he's not your mentor and you
are going to be missing out on the most
important aspect of having a mentor
which is the tailored advice to your
specific situation coming from someone
who's way more resourceful than you are
now I found another way of getting
mentors at a huge discount without ever
having to drop tens of thousands of
dollars a month to get only a few
minutes of their time and I'll go ahead
and explain exactly how in just a
second now seeking intense hardship is
one of the most important principles of
them all you can go ahead and write this
down you are not going to be successful
if you don't become a master of
self-discipline and self-control if it's
very simple in order to be successful
you need to execute on stuff day in and
day out consistently and that requires
very high levels of discipline it's easy
to do something for 2 weeks in a row now
think about what positive action have
you executed on every single day day in
and day out without fail for 90 days in
a row most people nothing except for
scrolling on Tik talk and maybe that's
why you haven't achieved the levels of
success you want to get to and you might
have heard me talking about some called
monk mode that was my way to hack
discipline and self-control in my
day-to-day life you see nowadays on
average we live very comfortable lives
even compared to what the wealthiest
humans on Earth would live like even
just a few hundred years ago we don't
have to suffer with a lack of food we
don't have to endure extreme
temperatures because when it's cold we
have Heating and when it's hot we just
turn on the air conditioning and that
has put us in a very unique situation
that as humans we're not used to and
it's made us too comfortable it's made
us weak and and tapping into that inner
discipline and living a life of
self-control is one of the biggest
advantages you can have in a world of
distractions and instant gratification
and that's why I created my mck mode
protocol and the discipline and
self-control that comes with it has made
me be able to achieve two times five
times 10 times more than I ever would
have been able to if I was just another
Instagram gratification driven human
being most people have no idea just how
much they can achieve in 90 days of
focus discipline execution day in and
day out because that's exactly what the
conditioning Factory wants for you they
don't want you to know your true
potential they want you addicted to
their dopamine peaking social networks
so that way you can't help to live
without it and that's exactly what the
monk mode protocol seeks to fix and that
is how you reset your brain for Success
the way it works is very simple you
select a period to stick to for your
monk mode protocol anywhere from 21 to
90 days
then we have three non-negotiable tasks
that you have to do every single day
missed the day you failed and you start
all over from zero and the three
non-negotiables are 30 minutes of
exercise whatever exercise you want to
do 10 minutes of meditation and no
alcohol or then you can add anywhere
from one to three custom variables to
tailor your monk mode routine
specifically to your situation that
could be reading 10 pages a day working
on your business for 4 hours a day
having less than 2 hours of screen time
on your mobile phone whatever you feel
like is going to push the needle forward
for you and just by doing that for 21 to
90 days you'll become a more disciplined
individual than 95% of the world's
population and the results will speak
for themselves I mean listen I know that
they did for me and if you combine this
with one specific thing that I'm going
to show you in just a second the results
you can achieve in 90 days will be
greater than what most regular people
can achieve in years
now here's what most people get wrong
about achieving Freedom the truth is you
don't need to become a millionaire to
become a free person you can achieve
Freedom making as little as $5,000 a
month $10,000 a month because income is
all relative for example a lot of people
look up to professions like doctors
because in most countries they make a
lot of money you know it's a very
achievable way to make $40,000 $80,000
maybe even $100,000 a month as an
example but that comes out at a cost
time location and often your sanity why
because usually doctors have to work
double or triple shifts just to make
those amounts and at first when you're
young that's fine you know you have a
lot of energy and you can endure it the
problem is it's not sustainable and even
worse most doctors when they start
making that type of money they start
living a lifestyle that requires that
amount of money to sustain it meaning
they become a slave of their own life
style and that's exactly what the
conditioning Factory wants for you
because no man is more enslaved than the
one who falsely believes in his own
freedom I mean just think about it are
you really free if you can't go
somewhere you want at the time you want
no you're not and if you can't go where
you want because you lack money that's
fine you know that that's fixable now if
the reason you can't go wherever you
want to go is because someone else
doesn't allow you to even if you have
the money to do so you're enslaved
you're still a product of the system I
mean after all who is truly free the
doctor who makes $100,000 a month but is
a slave to his lifestyle and can only go
wherever he wants for 2 weeks of a year
and sometimes he doesn't even get to
choose specifically which weeks those
are or the guy that makes $10,000 a
month but can work from anywhere they
want at any time of the week and chooses
to spend his money however he wants
because he's not bound to any specific
lifestyle listen the answer is obvious
understand this freedom is not about how
much money you have but rather how much
money you make without having to
sacrifice the financial location and
time aspects of your personal life to do
it and that's why I personally chose the
ladder I chose to be the guy that can
work from anywhere I chose to be the guy
that can do whatever he wants whenever
he wants and I chose to be the guy who
ends up making more money than any
career that the conditioning Factory
tells you to pursue because that's what
Financial Freedom truly means and in
order to do so I followed a very
specific curriculum that allowed me to
accomplish that and the first step in
this curriculum was to choose the right
industry to be in today 80% of success
is being in the right industry I mean
just look at everyone who's successful
at your age right now and in what
industry they're in they're not lawyers
they're not doctors they're not dentists
they are all Outsiders every single one
of them succeeded outside of the system
where the Internet it's simple today
succeeding in the the internet is 10
times easier than succeeding within the
system because the amount of demand for
people who have internet related skills
is huge and the amount of people who
possess those skills is so little I mean
just ask anyone that has a company that
sells through the internet what their
biggest problem is their answer is
always going to be the same finding good
talent the truth is there's a few very
specific skills that if you possess them
you become an extremely valued
professional and as long as you pick up
the right skills success becomes becomes
inevitable because the amount of
businesses out there seeking for people
with those skill sets and by the way
willing to pay top dollar for them is
immense inside of educate my online
education platform I have thousands of
students who for the longest time were
stuck being a product of the system and
went on to Achieve Financial Freedom to
those exact same skills and I'll reveal
them in a second as well as the exact
curriculum I've followed to make
millions and Achieve Financial location
and time freedom for myself so look what
you have to do now above all else is
analyze what's happening today there's
two big events unfolding the first is
the push for stage four conditioning the
media the school systems the big
industries that have final say on how
the school system is ran even the social
media networks they are all owned by the
same people the big universities that
have more in their endowment accounts
than most Fortune 500 companies have in
their bank accounts while they're
working closely with Wall Street to
enforce their agenda down your throats
both in University settings as well as
in the workspace the conditioning
Factory has everything streamline they
have all their pieces in the right
places they already control the
narrative they control what can and
can't be said they control who can say
what because if you're part of one of
their favorite groups you can do and say
whatever you want no matter how
segregated it is as long as you're
aligned with their agenda and if they
manage to complete their implementation
of State for conditioning you know what
happens next well the ones who decide to
follow their own version of Truth and
try to become free individuals will face
the exact same fate that Socrates did
they find excuses to come after
you you see Socrates didn't steal he
didn't kill anyone all he did was make
people aware of the truth and just how
ignorant and indoctrinated they were by
the system and what happened he got
executed because of that for corrupting
the youth use and that was not during a
dictatorship by the way that was
literally in the birthplace of democracy
the reigning government system in the
entire West and if you think that that
only happened back in the days just
think back to any dictatorship ever you
don't agree with their truth what
happens they come after you it's that
simple and you know that today already
there's a lot of things that you can't
say right now that were considered
trivial just a few years ago it's
getting harder and harder to succeed and
be free by the minute and if you don't
do anything about it that will become
your reality period now it's also during
these periods of monumental change that
the biggest opportunities arise and the
last time an event of this magnitude
happened was in ancient Greece before
Jesus was even born that's how long ago
it was and today we know the exact
principles that have been lost for
millenniums that ultimately led to the
creation of some of the most successful
men the world has ever seen you know
back then people who used to be mere
peasants went on to conquer entire
continents from edge to edge under their
mentors and became generals rulers and
even Kings along the way it was one of
the greatest social shifts in history
and history repeats itself and we could
be about to experience the same with a
great rescue but the time is ticking
I've given you the five lost principles
to become an outsider and when you
implement all five of these principles
you too will become an outsider and
you'll get to enjoy all of the spoil
that come with living a life of complete
freedom and I'm not referring
specifically to money here after all
majority of you watching didn't get
started in this journey because of the
money but rather because of the
experiences that being free can provide
you with now for some of you that might
be the ability to drop out of college
for some of you it might be the ability
to finally quit your job to stop working
on someone else's dream and start
working on your own or it might be the
ability to start working on something
that actually fulfills you that allows
you to to take care of the ones around
you and do whatever you want whenever
you want without having to get the
approval of someone else basically what
it means to become an outsider is that
you'll finally get to break free of all
of the social conditioning you've been
fed and take back ownership of your life
to live it on your own terms by your own
rules that's what an outsider does and
now you have two options you either
decide to go back to what you were doing
before and just pretend that you're not
aware that doing that will never lead
you to any suc success and that
everything you just learned during this
event it just never happened or you
decide to become an outsider yourself
and at this point you should have
already established what your truth is
so you are the only one that can tell
what is the right decision based on what
the truth is for you if you don't want
to become an outsider that is totally
fine listen that might not be the truth
you want to guide your path and if
that's the case I genuinely wish the
best of luck for you but I can't really
help you any further
now if you decide to become an outsider
you're going to need number one to
unwire your limiting beliefs to have a
mentor to have a curriculum to seek
intense hardship to forge discipline and
self-control and the truth is you're
probably not going to be able to do it
yourself whether you like it or not I
wasn't Plato wasn't Aristotle wasn't
Alexander the Great wasn't and I'm not
saying you have to necessarily learn
from me by the way you can go ahead and
find different people out there that
teach you each one of these skills
individually that is definitely an
option what is not an option is trying
to learn everything yourself now if you
do want to learn from me I'm going to
provide you with the five loss
principles today starting with the same
curriculum that I personally used to go
from zero to a multi-millionaire in my
early 20s now as I mentioned a few times
during this video I have an education
platform called educate now inside of
our platform we have taught around
30,000 people to this day on how to
start a high income Online Career from
zero and work your way up to to $10,000
a month this provides you with the
financial location and time Freedom
needed to live a life of freedom and one
thing is a fact there are hundreds of
skills you can learn in order to make
money online but some skills have a way
higher demand than others and of course
if you choose one of those your odds of
success Skyrocket so here are the three
best high income skills for beginners to
make $110,000 a month the first one is
agency the agency curriculum presented
inside of our program agency Navigator
now agency Navigator is the curriculum
you need in order to start a location
independent online business from scratch
and scale it to a full-time income in
the shortest time frame possible even if
you have no previous experience and this
is the curriculum I've used myself to
make my first $110,000 month my first
$100,000 and even my first million at
the age of 18 it simply works and I'm
Not only living proof of it but so are
our students our average student takes
around 67 days to sign their first
paying Clan and the average Clan
retainer of our students is $2,000 a
month and the real beauty is that after
they sign that first one they really get
that confidence under their belt it
takes them around half that time to sign
their second client and at this point
they're already making a full-time
income now I want you to take the
example from Jackson to understand the
power of this business model he signed
his first client for $2,000 a month 3
months ago he has now gotten paid a
total of $6,000 from this one client
alone and he will still continue to get
paid by this very same clan for months
and potentially years to come I mean
just think about how much this one clan
can generate him in its entire lifetime
dozens and dozens of thousands of
dollars all of this money because he
sold this client once and I personally
selected this model because my personal
strength lies in managing people and
with this business model all you have to
do is connect businesses that have a
problem with a contractor who can fix
that problem for them so I basically
just find the right people who get all
of the work done for me which by the way
is usually the boring part and allow me
to focus only on the activities that
grow my business and make me more money
now for years that's the only thing that
I taught students how to start an agency
and I've gotten literally thousands of
students to quit their jobs and even
created a few dozen millionaires there
is literally no program in the industry
with more success stories than the
agency Navigator now along the way I
noticed that starting a business it's
not the only way of succeeding you know
the truth is majority of six and seven
figure earners are not actually business
owners instead they work for the right
businesses and one of the fastest ways
to get to $10,000 a month online without
having to start a business and deal with
all of the headaches that come with it
such as product development Service
delivery managing employees and payroll
marketing Etc is to Simply become a
sales rep to a business that already
makes a lot of money you simply get to
sell their product which is already
proven and sells a lot and the more you
sell the more money you make here's the
thing majority of the people think they
need to become the new Iman gaji to
achieve the freedom they want and that
couldn't be further from the truth I
have hundreds of people who work for me
who achieve their own financial location
and time freedom and you've probably
seen them hanging out with me in some of
my videos all you need to do is become
someone that wealthy people like me
would hire and I personally employ more
than 50 sales reps throughout all of my
portfolio companies between my personal
software companies my e-learning
business as well as the other companies
that have Equity stakes in and it's
crazy we have 19-year-olds making killer
income traveling the world while they do
so you know some months they're in Cape
Town some months they're in Italy some
months they're in LA and as long as they
show up and they perform I could not
care if they take their calls from
Antarctica they have their location
Freedom as long as they stay focused and
that's why this is one of the easiest
paths to succeed becoming an online
sales rep and that is the exact
curriculum that we teach inside of sixf
figure sales rep finally the last
curriculum I'll I'll give you access to
inside of educate is Penta profit now if
you don't want to be talking to people
all day long and instead you prefer to
just work on your computer this is the
one for you inside of Penta profit you
learn how to write messages that make
people take action that is basically
writing emails ads website Pages or any
other form of online medium that has
text on it this is one of the most in
demand skills today and businesses pay
hundreds of thousands of dollars to
those who have such skill set why
because one one single video one single
ad one single email can generate that
business millions and millions of
dollars because the amount of people
that you can reach with a video or an ad
today is literally in the hundreds of
millions and the best part about it is
that in today's day and age you don't
actually even have to be good at writing
to succeed with this curriculum now I
know that's quite a few options to
choose from and deciding what's the best
for you can be overwhelming but you
don't need to worry about it the first
thing we'll do once you join educate is
to help you choose what is the best
skill for you your specific personality
type so this way you know exactly which
one you should choose to have the
highest chances at success now one of
the most important principles of an
outsider as we covered in depth during
the rescue is to have a mentor and at
this point you already understand if you
want to succeed and truly become an
outsider who gets to enjoy financial
location and time Freedom there is
nothing more important to get you there
than having a mentor Aristotle had a
mentor Plato had a mentor Alexander the
Great had a mentor and if they all
needed mentors saying that you're
special and you don't need anyone is
simply lying to yourself and then we go
back to the mentorship Paradox you see
for a mentor to be a good Mentor they
have to be successful which means
they're going to be more expensive than
you can afford so what do you
do well that was the exact problem I
fixed with educate what you get inside
of educate is essentially more than 20
plus mentors at a huge discount we
created what we call an educator and
inside of educate you'll get access to
our multiple curriculums each one taught
by a different educator agency Navigator
is taught by me six figure sales rep is
taught by my CEO Paul Dy and Pen to
profit is taught by my CMO Luis Berger
now what most people don't know is that
you also get direct access to Paul and
Lis as your Educators that is your
mentors and that's because every week
they host mentorship calls for the
education students where you can ask
them any questions and get their direct
feedback live tailored specifically to
your own situation and challenges that
is true mentorship and they're not the
only Educators you get access to by the
way inside of educate we have a lineup
of over 10 plus industry-leading
professionals who host weekly mentorship
calls where you get to jump on a zoom
meeting and ask them any questions you
have we have calls on sales copywriting
agency operations client Outreach
mindset accountability and more more
that is literally having an expert in
the field answering your questions live
every single week and if you were to pay
to get access to any one of those
individuals you would be spending tens
of thousands of dollars weekly I mean we
literally just got back from the educate
Mastermind where over 40 people paid
$25,000 each to get access to the advice
of these exact same people for 3 days so
what educate gives you is access to
industry-leading mentors at a huge
discount I mean it's like buying a
Ferrari for $10,000 and we still have
another level of Educators by the way we
also have our one toone Educators that
Mentor every single educate student so
when you first join educate they're
going to jump on a call with you and
help you decide what is the best
curriculum for you to follow based on
your specific needs and strengths so
this way you know that you are pursuing
the right path without having to try to
figure out everything out on your own
then after they help you decide what's
the best path for you they will draw a
customized action plan to your specific
situation on the step- by- step that you
need to follow in order to achieve
success and become a free person with
whatever curriculum that you choose
these mentors understand the market
better than anyone else and that's
because every single day they talk to
dozens of students they get to see
what's working and what isn't right now
and I was chatting with our lead
educator the other day he told me that
every single student that had worked
with him for 6 months was making money
as in every single student that showed
up to the calls the calls by the way
that are included they're free it's not
like every time you jump on the call
with your onetoone educator and your
onetoone Mentor you need to pay extra
money so just simply the people who
bothered to show up to the calls made
money and that's why every single
successful person out there says that
having mentors is the shortcut to
success if you just follow what they
tell you you get results period now it
is true the most difficult part of this
entire journey is just getting rid of
all of your limiting beliefs in the
first place and throughout the years I
have seen it over and over people who
had so much potential but never achieved
any Real Results due to the limiting
beliefs that stop them so I decided to
do something I've created a new program
that sole purpose is to help you un your
life before you even think about
becoming successful because at the end
of the day you won't ever be successful
if you don't address the road blocking
obstacles that stop you from getting
there in the first place now this is the
first program that I've recorded in 2
years and you're going to get exclusive
access to it with your educate
subscription it's called digital
Launchpad and with it you'll finally be
able to get rid of the Decades of social
conditioning you've been fed by the
conditioning Factory and eliminate your
limiting beliefs for life now the last
principle you need here is self-control
and self-discipline and I've already
told you the best way to achieve that by
immersing yourself in an intense period
of work now throughout the years I've
noticed that the people who take this
plan and immerse themselves completely
into doing it for a whole month every
single day while their odds of
succeeding are exponentially higher than
the ones who try to do it over long
periods of time without ever going all
in and that's really because you learn
so much faster when you immerse yourself
completely in a subject without giving
any room for distractions and not only
that but the amount of results you
produce in one month when you go all in
is greater than you'd produce in 6
months just half assing it I mean just
think about it Navy Seals are considered
to be the best Special Forces Unit there
is and they are only the best because
their training is the most intense there
is they are forged through intensity and
just like most precious stones are
created under the most intense
conditions extreme temperature extreme
pressure intensity forges longlasting
success and what we figured out is that
if a student gets into educate and they
don't go through the first phase of the
curriculum within AEK week then their
odds of succeeding drops by 10x and
that's because they already lost track
of the intensity they didn't go all in
listen it's the exact same thing with
going to the gym let's say you pay for a
gym subscription but you don't show up
on the first week what are the odds of
you showing up in the weeks after that
it is way lower than it was of you
showing up in the first week so pretty
much just by not showing up in the first
week you already walked 80% of your way
to failure on the other hand what if you
showed up every every single day of the
first 6 weeks that you joined the gym
first of all you'd already start seeing
your first small wins in progress during
that period which would get you even
more committed to showing up then
knowing that you already showed up every
day of the first 6 weeks and already
started seeing your first signs of
progress How likely would you be able to
keep showing up in the coming weeks very
likely I mean pretty much 100% odds and
almost 2 years ago I created a secret
program for our students that aimed at
doing exactly that that providing them
with an intense start that would
FasTrack their way to success and still
to this day this has been the program
that has generated the best and fastest
student results that we've ever gotten
it consisted of six live master classes
with our best Educators during the
course of 6 weeks each week would cover
one step of our curriculum and give
students the exact action plan they
needed to execute on during that week
and at the end of the 6 weeks they would
be ready to start making their first
commissions online in fact quite a few
students started signing clients and
making money even before the end of the
6 weeks and for the first time ever I've
decided to relaunch this program inside
of educate so when you get an educate
subscription today you'll also get
enrolled into the educate FastTrack and
over the course of 6 weeks Together live
on Zoom with me and the best Educators
we have inside of educate we will get
you from wherever you are right now to a
position where you're you're ready to
start making money online we're going to
show you how to choose the right
curriculum for you we're going to give
you the exact action plan that you need
to take action and we'll show you
exactly how to approach potential
clients and what to say to get them to
work with you or to get a job with them
and we'll show you exactly how to
deliver them with the best results so
that way you never feel like you don't
know what you're doing all live during
six weekly live master classes this is
the intensity you need to hack your way
to success this is educ FasTrack the
first class starts on Thursday already
so you don't want to miss it these are
the five principles you need to become
an outsider and Achieve Financial
location and time freedom and with these
exact same principles we've had kids
straight out of high school as well as
people who could barely speak English
successfully starting their online
businesses and achieving their Financial
Freedom while also enjoying location and
time freedom in short becoming an
outsider themselves and if you had this
exact same curriculum and mentors at
your disposal do you think that it would
be out of this world for you to achieve
the same now this is the question that
only you can answer now look every
single day we have dozens of students
joining educate for
$1,500 but today when I open the cart
for this offer you'll get access to all
of our curriculums agency Navigator sixf
fig sales rep Penta profit and the new
digital Launchpad as well as the 20
weekly mentorship sessions with our
educator
as well as your personal one-on-one
educator and most importantly the
educate FastTrack basically everything
that we just discussed the total price
for this new package would be in the
tens of thousands of dollars if you were
to buy each one of these things
separately especially because of all of
the mentorship hours you get on a weekly
basis and it's not one of those fake
inflated prices that no one's actually
paid for again we've had tens of
thousands of students join just agency
navigator for $1,500 as well as more
recently people paying upwards of
$25,000 for a 3-day event with the exact
same Educators and to be honest if you
were to pay $10,000 for this package it
would be a steal knowing that our
average student gets their first paying
Clan within 67 days and they usually
range at $2,000 a month retainer however
you're not going to be paying the total
price of $10,000 for this package in
fact you're not even going to be paying
the full price of $1,500 just for agency
Navigator alone is because we make a
commitment to you when you join educate
you have a one-on-one educator assigned
to you you have a profile you're a part
of the ecosystem we are making a
commitment to you we continue to deliver
incredible programs and when you're
subscribed to educate you have access to
any new programs coming out and we have
new programs every 4 to 6 months but for
the first year only we want people who
are serious and dedicated because we are
serious and dedicated to your success
and by the way that's also to cover the
cost of hundreds of thousands of dollars
that we spend every single month on the
world leading mentors that we have doing
the coaching as well as your one-on-one
Educators that get assigned to your
personal profile I personally spend
hundreds of thousands of dollars in
payroll to get them inside of educate
now this offer is only going to be
available until next Monday after that
educate will go back to its regular
price of $1,500 in the first year and
you won't have the chance to access the
extra bonus such as the FastTrack ever
again we are opening enrollments in the
exact moment that this video is
premiering so if you want to be one of
the few people who are going to get
premium support from our coaches make
sure that you claim your educate
subscription now you can find the link
to enroll in the description below if
you're watching after the premiere and
if you're watching the premiere live
right now I'm going to personally drop
the link in the live chat in 3 2 1 now
it's going to take you to a page with
all of the information you need to know
about the educate package for the rescue
and if you have any questions at all we
have chat support on the page ready to
talk to you and solve any issues the
fact is time is is ticking and the
window of opportunity to escape stage 4
conditioning is shrinking by the minute
we have reached the point where most of
our freedoms are on the verge of being
restricted and the longer we stay in
this situation the closer we get to
total control and when that happens none
of what we just discussed will be useful
anymore so either you free yourself now
or you regret your decisions later this
is your last chance of escaping the
conditioning Factory and becoming an
outsider so I suggest you act now
because tomorrow might be too late and
let's be real Black Friday is in two
weeks and you can either spend your
hard-earned money buying useless sh that
will only consume even more of your
already scarce time or you can use the
same money to invest into something
which is actually going to take you
somewhere and by the way you literally
have no Financial Risk of joining
educate today and that's because we
trust our program so much that we
decided to implement a 100% money back
guarantee so if for whatever reason you
don't like the program all you have to
do is email support asking for a refund
and we'll process that within 48 Hours
of your request and now the decision is
yours to make are you ready to rescue
these principles together and after over
2,000 years bring back the roots of
Education to life you are the only one
who can decide but just remember the
clock is ticking and I am waiting for
you inside of
educate