[Music]
the truth is you've been brainwashed and
this is how we got
here the system was built with the
interest of its creators in mind rather
than the interest of the students that
go through the systems themselves that's
what they were doing turning you into a
product of the system someone who gets
treated like a product that at the end
of day can be easily replaced they will
never do more than what it was
manufactured to do and that has an
expiry date and with that I don't want a
nation of thinkers I want a nation of
workers after all it was a cause for the
less favored people all in the name of
diversity and education and it worked
exactly as planned but what I found was
a much bigger story here it's not being
told a very carefully crafted plan a
plan that connected all of these
problems together a plan that has been
kept secret for a long time dating back
to over 250 years ago a plan that if
people were aware of their existence
would rock the foundations of the
current system and expose the side of
the system that is hidden in the shadows
a plan that is crafted by three
notorious individuals over the course of
three centuries and broken down into
four stages of social conditioning
the goal maximize the reach of the
system I mean kids would come in as
bright creative enthusiastic children
and come out as obedient mindless and
not capable of thinking for themselves
and I'm not sure if you've noticed this
but they purposely made the schools look
like prisons that's why they put the
children sitting in rows that's why they
had alarm Bells that's why they had
strict timings for classes and intervals
in a few short years this absolutely
transformed the amount of schools in the
United States of America and after that
every new generation will go to school
ready to learn and become critical
thinkers only to come out of school as
an obedient factory worker with no big
aspirations the system started to spread
itself throughout the US in record time
now listen if you're not from the US
you're probably thinking right now well
I'm not from the US so that doesn't
really affect me what does it have to do
with me well I'm sorry to tell you but
it was already growing into
today for every dollar the government
loan through student loans tuition goes
up by 60 on the other hand Harvard has
enough money to pay the tuition of every
single one of their students for the
next 120 years in a row this is
unsustainable and eventually this system
will collapse the system was built with
the interest of its creators in mind
rather than the interest of the students
that go through the systems themselves
and the ones above you they don't want
you to know about the truth they want
you to be a product of the system
someone who does what they're told and
nothing more and this is really how they
create an illusion of choice for you oh
you can choose this course or this
University or this degree this is how
they trick you on the other hand if we
manage to take back control over the
truth and get it to as many people as
possible we will experience the great
rescue where the principles that once
created the greatest Minds that have
ever stepped in this world will be
brought back to life and with it we'll
get back to the origins of
Education even though you've put in a
lot of effort into everything you've
been told that would make you successful
going to school getting good grades
getting a good degree working a safe job
it was all a setup from the
Geto it was never meant for you to
succeed in the way you want to but
rather for you to experience success in
their
terms and that's why over the last 12
months we've seen Mass layoffs from Big
corporations like Google meta Uber Etc
the bubble is not about to burst it
already started
bursting the problem is somewhere along
the journey there was a shift in powers
and the ones who got to power they
stopped caring about the interest of
their people and here's the thing the
ideals and principles that education was
originally built upon they were the
ideals that created some of the most
brilliant individuals and brightest
Minds the world has ever seen
they were fighting the same war and
followed the book on how to win it so
must
[Music]
[Applause]
we
and it all depends on
[Music]
us