Play [ __ ] twin [ __ ] happening
[Music]
got two twins they top tier that's my
favorite fetish
[Music]
what are we doing we're getting some
cigars where are we going we're going to
Bali
Iman said happy birthday my boy love you
lots feel blessed love you bro I'm
excited I'm excited happy birthday we
forgot to mention what we're going to
body with you we're the boys
happy birthday what
are you doing right
nice
[Laughter]
oh my God hey
okay
imagine all of this to miss the flight
now
[Laughter]
serious
[Music]
no more dares
man not much we're here we're here
living arriving flight scenery the
itinerary
a little bit fresh air bro we don't get
this in Dubai I will say the air quality
in Bali is not the best
here we have uh six rooms in here yeah
no I'm sure if we're not drinking
boss man
huh well you take the one of them the
biggest one
special birthday treatment
geez I got the view huh
this is
nice mad
Depot
this is crazy crazy all right bro
birthday cigar cheese thank you brother
and I owe you one final gift oh for your
birthday when I was in Maldives last
month I saw this and I thought nah this
is a little slice of Alex geez
board
the compilation
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
then we got dinner at eight and we got
Beach Club again at 9 30 and then we've
uh Club at 12.
Amara's keeping us busy
[Music]
it's not my kind of music so I'm I'm
meditating
[Music]
each company just order a [ __ ]
Maybach
[Music]
before I tell you what we're doing I
want to address something on one of my
latest videos I had a lot of people
roasting me for my tennis ability
[Music]
and I just want to say something growing
up in the UK two thick tennis tennis and
skiing those are rich people things so I
only started playing tennis a couple
years ago so I will admit I am horrific
at tennis but you guys want a day in the
life all right so yeah you know I'm not
gonna sit here and only do things I'm
good at for the Vlog I'm sure the tennis
I know I'm sure a tennis so yeah now
that we've gone that out the way what
are we doing we're going car shopping
again again
yes
and except this car isn't actually for
me this car is a gift I'm sure you guys
have seen a giveaway quite a lot of
gifts
um and especially to the people that
have been there for me for a long time
and have been there with me from the
jump so this person I'm getting a gift
for has been basically a part of my
journey has helped kind of support me
through the highs and the lows over yeah
ever since I basically started my
business so as a little token of
appreciation I'm buying them a car thank
you
that's what you Dubai first bro yeah
that's for sure all right see I'm
looking to spend around a million
Dirhams that's like 270 000 so right now
the options are Porsche 911 Turbo S
Bentley Continental GT G63 but honestly
there is common as a taxi here
or a Ferrari Roma
911 Turbo S is the best car out of those
but it's a driver's car and driving into
like getting from place to place and
driving to enjoy yourself and in Dubai
you're basically just stuck on a highway
most of the time obviously the Roma is
also a driver's that Porsche is nice
obviously the Roma is also a driver's
car but at least you're in a driver's
car that you have that thrill of being
in a Ferrari whereas yeah I don't know I
just I don't know I just think on the
highways in Dubai you're just not going
to get that same thing in a Porsche so
uh which one which one because I have
one test plate so I need to put it on
one okay okay all right well then they
can start they can start with aroma
aroma okay they're on the face of my
city co-signed by Diddy hard liquor I'm
shitty
[Music]
wasn't always this pretty
what's your opinion bro I I see her in
this than a G wagon to be honest yeah
but at the end of the day it is her
decision
this is pretty nice should we just
connect our phones oh you need to see
this [ __ ] thing is this the charger
no bro you need to see the music system
on this yeah it's crazy
[Music]
100 meters I just put nine gallon a
sprinter making a habit out of this I'm
not even buying the car for me but yeah
buying cars for sure was that four how
long has it been we're in four months
when do we buy the range in March March
April May
four months four and four months so one
a month one a month what are we getting
next month
okay let's just I can't see on camera
what are we getting today
[Music]
like I got a cup of this [ __ ] two times
so big news I bought a Supercar now this
Supercar actually isn't for me it's a
present it's a gift there are quite a
few people from back in 2016 2017 sort
of early stages of my career that were
really there for me when I was just
starting out and throughout the years
I've done various different things to
show my appreciation help them in any
way that I can most of it is very
private I don't really tell anyone or
talk about anything but Alex said that
you know what maybe it'd be
inspirational for you to get to a point
where not only can you buy a Supercar
for yourself more importantly you can
buy a Supercar for your loved ones and
the people who are really theirs through
thick and thin so after I show you the
car I think I will explain why I ended
up picking this specific car as the gift
so I ended up buying a Ferrari all right
I bought a brand new 2023 Ferrari Roma
uh I guess this is the first thing to
mention is that you can quite easily fit
like a weekend bag even two weekend bags
in the trunk of this so it's actually
quite a practical car to have day in day
out oh man it's so hot like this is
genuinely a very good day-to-day car
which you genuinely can't say about a
lot of Ferraris except for their new SUV
except I think they call it fuv the
Paris anyway I got the car in red and
then just got wrapped with Sam black I
think listen it's a understated Ferrari
and it's just one of the few practical
Ferraris that you can have as I said
you've seen the boot space the fact that
you even get that boot space in a car
like this is very impressive it's a V8
as well as a eight-speed gearbox it does
Drive beautifully I will say is that in
Dubai you don't really get a chance to
get a feel for this car this car is
actually going to be sent off next May
for the mod ball rally and this car will
be touring Europe and I feel for a rally
in Europe this will be an amazing car to
drive apart from that let's hop inside
all right so one thing you'll notice
about this car is the interior in my
opinion is beautiful I love this split
cabin design in terms of being on the
passenger side I don't know what this
display is called so it's cool if your
passenger here you can check the
performance of the car the Rev count
what gear you're in stuff like that you
can change the song settings etc etc I
know some people hate this interior some
people love it couple things I don't
like about this infotainment is very
clunky but then again it's also Ferrari
so like what do you expect I will show
them something cool if you're going
somewhere you can either have it the
fastest way the shortest way in terms of
distance or it can show you the most fun
way one day I was driving this car and I
set it to the most fun route and in
Dubai was no fun at all so I feel like
this works if you're in the countryside
in England if you're in Italy if you're
most places in the world but in Dubai as
I said fun route it's really not too
many of those so best thing to do is
just put it at the fastest route so
another interesting thing if you push
from Auto let's say you go to manual and
you want to use the paddle shifters it
does this little sort of like see this
red light up thing I thought that was
cool
now when you're inside the car it
doesn't sound that great obviously bear
in mind we're not driving at the moment
one thing I really don't like about this
car is the engine stop start it's like
this little touch pad which for me
personally I just think is um
I would prefer something a little bit
more tactile but speaking about tactile
to go from different modes so you've got
wet Comfort sport I don't know what
technical term is for this but it's got
this sort of metallic switch it is
similar to a lot of other Ferraris but
as I said it's just very satisfying
where I am there's a lot of speed bumps
and at the moment I'm specking my 812
GTS with that car for example you would
have to be very careful over the speed
bumps you'd have to put in Comfort mode
and then you have to raise the
suspension whereas this can comfort you
pretty much good then you got sport mode
and then you got race mode when you put
on race mode the back end is very
unpredictable so especially here in
Dubai Comfort or sport you're pretty
much good
[Music]
all right
the reason I got this car at first I was
looking at a wagon now wagons in Dubai
around a million derms like 270 thousand
dollars putting a brand new from
Mercedes is 1.06 so almost a 300 000 or
a car I've had people tell me because I
was mentioning the Range Rover SV price
the Phantom price stuff like that and
people are like no that car isn't that
much guys all you need to do is look up
the price in Dubai in Dubai have no cars
are substantially more expensive but
when I buy in London for example it is
substantially cheaper than buying here
now Aromas are around 1.1 1.2 million
depends on the spec that you get so
that's a 300 000 car so yeah we
basically whittled it down euruses hate
irises so that was out of the question
wagons they're just kind of a little too
common so I thought you know what let's
just get something a little bit more
special so that basically whittled it
down between the 911 Turbo S the
Continental GT and the Roma I feel like
the 911 Turbo S and the Roma kind of
fall into the same category of a
driver's car so then when looking at the
911 Turbo S and the Ferrari Roma they're
both still everyday cars but they've got
power to them and I'd say they're driver
cars they're not going to give you the
luxuries that a Continental GT will give
you the 911 Turbo S is around a million
Dirhams so maybe thirty thousand forty
thousand dollars cheaper than this car
but if you're spending that much money
and you're not really getting the best
out of the car in terms of Driving
Experience and what would you rather sit
in a Ferrari or a Porsche I mean it's
there's no question about it so for that
reason the 911 Turbo S then was out of
the equation and it was basically
between the Continental GT which as I
said I think that car has slept on I
personally love Bentley's I understand
they don't have that exciting factor
that a Ferrari does that a that a
Porsche does but I just think they're
great cars so yeah basically then we
whittled it down to a Continental GT in
a Ferrari Roma and long story short
ended up deciding on a Ferrari because
listen at the end of the day a Ferrari
is a Ferrari and I think when you get
gifted a Ferrari that's a special
feeling I think that was basically the
thought process when it came down to
deciding which car to buy it's funny to
see the comments as well whenever
anyone's like oh you know it's so weird
to see email driving I love driving I
just don't like driving in Dubai is
genuinely a very unpleasant experience
but for example in Cape Town I drive all
the time Europe I drive all the time so
yeah it's just always funny to see the
comments like oh it's so weird seeing
you man drive I think listen of course
you know when you're you have a dream
you have a vision to have a super car to
have a sports car whatever it may be
it's always like this dream of driving
this super aggressive powerful car I
think if you work hard if you dedicate
if you think in terms of years even
decades and not months you will get this
and I'm gonna be very honest with you
for a lot of you depends on what city
you live once you get this you'll
realize it's not what it's made out to
be listen of course it's fun to do this
sometimes
yeah sure it's fun to floor it every
once in a while but if you live in
London if you live in New York if you
live in Dubai you know what I mean if
you live in Paris you don't get to do
this often you don't get to just put it
down and send it
so for all of you I know that you will
get something like this in your life I
know you'll accomplish this I always
like to give people the warning that
most of the things they want in life
once they get there they'll realize that
maybe it's not what it's made out this
evening and in certain cities
unfortunately it's uh something that can
cause you a lot of headache I mean
imagine having this car in London for
example even just parking like at least
Dubai you got valet and stuff like that
but even just parking is a headache so
go out there work hard forget the
concept of time and one day I know
you'll be able to buy this for yourself
and hopefully maybe you'll even be able
to buy this for your loved ones and
share all of the success and all the
blessings that you've been able to bring
into your life