there is so much BS out there when it
comes to how to actually be a
millionaire just think positive just
manifest you need 17 streams of income
that's how you do it just shut the f up
so in today's video I'm gonna reveal to
you what secret traits that you need to
have to become a millionaire and this is
the stuff that most influencers are too
scared to say because it just simply
goes against what Society what are weak
soft Society is telling us right now so
I guarantee if you stick around until
the end of the video you are gonna hear
things and you're gonna hear a fresh
perspective that you know maybe isn't
that nice maybe isn't all roses and
fairy tales but I can tell you for a
fact works and I can tell you for a fact
we'll get you to where you want to get
to in life now the first secret
millionaire trait and I have seen this
with every single millionaire that I
have ever met including myself and by
the way this is even more especially
true with a billionaire friends that I
have they possess this trait even more
and that is they think that they're
special and in fact to an extent they
even think that they're better than
other people now I know a lot of you
guys may take this the wrong way and you
may think oh that's terrible to think
that you know you're better than other
people now bear in mind you're not
disrespectful towards other people but
in certain domains you're better than
other people you think Michael Jordan
doesn't look at everyone around him and
goes yeah I'm better than you guys do
you think that industry leaders and
shakers don't look at themselves and go
yeah you know I've got something special
to me now when it gets dangerous and I'm
sure we all know these people are the
ones that think that they are special
but they won't put in the work the
reason you can think you are better than
other people is because you have simply
put in more hours more time and more
work so listen you should absolutely
believe you are special you should
absolutely believe that almost to an
extent you're better than most other
people who are so brain dead so asleep
are so scared to run towards the things
they want in life so there is apps
nothing wrong with having these feelings
as long as you back it up because if you
don't back it up then it is simply
delusional and I will be honest with you
there are lots of people as I said I'm
sure you know lots of people that are
extremely delusional they're like I'm
gonna be a billionaire
cool do you have a plan do you have any
sort of road map in fact let's put that
to the side have you even made ten
thousand dollars in your life have you
made a hundred thousand dollars in your
life so let's not talk about billionaire
status yet so as I said you never ever
want to be delusional in life we should
always have that feeling of being
special of being meant for more in life
you know I can tell you for a fact
growing up from the age of even six or
seven I just had that feeling that I was
destined for more that something great
was gonna come out of my life and that
was even from a young age and I remember
even you know in school at the age of 13
or 14 years old feeling a sense of like
yeah I was better than my peers even
though at that time I hate to use the
word bullying but I was being picked on
heavily I was a complete Outcast to
complete Outsider within the realm of
school I failed in every single Arena
you could think of and yet I still had
that feeling of like no no I'm working
towards something bigger I was trying
little side hustles and little
businesses and this and that so in life
humility is extremely important and you
should be able to assess your life
situation and look at your life
situation and not be like as I said
these idiots that are like oh I'm gonna
be a billionaire and they just sit on
their ass all day and don't do anything
about it you should feel special and
then you should put in a special amount
of work a special amount of dedication
to prove it to the world and that's
exactly what I did now the next secret
millionaire trait that you need to
possess is you need to develop a high
stress tolerance I tell people Time and
Time and Time Again they're more than
likely most people think they want my
life but they don't really want my life
because listen it's not easy to have 150
employees between multiple various
companies managing that with complex
different corporate structures and
trusts around the world and Investments
and Family Planning and taking care of
my mom and my friends and my loved ones
imagine that with all the social media
online bs and all the stuff that comes
with it but I've told people the reason
that I can deal with it is because I
have an extremely high stress tolerance
so I need you to understand don't
believe all of the self-help BS that
it's just going to be all roses and
fairy tales and if you feel stressed
today take a break you know give
yourself a break you deserve a break
you've done no work and you faced your
first challenge your first obstacle but
you know focus on your mental health
just you know don't push yourself too
much it's absolutely ridiculous the
world we live in as I said I like to
talk very transparently and openly to
people
it will be stressful
it will be painful you will suffer from
mental health issues and that comes with
a territory in the same way you cannot
expect to be a world-class bodybuilder
or be a bodybuilder that steps on stage
and you say I want to be a bodybuilder
and I want to step on stage but when I
go to the gym it can't hurt the second
that it hurts I'm gonna take a break
because I gotta focus on myself and like
you know I don't want to push myself too
much and it's all about like taking care
of yourself you know if you want to have
that mentality that is totally fine you
will never get to where you want to get
to in life and by the way there's
genuinely and I know I'm I talk very
intense sometimes there's genuinely
nothing wrong with that I think if you
want to be some billionaire CEO or you
just want to make 30 40 Grand a month
have some sort of online side hustle and
surf all day whatever you want to do
that is totally cool as long as it is a
hundred percent congruent and honest to
your Life Path and it's something that
you choose I've told people many times
when they ask me I go listen I am built
for this life because I have an insane
stress tolerance but my life is not the
same life that other people should live
but the reason you clicked on this video
is because you want to learn how to
become a millionaire and as I said if
you want to get to that position you
need to increase your ability to handle
stress now bear in mind one thing I will
say it's not something that needs to
happen overnight it's something that
progresses I can handle a certain level
of stress in 2023 that I simply couldn't
handle in 2018 or 2019 in fact some of
my biggest businesses with the most
amount of employees the reason that I
didn't pursue or start those businesses
or move forward with those businesses in
2018 or 2019 even though I was given the
opportunity to people wanted to start
the businesses with me give me Equity
blah blah all this is because I simply
knew that back then I did not have the
stress tolerance to be able to deal with
it so it's not an overnight thing it's
something that you build over time but
as I said don't come to the first
roadblock and think oh it's tough It's
not meant to be tough this is It's you
know it's all meant to be roses and
fairy tales I'm just trying to give you
very clear expectations I think when
someone can talk to you very openly and
honestly and say then listen it's not
all perfect I feel like at least you're
a little bit more prepared to go into
war so definitely I can say this about
myself and definitely I can say this
about some of the most successful people
I know in any realm in life by the way
any realm whether that's Sports whether
that's business whether that's even a
high income career working for a very
lucrative company you need to be able to
handle a high level of stress and
embrace it the third trait to become a
millionaire that simply isn't talked
about enough is your charisma and your
ability to persuade now of course
everyone knows this you know everyone
knows it but people don't Place enough
emphasis on it you need to learn how to
have Charisma and this is something that
you can train by the way bear in mind
most people don't assume this about me
I'm actually naturally an introvert I
like to be alone I like to chill but if
there's a time and a place where I need
to be I am extremely charismatic because
I understand that people like to listen
to people who carry themselves in a
survey who have a certain Aura and as I
said that doesn't mean talking the most
it just means learning Charisma and you
need to understand that if you don't
learn Charisma if you don't learn
persuasion you will be underpaid and
you'll be under booked so listen whether
you're trying to land a high income
career whether you're trying to sign
clients and get business and sign deals
as a business owner or you're trying to
be charismatic in order to inspire
people to work for you at your company
you need to learn this trait so real
quick guys before we get into the fourth
trait I get so many requests for Q A's
you guys want me to answer some of your
business questions answer questions that
are specific to you and your career and
your Life Path YouTube's normally the
place for me to do it and my personal
Instagram is just a joke to me it's just
where I post some photo dumps from
holidays I go on with my friends so
that's why very recently I started an
Instagram called talk with Eman and
that's where once a week and I try my
best to do it once a week don't kill me
if it's not every single week but I try
my best I answer your guys's questions
and try to give you some real-time
business advice so if you've ever had
any questions for me and you wanted me
to help you out go ahead pull out your
phone type in talk with Iman you can
follow me on there and stay tuned for
the next q a as I said I try to do it
once a week don't kill me if it doesn't
happen I try my best anyways moving on
to the fourth trait you want to focus on
Mastery not passion and it's another big
thing I've been telling people for years
you know it's funny I've started to look
at the self-help industry and realize
just how much bad it's doing for the
world like just how astray it's leading
people trying to tell people hey focus
on your passion let me tell you
something what you're passionate about
today you won't be passionate about in a
month and sometimes your biggest
passions in life when money is involved
in it it doesn't stay a passion anymore
so what you're passionate about today is
not what you're going to be passionate
about in 30 years but what you commit to
today you will still be a master at in
30 years and let me tell you something
when you are very good at something and
you know that you always enjoy it you
may not be over the moon passionate
elated about it all the time but you
always enjoy it and respect it and you
also want to continue doing it because
you understand how much blood Blood
Sweat and Tears went into it so in life
don't focus on your passions find
something you're interested in dedicate
yourself to it focus on being a master
at it now once you're a master at it or
once you're very good at it then you can
add some other skills on top of it and
that's really where you sort of Stack
your abilities and stack the portfolio
of things that you're very good at but
the main thing is just please stop it
with a passion the things that
you are passionate about should be your
hobbies that's your down time that's
your off time because those things can
always change but when it comes to your
work when it comes to your career focus
on something where you hate it for a
long time but it doesn't matter you stay
dedicated to it this is where I have so
much respect for the Japanese culture
because I see it time and time again in
Japan teenagers will come on as
apprentices and learn how to make knives
and they will do that for the next 60
years of their life and I can tell you
for a large portion of it they probably
hate it or they find it boring but it
doesn't matter they find something and
they stick to it they have honor for the
craft and I think that's that's really
what it's missing in a modern society is
everything just needs to feel good it
and feel positive no focus on Mastery
not passion the next secret millionaire
trait is you need to have an ego now
everyone says oh ego is bad this and
that and let me tell you something I've
said it for years I've said it time and
time again you need to have some sort of
faith I don't care what religion you
prescribe to I don't care what you
believe in unless it's atheist that's
just the one thing I have never gotten
behind and I don't think I could ever
get behind but pretty much everything
else as long as you know that there is
something bigger than yourself and that
humbles you and you let life humble you
and you put yourself through difficult
situations where life continuously
humbles you then your ego will stay in
check but that doesn't mean don't have
an ego at all ego is what pushes people
to Excellence I can tell you something
right now at my company is the reason
that I demand Excellence from my team
and me is partly ego I love the fact
that I know my team is the sharpest in
an industry I love the fact that when we
roll out a new feature on my software
company I'm like those guys didn't do it
or you know what those guys have been
around for six years and we came in in
the last two years and complete glue
them out the water and listen that comes
from ego think about the best people in
any Industries in the world they always
tell themselves hey whatever you can do
I can do better and that's not a bad
thing at all as long as they still
submit to higher power a religion a
belief whatever it is as long as they do
some sort of prayer meditation even just
gratitude journaling just something to
Humble themselves and as long as they
put themselves through very difficult
life situations that as I said will
humble them we'll put them in their
place I get humbled all the time yeah
sure I accomplished a fair amount at my
age and I understand a lot of people
look up to me but that's why I always
put myself in very difficult situations
where I know life is gonna humble me and
I'm gonna be put in my place as it
should be so as long as you do that
don't listen to this whole self-help
world have an ego it's a good thing the
sixth secret millionaire trait is that
they're always thinking what could go
wrong and once again as I said it's very
different to the whole self-help world
because they're always thinking positive
affirmation blah blah this that no no
one of the biggest reasons that I got to
where I am in life is because I do a lot
of visualization before bed but what
I've been visualize you know for example
growing up I never visualized buying a
Ferrari or Rolls-Royce or buying my mom
a four million dollar house in cash I
never visualized those things because I
knew that if I do the right actions
those things are going to come and those
things have come I've done all those
things instead I visualize the actions
but I focused on it being difficult what
I would do when things got difficult and
me getting past that so I'll give you an
example let's say you really struggle to
wake up in the morning you visualize
getting up when the alarm goes off in
the morning but it's difficult it's not
easy you prepare yourself for it to be
difficult you prepare yourself to wake
up and just be like wanting to hit the
snooze button and you have every reason
not to get out of bed and you fight with
your demons and you still get out of bed
you know why because when you wake up in
the morning you only have one chance per
day and you might fail so you're gonna
have to wait until the next day to do it
but in your mind which by the way can't
concede between reality and Imagination
that's why visualization especially
before bed is such a powerful tool in
your mind you can practice waking up 15
times in your imagination before you
wake up the next morning and you can
imagine it being difficult and you
trying to convince yourself to stay in
bed but still getting past it so that
for example is an exercise in always
thinking what could go wrong so that way
you can prepare for things so even to
this day I'm always thinking what could
go wrong I'm always looking at all of my
businesses or my structures or this that
and I'm always saying what could go
wrong I'm thinking hey maybe if this
partner in this business tries to
me over you know what do I do in that
situation and it's not negative thinking
it's just preparation it's always
preparing yourself and this is something
that so few people out there talk about
but I can tell you honest you want to
get into the big leagues these people
and I can definitely tell you that I do
it we're always thinking what could go
wrong we're always thinking seven steps
ahead and you know what in an ideal
world nothing goes wrong and that's
great but at least you've planned these
things too and not only that it gets
your mind thinking it gets your mind
thinking in a different perspective and
it forces you to become a problem solver
so if you want to become a millionaire
you always need to think what could go
wrong and start formulating solutions
for problems that may not even arise yet
the last secret millionaire trade is
that they understand achieving success
is relatively easy
staying there and continuing success is
extremely hard and as I said looking
around I always see people go oh I'm
gonna become successful blah blah this
app for me because I've been documenting
every step of the journey since I was 15
years old on YouTube I started my first
business when I was 14 but because I've
documented every step of the journey and
I've kind of outlined exactly what I was
going to do before I did it I guess it's
easy enough for me to say but I
genuinely believe if you stick to
something long enough you will become
successful so for me that was never
really what I focused on instead what I
focus on my mind was really consumed by
was how do we stay there because as I
said if you manage to make a million
dollars I mean that's cool
congratulations but I mean it's really
not that special if you manage to do it
over and over and over and have
continued success in an industry or
maybe pivot to another industry and
flourish in that industry that is really
what the Legends are made of so don't
think that oh I'm gonna build up my
business or build up my career and make
a lot of money and then that's it I
can't tell you how many people I've seen
get to that position and then they kick
up their feet they get comfortable and
by the way I know video I've talked
about hey it's good to have an ego and
you need to think that you're special in
the sense those things aren't bad things
let me tell you what's truly egotistical
getting to a position in life and
thinking that okay I'm good now that is
truly egotistical you need to understand
that once you get to where you want to
get to in life you've just started now
you got to stay there and that is the
real difficulty so ladies and gentlemen
I genuinely think you may want to watch
this video again save it to your watch
later and come back to this video in a
month come back to in six months come
back to in a year because probably the
more successful you get you'll start to
realize how true these traits are that I
gave you these seven traits that I just
gave you and you also start to realize
how different it is from all the other
self-help BS that's out there so ladies
and gentlemen I hope that was helpful to
you I say all of this genuinely with
love as I said I know I'm very intense
sometimes but that's just because
I had to figure out all the on my
own I had no one to teach me this and
apart from that as always I'm watching
from afar and I'm genuinely from all my
heart rooted