I have read hundreds of books on
everything from investing to corporate
structure to the psychology of
persuasion and here's the truth 95 of
what they tell you is completely useless
when it comes to actually getting rich
so let me go ahead and save you the
thousands of hours I have spent reading
that never actually benefited me when it
comes to making money now listen do not
get me wrong the books I read were
wonderful in their own right they were
fascinating but they didn't help me get
rich and honestly you have no time to
waste so these are the 17 books that
will actually make you rich the first
thing that you really need to understand
is that the type of books you're gonna
read to go from zero to ten thousand
dollars a month will be very different
to those that you're going to read in
order to hit a hundred thousand dollar
months or even make a million dollars a
month so therefore I actually divided
these 17 books into three categories
going from zero to ten thousand dollars
a month ten thousand to a hundred
thousand dollars a month and a hundred
thousand dollars to a million dollars a
month then I actually threw in a bonus
category which is the books that will
help you grow from a million dollars a
month to ten million dollars a month and
Beyond and honestly I would say that
that is probably the most interesting
one and that's because at that level
macro economics actually become the most
important thing that's really when you
start to study how the world actually
works you get into books like the house
of Morgan which explains the truth
behind the banking system but we're
gonna get to that a little later in the
video now the first book on this list
almost sets the foundation for
everything to come and by the way it's
also the only fictional work on this
list and I'm talking about The Alchemist
now this book tackles the very
prerequisite of making money and getting
rich and that's having the guts to
actually follow your purpose because
make no stake about it is far easier to
never take that leap of faith or to
never start that business so before you
can even think about making money you
need to have a very honest conversation
with yourself and you need to decide if
you're willing to take that bet on
yourself and decide if you are willing
to overcome the obstacles that come with
following your purpose because when
you're starting from zero and you want
to get to ten thousand dollars per month
that is probably the hardest income
threshold to reach and the reason behind
that is because everything is working
against you you see when you're first
starting out you actually need to rewire
your entire brain you don't need to
Simply make money but you need to become
the person that's worthy of making money
so when I say that everything is working
against you what I mean by that is that
the person you once were is at odds with
the person that you're becoming and just
like Newton's first law of motion you're
fighting inertia and in some sense zero
to ten thousand dollars a month boils
down to one thing mindset you need to
adopt that mindset that success is not
just a desire
it's a necessity and that is exactly the
lesson of the next book on the list
Think and Grow Rich by Napoleon Hill and
much like the title of the book suggests
it boils down to the idea that if you're
able to conceive it and leave it well
then
you can achieve it and I'd say that's
really the first step towards becoming
rich actually believing that you can and
realizing that it's the only path
forward you see the book also talks
about another Pitfall I see far too
often in people just getting started you
see often when you're getting started
you'll get stuck waiting waiting for the
perfect moment waiting for the perfect
business model just waiting for
everything in order to not get started
and the truth is as obvious as it seems
is that there's no perfect time there
never was and there never will be in the
beginning of any Journey let alone the
Journey of getting rich is going to be
messy and my friend that's simply the
name of the game and honestly being able
to navigate through that mess is what
will make you successful and here's
where we get to the next book Atomic
habits you see the next book Atomic
Habits by James Clear teaches you how to
do exactly that you see we already
established that you need to become a
person worthy of success so how do you
do that well you are the sum of all of
your actions so to change yourself you
need to change your actions and
obviously you can't just reinvent
yourself overnight so you need to do it
in incremental steps by implementing new
habits killing old ones and keeping the
worthy ones and that's exactly what
Atomic habits teaches you to do I
remember when I read it for the first
time it completely changed how I
approached my work and allowed me to
stack all of my good habits day by day I
kept solidifying my habits until they
eventually became second nature now real
quick before I get to the next book I
know a lot of you guys are watching this
and going this is amazing but none of
these books are going to show me what
online business do I start this year
that will actually get me Rich because
as I said these are 17 of my favorite
books out of hundreds that I've read but
these books aren't going to tell you hey
this year this model is working this
model is not working maybe you should
try this based on your personal
personality type so that's why I'm going
to leave the link to my most popular
YouTube video down below this video has
helped millions of people decide what
business model is the right one for them
and which ones they should start today
because it is working the best so once
you finish that video I will leave a
link in the description go ahead check
out that YouTube video pick the right
business model for you and let's get
back to the video now once you've built
a solid base of habits and perhaps
you've already chosen your business
model and you're starting to make some
cash you need to start setting
expectations and what I mean by this is
you need to really begin to understand
how to think about money and that is
exactly what you're going to learn in
money Master the game by Tony Robbins
you know it's funny I distinctly
remember being 17 years old reading this
book and doing one of the exercises
where you have to design your life in
three ways in the first scenario you're
just scraping by and you write down how
much money you need in order to make
that happen from your passive
investments in the second scenario
you're living comfortable but not
extravagantly and once again you need to
calculate how much of a nest egg you
need in order for that to happen and in
the final scenario you calculate how
much money you need to go all out and
what you'll come to realize is that if
you're being honest with yourself
success is a lot closer than you may
think and it's funny I even went through
this exercise as a 17 year old and I'm
sure we all think we're like oh I need
to make a 10 million dollars a year to
live my dream lifestyle and I looked at
it and after I had written everything
down my dream lifestyle was like seventy
thousand dollars a month and the funny
thing is the next year when I was 18
years old I was making that amount of
money every single month so I guess it's
just crazy how writing things down
physically works and it's funny I still
have those journals in my house to this
day but anyways back to my point I think
for me it was very powerful because in
my mind as I said I thought like from my
dream lifestyle I have to make millions
and millions of dollars a year and
listen seventy thousand dollars a month
I understand it's still a good chunk of
of money it was still substantially less
than what I thought I did so when I
wrote everything down I was like oh wow
for me to live my dream lifestyle it's a
lot closer than I thought now listen of
course your expectations will always
change and as you become more successful
you might want more from life but it's
just a very powerful exercise to get you
to quantify what success actually looks
like financially because how can you
start working towards success if you
don't even know what it means when it
comes to cents or dollars so once you've
set your expectations you need to start
executing and executing by the way means
how do I make that money actively you
know in the same way that a year later I
was actively earning what was my dream
lifestyle you know my future dream
lifestyle I had written 18 months before
or you know a year before and what's
even more powerful is that if your
passive income gets to a point where
where it pays for that lifestyle for the
rest of your life and what I mean by
passive I mean the income from your
Investments not some business that is
passive because these things can always
shrink and you know and businesses get
stale and I'm talking about your safe
Investments to grow your one year and
what was crazy for me was that three
years later after I had done that from
an active perspective I'd built up a big
enough Nest Egg where I made that every
single year just from my investments so
that's really all to say that this stuff
is powerful and the stuff works now the
next set of books I want to talk about
is going from ten to a hundred thousand
dollars a month because once you've
nailed down your mindset and your work
machine you really enter the next phase
of getting rich now instead of working
harder you need to learn how to work
smarter or preferably still do both but
that really means that you need to focus
on systems that you can leverage and as
a result the type of books that will get
you from ten to a hundred thousand
dollars a month are very very different
in the four hour work week illustrates
this point perfectly in describing the
Pareto Principle you see the Pareto
Principle also known as the 80 20 rule
states that 80 percent of Any Given
output derives from 20 of the input so
in other words twenty percent of your
clients will make up eighty percent of
your revenue and the craziest part is
that this rule extends far beyond just
business it's pretty much a law of
nature for example 20 of food causes 80
of weight gain so regardless of how you
frame it the 80 20 rule allows you to
figure out how to work smarter not
harder the next book we need to talk
about is influence and the psychology of
persuasion now this is one of the
highest leveraged skills you can have is
the ability to persuade masses of people
and that's really where influence the
psychology of persuasion this book truly
shines and I feel like this book is very
powerful when you read it right before
reading the next one which is
confessions of an advertising man you
see this book paired with David ogilvy's
confessions of an advertising man are
pretty much the only marketing books
that you will ever need to get rich
because they're going to teach you the
fundamentals of persuasion both in
marketing and more broadly as well as
the skill of copywriting so once you
know how to Market and persuade buyers
you need to make sure that your product
is constantly evolving and that is the
focal point of the next book I'm going
to recommend which is the Lean Startup
now the book talks about the importance
of execution plus having a proper
feedback loop because when you're able
to execute fast and have proper feedback
you're going to be able to quickly pivot
off the back of that and tap into the
heart of the demand in any given market
now the next high leverage skill you
need in Your Arsenal as you build your
way up from ten to a hundred thousand
dollars per month is negotiation and
we've all heard the saying that
everything is a negotiation and that's
precisely why it's so important to be
good at it now the difference between
knowing nothing and just reading a few
books on the topic are massive and
that's why I never split the difference
is going to give you the Baseline you
need in your path to a hundred thousand
dollars a month it teaches you a method
called tactical empathy which you can
use to build trust and Rapport and the
result of this the other person will
mimic the same level of empathy for you
whether you're negotiating with clients
business partners or potential investors
the techniques in this book will help
you make more money and it doesn't have
to be Complicated by the way simple
things like mirroring what the person is
doing in front of you will have a
profound subconscious effect on them
that could mean just repeating someone's
last few words at the beginning of your
sentence that can form the familiarity
that you need to win negotiations but
the key to success here is understanding
people and that's where the next book
comes in now listen no matter where you
make your money you're gonna have to
deal with people it doesn't matter if
it's your employees or the police you
need to know how to deal with people
because the difference between knowing
how to navigate the social landscape and
not is truly the difference between
failure and success you need to learn
how to inspire others to fulfill your
vision and also how to not piss off the
wrong people because let me tell you
something friends are far more useful
than enemies and that's why how to Win
Friends and Influence People is perhaps
the best book I've read when it comes to
understanding human nature that book
when the 48 Laws of Power are your
complete guide to Human Relationships
the 48 Laws of Power teaches you laws of
human nature it's actually rooted in
history now I also want to give you a
disclaimer and say that the 48 Laws of
Power can also be used for evil so make
sure you use it wisely now once you've
nailed down your marketing your product
and your relationships there's one
Central Point that remains you need to
be able to build a bulletproof business
and that means you need to understand
the ins and outs of business so when
you're trying to get from ten thousand
dollars per month you can be a bit rough
around the edges but that does not fly
when you want to play in the big leagues
now sure you could go out and spend a
quarter million dollars on an MBA or you
could just read the personal MBA because
this book distills everything you need
to know about business and really 99 of
the things you'd learn from doing an MBA
in the first place this book talks about
everything from operations management
and finance to leadership and accounting
and I can promise you that if you read
just this book you'll know more than
most business owners now next let's talk
about going from a hundred thousand
dollars a month to a million dollars a
month now something interesting happens
when you go from 100K to a million
dollars a month you see up until 100K
per month you focus on building skills
you want to learn the nitty-gritty that
allows you to excel essentially there's
a one-to-one relationship between your
skills and your income but that changes
drastically when you want to get 10
million dollars per month now the
knowledge you begin to seek is far more
esoteric instead of looking to improve
your sales you're trying to understand
the bigger picture that you operate in
in simply where you start to look beyond
your business and that's when things get
really exciting and at a hundred
thousand dollars a month is also when
investing becomes crucial in your wealth
accumulation now of course you should
have good investing habits from day one
but at a hundred thousand dollars a
month and above is where things get
serious and that is precisely why you
need to read books like the intelligent
investor to really move the needle when
it comes to making you more money and
this is not just some get rich quick
scheme this is a tried and tested method
since 1949. the book outlines everything
you need to know about value investing
which is really the only way you should
be investing to protect and multiply
your wealth with minimal risk now later
in the video we're going to talk a
little bit about JP Morgan but there's
one quote in particular that stands out
from him you see JP Morgan famously once
said that whilst millionaires don't use
astrology billionaires do in the next
book reality Tran surfing is less about
astrology but it is about using the
world to your advantage reality Tran
surfing posts a theory that you can
manage your reality with Tran surfing
you can make your goal rules happen now
of course take this with a grain of salt
but there is no doubt that there is much
more to reality than meets the eye and
equally it is clear that some people
just seem to be able to bend reality to
their will and all I'm gonna say to that
point is that I know a lot of people
look at me
with that same thought they look at me
and they go how have you done all of
this how have you accomplished all this
how have you been able to bend reality
to exactly what you wanted and all I'm
going to say to that is I read reality
Tran surfing when I was 14 years old for
the first time since then I must have
reread it over a dozen times I'm not
going to say anything more make of that
who you will now as important as it is
to master your own reality you also need
to understand everyone else's because
how people act ultimately shapes the
economy and that's what the book
misbehaving is all about it's an
introduction to behavioral economics
behavioral economics is one of those
areas that simply doesn't matter when
you just want to get to ten thousand
dollars a month but it matters a whole
lot when you want to get to a hundred
thousand dollars and especially a
million dollars a month or more the book
explains how investors can use
behavioral economics to their advantage
and this is yet another great example of
how one simple book can make you now
let's go from a million dollars a month
to 10 million dollars a month and
further and this is where things get
very very interesting here's where
things begin to really shift to get to a
million dollars a month and above you
need to analyze the world around you and
you need to understand how things work
but in order to get to 10 million
dollars a month onwards you need to
start analyzing history in order to
understand the future and it's at this
level you need to get into the most
esoteric books books that I've been
talking about for years on my YouTube
books like the creature of Jekyll Island
this book unveils The Secrets of the
money magicians of the Federal Reserve
because it's only once you begin to
understand how money actually works that
you can start to really get wealthy and
I know that when I read this book it
completely opened my eyes to the real
world a world which most people are
blind to but once you understand the
Federal Reserve you also need to
understand how the banking system works
and once you understand the fed and the
banking system you can truly begin to
realize your ultimate potential and
that's why these books are so important
in making you rich and that's why the
next book I want to talk about which is
the house of Morgan it's actually a
biography of the entire Morgan family
and how they created the modern day
banking system I have said this time and
time again but history is doomed to
repeat itself and the only way to truly
be able to understand the future is by
studying the past and once you have a
firm grasp on the past you can even
begin to start predicting the future you
see history repeats itself and you can
actually use that to your advantage go
ahead and think about all the different
bubbles in history everything from the
gold rush in the 1850s to the rise of
Bitcoin I mean what if you'd bought
Bitcoin in 2010 well if these cycles of
boom and bust have happened all
throughout history well then they're
bound to happen again the key is that
you need to be able to spot the trend
before everyone else and that is exactly
what devil take the hindmost teaches you
this book will walk you through the
major cycles of boom and bust in recent
history and that means that after
reading this you're going to be able to
identify these Trends and that my friend
is how you can multiply your wealth
tenfold equally it's also how you can
protect your wealth so that's why it's
so important to understand the past in
order to understand or even predict the
future you see in some sense getting
rich is all about doing the right thing
in the right order at the right time I
mean just think about it you could have
had the best idea for a tech startup
after the.com bubble but you would have
never gotten funding and vice versa so
that's why it's important to be able to
spot the trends as they emerge so ladies
and gentlemen those are the 17 books
that will help you make your first ten
thousand dollar a month all the way up
to your first 10 million dollar a month
those are the best books I I have used
in that time period if you want to make
more than 10 million dollars a month I
can't help you with that because I've
never done that but these books read at
the right time in that order have helped
me the most and I can tell you the books
that I read to start making more than a
million dollars a month I still read
some of those books when I was dead
broke it was interesting but I don't
feel like it helped me at the right time
and that's why I think it's so important
that you read these books I mean you can
read them for entertainment even if they
don't apply to your current situation
but just understand when you read these
books at the right time when you're
facing the problems that these books
will teach you about that's when it's
the most powerful a lot of these books I
reread when I applied more to me and my
life situation at that period of time
and it was always so mind-blowing
because I would read the book and I'm
like but I've read this before but why
is it that this time I find it so
incredible like why has this been so
powerful this time and of course it was
because it directly reflected what I was
going through at that point in my wealth
creation phase so ladies and gentlemen I
really hope enjoyed this video I stayed
at a very very late compiling all these
books and just going through all of my
physical books all of my Kindle books
everything to really bring you this
specific list so I hope it was a value
to you and as always I'll be watching
you from afar and I'm rooting for you