so these at 148 models honestly what
would be the maximum budget that you
would want to spend this couch to two
chairs it would cost about four hundred
thousand dollars so the G550 this is the
out what it looks like outside that
airplane is going to cost about 3.6
million dollars a year to run it
it's hard to hate on the truth I'm
living enough men hey with Elijah
instead counting cash with the phone
through my ear I feel like Meek on a
private jet
we are in Liverpool doing some final
taste tests for it's quite cool that
we're able to come to the manufacturing
plant because they don't normally let
this happen the suburbs are filled with
ebonics and trap Sonics and then what's
the sodium content like in lecture
profile
yeah so we've got sweet but slightly
more electrolyzing so it's the same in
terms of sodium potassium chloride
magnesium there's like
because you smell it it smells like a
smells quite intense and you drink it
it's like an odd flavor yeah it's odd it
doesn't taste it and then after it's
nice
during that I think it fixes it oh yeah
this one's much better
oh wow your favorite candy
I like this one a lot yeah this one's
nice I actually think this one's my
favorite one out of all of the flavors
so far try that because you you've drunk
yeah
that's great yeah it doesn't even taste
like if you know that this is really
healthy for you it just makes it 10
times more enjoyable no but I'm I'm
dying right now you'll never ever sell
me on a bottle ever he's gonna try that
every time we see it right
so after a heavy morning of testing you
come down to six flavors from probably I
think we've had 40 50 different
variations so came back after lunch had
some more prepared and yeah we have six
in front of us unfortunately we can only
launch two to start with so I guess it's
time to decide
let's do it
it off bro
I need to fire my personal truck what
the is this
what is this
I mean it's just it isn't this isn't me
I mean the the Laura was good but we
just need more Laurel did someone say
Laura
why why are you walking so slow and
aren't you meant to me
Iman my dearest Iman how are you
it's good it's no Loro it's good so Iman
see you over here you have some good
shoes some walks not bad not bad is
deals very Quantum we'll let them slide
these right here absolutely more
fantastic okay which one should I go for
what I always saying man what I always
say you see it you buy it you buy it
so Iman I say you're downstairs
[Music]
so I also have some exciting news about
to hit a million on Instagram
on Instagram okay do you have that app
dabbled good job Iman let's celebrate
with some Laura
foreign
[Music]
Olympics
as good as they come
[Music]
what is this
no but you haven't told yourself
also known as vikunya by Laura Piana
comes from a majestic proving animal
known as the the cunya they are shared
once every two years very delicately
always left to roam freely and with
their shared fibers our friends of Laura
Piana make finest of excellences
blockchain
I had this and then Alex cut a deal with
our temporary made in South Africa to
put in the washer now it's his
good deal
[Music]
see it
what do we do Iman
you buy it fine so yes very good
come on nothing better
gok or white
isn't that big
foreign
[Music]
the seats broken
very good we are going to the jet
business it's a jet business started by
a guy called Steve I remember when I
used to live in London I saw it for
years like I would see a walking just
here on Park Lane hear about to
Knightsbridge and I always used to see a
jet and you don't really ever see that
in London or really anywhere in the
world like a physical store for
purchasing Jets like you know you've got
real estate agents and stuff like that
and come in you can see some houses
stuff like that but you've never got
something like that for jets but yeah
now that things are kind of progressing
along a little better and it's something
that I've been looking at a little bit
more not yet I want to make that clear
not yet but within the next one to two
years yeah I thought we'd go along have
a chat with Steve and then also maybe
give you guys a little bit of insight
and context into the jet business how it
works I'll probably even get him to talk
about jet chartering I know a lot of you
guys are curious how much does it cost
to actually fly private is it stupid
what are the kind of planes so we'll run
through all that with Steve ambitious 14
year old grades going down and some
my favorite phrase is time is money buy
a jet so I mean it really is uh the
whole base is on an airplane I'm always
saying you know it's not about luxuries
it's really about a time machine and
being a capital asset to a company this
is a club room where sometimes like
right now you know we have a client in
in the main Studio there and so if we
really want to I have another video well
here that I can do another presentation
on however this one I can't do the full
floor plan of all the airplanes and I'll
show you I'll take you through the app
on that wall because it's just much more
effective it's one of these experiential
Journeys if you want to call it that if
you're really interested in trying to
buy an airplane this it's an
unbelievable tool so this is a little
bit more of a private
um kind of action I know it's an ashtray
there you got smoke in here you can do
whatever you want here
why is clown side Delight to highlight
the chicks this is a Airbus 319 Airbus
320 actual cross-section of of the
aircraft I didn't really buy uh build
this thing in here put it in the front
window really to sell air buses or
boeings the real reason was obviously is
a marketing gimmick to catch the
people's eyes in the window here on Park
Lane hear about the Knightsbridge I
always used to see a jet
a good marketing little place this is
really the the money shot people come
driving down this road and there's about
well pre-covered there was about 90 000
Vehicles every day going up and down
here about
um 40 people who own a jet every day
passing through this window and about
half are different every day so what we
do is at night time we take this little
advertisement or video and we put it
over here so at night everything is
black around here and then so when they
drive down they see this little video in
the window and then they see the
airplane then they see inside the window
and if they have anything to do with
corporate aircraft normally they will
find the time to come back here and and
come inside a couple carrots in my ears
enough cards for me I'm feeling like the
local scene finally cherishing me so
these are 148 models what we do now is
we have to figure out a a sensible way
to filter the airplanes out that don't
meet your parameters honestly what would
be the maximum maximum budget that you
would want to spend 30 mil okay do you
want to have one section two sections or
three sections there's four or five or
six people in a section what do you
think is
eight minimum so now we're down to 58.
the next one is the maximum range so the
longest trip from A to B where do you
think that would be five or six times a
year I'd say farthest realistic maybe
Dubai to London this is the range that
you can go non-stop okay so anywhere in
Europe you can make it to South Africa
and you can make it to Singapore however
this is with no wind right so now this
was the winds last week at 35 000 feet
so what this means is that you're going
to be able to fly faster when you're
going east and you're not going to be
able to go as far on Range or it's going
to take you longer when you're going
west you can see that here you can make
Singapore with all these airplanes but
if you were to start now in Singapore
and watch this this is so you can see if
I go to Singapore
you are just barely matter of fact if
the winds get a little bit worse and get
the 75 knots average you're not going to
make it back in that g280. one of the
things people don't ever ask which they
absolutely should ask is how much
baggage can I put in my airplane you can
see that this number is the 6.4 cubic
meters of luggage and this is half and I
can tell you this is a nightmare
question every time somebody has an
airplane they never ask this question
and this is the most important thing of
every flight so this is 100 scale okay
so I'm six foot I'm 180. this is the
exact size and so if I wanted to take
let's say the seats on the Gulf Stream
and compare it to the Challenger that's
the difference in Iowa that doesn't look
like too big of a deal you're getting a
little bit more eyewith but really where
you see the difference is when we look
at the as a floor plan so this this is
100 scale of the Gulfstream 550. you got
the kitchen door here the galley door
and most airplanes the front section has
these 4 or single seats this is the
really the normal setup so the G550 this
is the out what it looks like outside
and this is what it looks like inside
you can see it's got those three
sections this is the door that closes
off and you got that bedroom back there
and the bathroom behind it this
airplane's got for the class it's got
the biggest window see how big that
window is yeah it's huge window this is
twice the size of let's say the windows
on the airlines up front you have a
really big kitchen flight attendant can
prepare anything they bring your food
from Whole Foods or you can get it from
Harry's Bar or you know wherever you
want it and it's you can get it from
whatever your place you want but it's
nice when it's prepared fresh on the
airplane I'd say this airplane You're
Gonna Fly at 350 hours a year and you're
going to pay 450 dollars a gallon okay
that airplane is going to cost about 3.6
million dollars a year to run it okay
which is about ten thousand an hour
really the main thing there's three
things you could do to Interior the soft
goods which is all the fabric whether
it's the the side panels the ceiling the
seats the carpet that kind of stuff then
the other part is the color of the wood
and then the other one is moving
furniture around to move furniture
around is very very expensive they have
to redo engineering drawings I mean
literally on a G550 just to give you an
idea if you wanted to change this couch
to two chairs it would cost about four
hundred thousand dollars what percentage
of jet owners would you say just
genuinely have it for personal use or
corporate use two-thirds it's one
one-third of all airplanes are out on
the charter as a third party Chargers
because I think that's probably one of
the things that most people don't
understand it's okay cool very nice you
bought your jet this that now you're
down three million dollars a year just
to maintain and upkeep it are you seeing
them more and more jet owners are buying
it understanding that you know for
example my position I'm spending me four
or five hundred thousand dollars a year
on jet Charters you know why don't when
I buy a jet myself and then why don't I
Charter it out in the meantime well that
is a great question when you're
operating it when you have an airplane
the budget is broken up in two things
you got fixed cost and you have variable
costs fixed cost is what you have to pay
whether you fly one hour or 400 hours
okay it's the pilot salaries it's
insurance it's the hangar all those
things whether you move the airplane or
not you pay and then every hour you fly
it you have fuel Landing fees catering
Pilots hotels Euro control flight all
that kind of stuff so the variable cost
per hour is five thousand seven hundred
dollars so if you're flying 400 hours a
year it costs you four thousand an hour
fixed Cost Plus
15 so it's 9 500 an hour but if you
start flying more hours then this is
less per hour so it's cheaper to fly per
hour the more you fly it if you're able
to Charter this airplane for 12 000 an
hour dollars we're talking about and
every hour this question you half that
that means you're making six thousand
dollars an hour profit not including
fixed cost if you can uh Charter the
airplane out for 200 hours that's 200
times six you're making a profit of 1.2
million dollars that comes off of this
and now your fixed costs are only four
hundred thousand so if you're flying now
if half to 200 hours in your and you're
renting enough 200 hours if you get this
to 400 000 and you're flying 200 hours a
year it's two thousand dollars an hour
plus this so now it's costing you 7 500
an hour and the more you fly it the
cheaper it gets you'll say well I can go
rent it out 300 hours a year you can but
you know every other day you're going to
get a phone call you have to give owner
approval and you can say wow who is it
you know I just did the interior I don't
want them to have red wine I don't want
them to smoke I don't want to have a dog
I don't want to have a coffee yeah
because they're going to split on the
carpet and on a Gulf Stream and replace
the carpet it's seventy thousand dollars
so or if you have a you know a kid who's
chartering the plane he has a Sharpie
and he's oh mama and right across the
wall on the Suede and you know you're
not going to get it out so you have to
replace the pound you know these kind of
things are are inconvenient