all right so for the first time I'm
revealing my watch
collection
yeah's just the best watch brand on
[Music]
Earth honestly thank you very much I
already have this watch right
[Music]
here
this is probably half of it I've got
another 25% of my collection in another
box just like this here in Dubai and
then I've got another box like this uh
in London so I also keep some of my
collection in London so in the watch
roll I have my four favorite watches in
my collection at the moment but we'll
save that till the end of the video what
watch would you say you wear the least I
guess in the half of the collection that
I have here today probably this rose
gold Daytona with black dial I've got
quite a few white gold daytonas there in
the rest of my collection in the other
box that doesn't get as much rist time
and you'll notice that there's still
quite a few scratches on here and that's
because any watches that I personally
don't wear that much I give to my
friends to wear so this has gotten a lot
of risk time on my friends wrists but
for me personally I'm just not a massive
fan of rose gold and white gold daytonas
at least compared to a platinum Daytona
or for example something like this I
love the rose gold Daytona on the oyster
flex and I think it comes down to really
just the way that the bezel pops on the
oyster Flex because they do the ceramic
bezel same as what you'd find on a steel
Daytona rather than the bezel that they
do on the full rose gold so out of these
I'm sure you can understand why I just
prefer the pop of color with the oyster
Flex with the steel or for example right
here with the Platinum Daytona which you
say is your favorite out of these 100%
Platinum Platinum I remember I requested
this watch from Rolex in 2020 and no one
really wanted them like they want them
now so yeah what can I say it's just
it's there it makes a statement but it
doesn't need to scream too loud so this
is a watch that I love this is a
meteorite Daytona on the oyster Flex
once again just talking about precious
metals I got offer the meteorite which
is a extremely difficult dial to get I
got offered it on my chist between a
full white gold or rose gold bracelet
and I ended up declining that watch
holding out and opting for this instead
I took this watch skiing earlier this
year and I don't know it just felt like
the perfect watch like in the snow in
here I have one more I actually wish I'd
put Less daytonas in this Bo I wish I'd
taken some of my other watches uh I have
one more Daytona white gold blue dial
once again just uh once again what can I
say beautiful watch classic watch
Timeless watch because it's white gold
wow this has a lot of scal I think this
has been with my friends far more than
me so whoever to abuse this watch wow I
didn't realize until now it's definitely
very scuffed up but at least my friends
got some good enjoyment out of it I
think I have one Vashon in here so this
is the Vashon overseas this is the
second overseas that I have so what I
love about this watch which uh is also
same with the Cartier
Santos so this is one of my skeletons
this is a steel I've also got a rose
gold I don't really wear this watch much
anymore so Alex my head of production
this has basically just been his watch
this entire year so yeah yeah you're
you're daily
beater don't worry about it don't worry
about it there'd be chunks out if I was
wearing it I'm I'm the worst with it so
anyways as I was saying the thing I love
about this is just this uh easy uh link
system with the bracelet so you can take
this off as such and then now you've got
the rose gold bracelet off and I don't
have the strap here with me but you can
put like a Navy strap on I've got Navy
strap to match the dial I think without
a doubt of any brand this has the most
beautiful blue it's honestly just
mesmerizing I know that sounds like
dramatic but it's you can just look at
it in so many different lights the
Sunburst effect yeah honestly incredible
incredible dial Great brand great watch
and I feel like if you see someone with
a Vashon you know that they're probably
a bit more of a serious collector than
just wearing a royal oak or an allus or
something like that let's talk about
that AP this one yeah big boy big boy so
I'm not really a fan of offshores I'd
been offered a couple offshores in the
past was never that interested it's a 42
mm offshore and it's also titanium so
it's very light usually offshores are
very big they're very bulky and fair
enough this watch is still very very
bulky but I don't know just quite light
and it's big but it's not a 44 like some
of their other offshores so I just
thought thought you know what I need an
offshore in my collection it doesn't get
that much risk time but sometimes for
example when I'm going on holiday short
little trip somewhere you know this
makes it outside of the watch case show
us
something that is a heavy HIIT okay I'll
give you what other people would
consider I mean there's a lot of Heavy
Hitters in here but like one that people
would most certainly consider a heavy
hitter and then one that the watch
Community uh so this is a 351 this not
the 3502 with the open case back it's
the 01 with the closed case back this
watch is extremely extremely light I
have it on the velcro strap over the
years I've played around with having
this watch with the deployment clasp as
well as some of my other RMS I put them
on deployment clasps but like I always
just keep coming back to the velcro I
know it is insane it's absolutely
ridiculous to have a watch that's worth
$300,000 on velcro but that's just
that's RM RM to me is about just not
taking yourself too serious it's
comfortable it's light as I said that's
why I like the velcro that's why I avoid
the deployment clasp so I'd say another
one that would be considered a heavy
hitter is one of my recent pickups uh
this I've been waiting for for some time
from pek this is a world time but it's
not just any world time it is an enamel
world time so actually just a couple
months ago I was at pp6 which is pect
manufacturing plan and that was a super
cool experience PCH flew me out to
Geneva on the jet I got to spend a
couple days there I got to sit down and
have lunch with their CEO and one of the
arms of their manufacturing plant was
their enameling facility so basically I
got to learn about the whole enameling
process and I will say when you go to
the factories of these manufacturers it
genuinely does just give you a totally
new appreciation for these watches so I
definitely say that anyone who's into
horology this would be a heavy hitter
for them so just going back to
complications this is a white gold
Nautilus 5740 I'm not going to sit here
and pretend to be Nico Leonard and know
all the numbers and all the different
reference ref is I am a collector I'm
not an expert so I do want to just make
that clear I'm not going to be able to
tell you too much more about the watch
except for the fact that I believe it's
the most complicated nless it's white
gold and it looks beautiful would you
say it's your favorite out of that box
no no I'd say that out of this box it's
probably either the enamel dial or this
which is a rose gold aquanut I adore
rose gold watches and the combination of
rose gold and brown is my favorite
you're going to see one of my watches
here and one of my other watches which
is my favorite watch and was my favorite
watch for the longest time the 5711r
rose gold narus until I got something
that's in that watch roll which ended up
beating it as my favorite watch but yeah
when it comes to aquanuts very
comfortable I think incredibly
comfortable bracelet I actually find
them to be more comfortable than rolex's
oyster Flex that's just me personally
and I just like the low thin profile of
it I just like it when the watches are
just flush and
Sleek yeah so I love this watch uh let's
see if we want to go back to Rolex we've
got a couple Day dates in here this is
the 60th anniversary green olive dial
this is an example in white gold and
this is an example in rose gold with a
diamond bezel I'm not a massive Diamond
guy to be honest and if it is Diamond
obviously it has to be Factory but I
don't know sometimes it's fun to just
mix up have a little bit little little
pop of shine I'd say that there's still
a lot of stuff that I really need to EXP
explore I pretty much only got Rolex PCH
Philip rishard Mill AP feron Cartier I
feel like I still have a lot of
collecting to do I lot of moon swatches
I do have a lot of moon swatches that
correct I was wearing one when I started
Moon swatches are just cheap they're
just fun I put them on these rubber
straps and yeah it's nice if you're ever
in Europe and you don't want to get your
uh arm chopped off it's good little fun
watch to wear uh let's see what else do
we have in here we've got Batgirl some
people like go on the oyster bracelet I
personally like go on the the Jubilee I
actually really love this watch I don't
know it's just it's a good watch good
watch Pepsi I think I've already talked
to you guys about this this is a white
gold this is not the steel uh the steel
I believe has a darker dial so yeah
white gold but for 99% of people you
would never be able to tell the
difference rose gold AP once again on
the theme of thin profile watches I just
really love the jumbos because they're
thinner more flush some of the AP cases
can get kind of big which is great for
certain occasions but just dated day I
don't I just like the thinner profile of
it so I've got this watch as well in
Platinum with the green dial and that
watch is crazy watch super difficult
super difficult watch to get and then
let's see the last one to talk about
here is probably this which is the
5205g this a white gold piece from pek
at the moment I've got on this sort of
canvas e strap I've had this watch for
maybe four years three 3 years four
years at this point once again it's got
this blue Sunburst dial Great watch
beautiful beautiful 38 mm so a little on
the smaller size for my wrist but it's
it's just Timeless it's a Timeless size
is going to be appropriate and hold its
own so yeah this is gray watch and then
now getting into my favorite pieces in
my watch collection at the moment
obviously as a collector that changes
month by month but they are some Heavy
Hitters I will I will say that so these
are the four watches that have been in
my rotation the most and gone the most
risk time as of late this is my favorite
watch Ever if I had to have one watch
for the rest of my life it would be this
it is the 5712r it took everything that
I loved about the 5711r and just made it
even better one big thing that they
added on this is the extension so if you
press here and you can do it on both
sides it can make the watch longer it
can make the bracelet longer and
obviously that is very useful on hot
days you can you know increase the
extension then that gives you some extra
wrist space right now it's quite cold so
this slides back back quite a lot for me
I don't know what it is but with pek
like sometimes I feel it's inappropriate
to wear rose gold in certain situations
but like I don't know why with this
watch I just feel like it's not
screaming like I just feel like it's so
elegant so even though it is rose gold
even though it can be perceived to some
people as flashy for me it's just
stuning what a watch what a watch this
is a platinum DayDay this exact
configuration this has the baguette
bezel and it also has the baguette
markers you know it's got some ice on
here I just think it's incredible I know
it's got some diamonds on here but I
still feel like it's appropriate it's
not like that crazy it's it's still in a
way elegant and I just think it's
beautifully balanced there's certain
Watchers that you just look at and
you're like this works this makes sense
and I'd say this is definitely one of
those watches where it's just very well
balanced now the next watch is
incredible absolutely incredible this is
a Celestial there's a couple minute
repeaters that I'm eyeing up I I think
that'll probably be my next dress watch
from pek is a minute repeater but
outside of that I'd say this is probably
my favorite dress watch now this is a 44
mm watch it's a large dress watch so a
lot of people it just won't work for
them once again because I have larger
wrists this still works this is
definitely not a watch you're going to
see often there's definitely not many
people that want to be spending this
sort of money for a dress watch that
like no one knows what it is and this is
definitely a collector's piece but it's
incredible to be able to look up the sky
and know exactly where the constellation
is and where all the stars are placed
and that perfectly matches your watch
yeah it's just an insane complication
insane watch and the last watch is a
watch that has been in my rotation ever
since I got it I was in love with it and
even when I first started getting into
rard Mill this was the watch that from
day one I told him that I wanted this is
a 6702 and they have a few variations of
it this is the Zev I believe and this
watch is so insanely light but as you're
going to see as is a theme with a lot of
my other watches I like thin profile
watches so this is RM this gives you
that comfortability that lightness that
you get with rard Mill but without you
know that extra chunkiness so for
example if you take it compared to the
351 just check that out you know you can
see how much extra the 3501 protrudes
out compared to the 6702 yeah stunning
watch huh so ladies and gentlemen that
is my watch collection I started
collecting watches in 201 18 when I was
18 years old I'd made my first million
doll from the business and I basically
had been collecting ever since and I was
collecting even when it wasn't a
financially smart decision when every
single Watch I was buying and I was
losing money on that doesn't really
matter I think if you find something
that you are interested in go collect
obviously be sensible and most
importantly buy whatever you're to I
have some of my friends that have just
collections of Omega speed Masters or I
have friends that pretty much only wear
vintage Cartiers so whatever you're into
find out what that is keep working hard
and I think watches are an incredible
way to reward yourself for every chapter
of your life and watches are also an
incredible hobby that you can share with
your friends your loved ones you know
all of my friends wear all my nice
watches cuz I just you know I just don't
have enough time to wear all of them so
I would much rather they get appreciated
by other people even if there are
scratches or this that like these things
are are made to be used and worn so with
all that being said work hard and I'm
sure I'll see you with a collection like
this sometime soon