here we go baby welcome back to the Vlog
so where are we going we are off to do a
bit of car shopping I think I've said
this before but what I'm in UK as you
can see most driven in Dubai I'm driven
I'm almost in the back driving in Dubai
is genuinely stressful so most of the
time I just sit in the back do some work
make some calls yeah that's day-to-day
occasion when we go abroad I'll rent out
some nice supercars some nice sports
cars have a little bit of fun zip around
so at the moment all the cars that I own
are all cars that's in the back today
I'm buying my first ever Supercar well I
might be buying we're stopping off at
one place then we're gonna go check out
a few other spots as well see what can
be done how quickly it can be done
because there is for example one
specific car I want but it'll take three
to four years and unfortunately I don't
have that time because I need a car in
one year exactly for a very special
event that I'm very excited for and
actually it might even be a cool
opportunity for us to hang out and spend
some time around some cool cars but I
will tell you a little bit more about
that at the end of the video
[Music]
I guess we have to wait until then to
talk about but there's not many people
who buy a car knowing that they're gonna
slap on an aggressive amount of Miles
pretty quickly so it's only 1500 miles A
Thousand Miles yeah so I guess that kind
of changes things you know and that's
funny like I feel as a listeners the
cars you want to drive for a quick 30 60
minutes I have to consider a few other
things with this purchase you know like
such as like the health of my back oh
really
[Music]
what the [ __ ] This Is Not Gonna Change
oh god this is my worst nightmare I
actually can't think of anything worse
have you driven one before yeah was it
rock hard seats yes these have got
Comfort Seats really I know you these
are Comfort Seats
this is unbelievably comfortable
[Music]
I need my tracksuit all right what else
we got well this is the one or you can
go super loud
an sto yeah no not that thing yeah no no
chance no you don't want that it's a
comfortable thing
I mean listen I get it if you're on
track days right that's a good tracking
car but like yeah
[Music]
nah what how I mean yeah it's nice but
you're in your 20s yeah so yeah but I
have a phantom bro I'm an old man you
know this is beautiful beautiful spec
great color nice interior drop top
I'm sure the carplay in here is nice
yeah I'm sure it's great
ah I can get a nice and comfy on this
one I'm not letting you buy this I'll
buy that I'll go half of you if you were
half of me on a pet me
oh God
I don't know what we're going about okay
I'll consider it okay if you want
something that's got four months it's
all the Lamborghini drama of v10 or V12
but you want five seats big boot space
this is a car you buy you know what I
think this is probably the only Lambo
I'd own yeah like I'm just probably the
only Lambo I'd buy I have no use for it
but it's because you haven't been in an
event at all I have but it's not driven
it
you think uh the issue is I don't think
it really fits into car rally to be
honest how much money you got a lot how
many problems you got
be honest he's not here be honest yeah
it's you won't you won't drive it I know
you yeah but I will
what do you realistically for me it has
to be a Porsche maybe a Ferrari I'm just
so aggressively against Lambos
hey it works does it yeah you know all I
need now Lamborghini I bet me no
now's a good time for me to explain why
I actually need my first Supercar so as
you guys know I don't do any in-person
events I don't do Keynotes speeches I
got so much that comes across my table
this is the first thing in so long that
actually interested me and that's
because I know how incredible of an
entrepreneur John is and I know that
this is just gonna be such a cool chance
to meet so many you guys spend a week
together so now is probably a good time
to actually unveil what this is so maybe
you want to tell them a little bit about
the magic that you've created with Mod
Ball but basically the mob ball it's
been around for 17 years it's like the
craziest week it's like a rolling
Festival last year I went to the Monaco
Grand Prix this year's Ibiza but next
year we're taking it back to the Monaco
Grand Prix because it's so incredible in
the past year what I've seen you do on
YouTube and your social media and your
businesses is like incredibly impressive
and long story short we're partnering up
for next year's event everyone's going
to bring his entire but media side of
things all that kind of stuff and we're
going to bounce ideas off for all the
parties and events so I know that you
like to party every now and again so
yeah we're basically joining our brains
together to create the most epic model
in 18 years so for most of you guys this
will be a court opportunity for me to
take you through the Journey of buying
my first Supercar it's gonna be a super
cool week we're going to be touring all
the way through Europe and ending off in
Monaco for Grand Prix and Marco Grand
Prix is one of the probably five to ten
events a year that everyone wants to go
to and no one can do it right and not
only that but be there with a hundred
plus other people that have the same
interest in you have the same likes as
you and it's not just that but a week of
traveling with people I mean that's
that's one way to bond and you're
definitely going to leave with a very
special connection with all the people
who attend it's good you mentioned that
because obviously we're opening up 150
slots but for the hundreds of other
thousands that watch this but
unfortunately you know don't have the
financial means to attend this yet and
by the way this is something that can be
aspirational you guys can actually come
and we'll make it known where we're
stopping off in which cities and you can
basically come and see a 150 incredible
supercars speak to the owners I'm sure
that if you ask the owners of these
supercars hey what did you do how do you
end up in this position you know can you
tell me a little bit about your story
you know you're going to end up meeting
so many interesting characters along the
way so one of the things I've always
wanted to do on mobile because we have
like a we have a Great Gatsby pie during
the week and in Monaco we can have a
charity vote and I would love love to
raise a million dollars somehow for
charity it's a little bit about how you
can get involved bear in mind it will be
application process this is similar to
any serious business Mastermind of
course we're gonna go we're gonna have a
ton of fun we're gonna raise a bunch of
money for charity we're gonna have
lifelong experiences but at the end of
the day we need to make sure and it's
very very important we need to make sure
we Safeguard who comes the caliber of
people to come because then they were
spending a week together so for us to
dedicate a week of our life and interact
daily with all of the attendees we want
to make sure that we have the highest
caliber people there so there'll be a
link below where you can apply the cost
is 9950 per person minimum of 2 two
people in a car and John maybe you can
tell them what that actually includes
yes that includes all the hotels the
entire experience all the events doesn't
include alcohol obviously but yeah
includes actually everything car
displays all the stickers on the cars
everything that goes along around it and
then the final part of it is that we
we've already put together the final
party on top of Nikki Beach so not only
do we get to experience the Monaco
Formula One Grand Prix as a group and
with a big party but we're overlooking
the hairpin and the Yachts at the same
time that's probably the best place you
could be for F1 Grand Prix yeah the
question is though how are you doing it
I think we need to go to Ferrari next
and that's about it I'm very excited to
see some of you guys next year spend a
week driving together creating some
amazing memories and top it all off at
Monaco F1
all right so in London now off to Rolex
dinner for their top clients I will see
what I can record and if I can get
anything for you guys then yeah and I'll
show you some of the new pieces
[Music]
so guys it's the next morning on from
the Rolex event we are currently on the
way to farnborough airport where we came
from yesterday the funny thing about
Patek is they're not gonna be like oh
and then we take the jet to Geneva but
it's at farnborough airport which is
only a private airport so I think we're
going back on a jet I think or they may
have just told the Wiz there to come to
Farmer so we'll see we'll see yeah
anyways it's early morning off to go to
Geneva to go around the factory to get a
little tour of the historical buildings
and see some of New pieces so I'm very
very excited for this one to be honest
as you guys know Patek is outside I've
even watches that says party my favorite
brand on Earth so
oh baby
[Music]
no text back so call misses I feel like
we all victims
[Music]
drunk testing I should not do Patron
what are we doing well Amara planned
activities and then the worst [ __ ]
activities on earth look at it Segways
and you have to wear a helmet apparently
I can feel how bad it is clay pigeon
shooting except it's [ __ ] laser
this is pathetic I'm already talking out
here Amara took a fat out okay so just
get it over them all the way around yeah
that's it and then you've got to go
around the pole all the way around on
the second one come through here for the
second nap yeah
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
I'm late because I come bearing gifts
Santa Claus lots of gifts
yeah
there's like actually like [ __ ] tons of
gifts
you supplies
[Music]
also um wait uh there's one other thing
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
so much
[Applause]
well listen uh I mean there's 101 things
I want to say but as you guys know I
don't have much family that's basically
just me and my mom only child and and
you know when I was younger I found that
very difficult I found it very tough
just being me myself and I I'm sure you
know maybe some of you guys have
brothers or sisters but maybe you felt a
little alone and you felt like you know
maybe
you don't have your tribe or the people
that had your back no matter what you
know as you mentioned the people who you
know you'd go to war with I always say
this I think loyalty to me is such a big
thing and I think I know from the bottom
of my heart that we all have each
other's back and I know from all my
heart that we would all go to war for
each other that's why you know it's
listening to do some incredible things
for our customers for our community for
for the kids in Nepal but like I can
tell you out of everything for me the
most incredible thing about this company
is having family and you guys Jenny are
from low in our best family I've ever
wished for so
thank you