[Music]
you know I just remember day after day
coming downstairs and just seeing my mom
and clipped those [ __ ] coupons and I
just remember thinking like no like this
is not this is not going to be my life
this is not going to be our life
you know if I don't take care of my
family you know he's not just me and my
mom no one is
so
we'll get through it how does this
moment feel
this moment feels Bittersweet it feels
like I guess a sense of accomplishment
but also
a nostalgic in a bad way because I don't
necessarily have the best memories in
and around here
so guys I don't usually do this thing
where I Vlog and I share my day and life
and whatnot but this is a video that
means a lot to me so I'd appreciate it
if you stuck around for the entirety of
it but um I'm moving out of this house
tomorrow morning
I've been here for 14 years
um it's kind of all I know
but all will be explained in this video
[Music]
after a couple years of dating my
stepdad my mom moved to London and we
ended up living on the street in his
house and some back then 20 years ago of
course it was nice living in London
living in an expensive area but my house
was not a home my house wasn't on a
place that was particularly happy at so
I grew up in a house like this
it's crazy
with no warm water with no heating when
my stepdad found out I was starting a
business he cut off the Wi-Fi the walls
were caving in in my room there was mold
it was a [ __ ] show and to make things
worse my stepdad put cameras not on the
outside on the inside of the house so I
grew up as like a [ __ ] prisoner in my
own house like I was I had someone
watching me 24 7 and yeah when I say
this is bittersweet
this is
The Last Place on Earth I would want to
buy my mama house The Last Place on
Earth
family office manages the wealth of
families except my family is just
basically me and my mom so today I'm
just making a very big purchase
look Central London residential real
estate is probably the one of the safest
asset classes in the world this is why
the whole world goes everyone buys
property there the Indians the Arabs the
Russians the Chinese
crazy 15 buses yeah [ __ ] hell
so after everything's all said and done
it'll probably be closer to what four
million dollars yeah for the purchase so
once I got to a certain age you
basically my stepdad divorced my mom and
my mom got a letter through the mail
from his lawyers that basically said you
have seven days to leave the house she
lost her home so at that point obviously
I didn't know how long it would take but
I promised her that I'd buy her the
house and I didn't think I could do it
soon but yeah I guess I made it happen
today I just haven't been you know as
happy or as engaged as I normally am
sometimes you just get so caught up in
the bigger picture you get caught up in
this person who's doing this more than
you you lose touch of how far you're
going and your own track and at the end
of the day that's the only thing that
matters I'm the type of person who goes
too hard on himself
I
you know I I sort of discredit what I've
achieved so far which in the scope of
things to me isn't that much considering
the vision I have and what I want to do
but it's still something to be proud of
and that's something I need to remember
for myself so if you're in the same
position be proud of where you are and
keep moving forward but don't forget
what you've already accomplished and
achieved
[Music]
um
everybody
all right 11 30. okay
so I had to sacrifice my queen
in order to keep the king alive so I
told her listen like you're basically
the first person offered this watch
I went to Geneva this weekend with Patek
you know they arranged it
Patek has been very kind to our family
don't screw this up yeah no it should
definitely come for that no but bro my
mom's so funny she's like she's like
okay arrange for a different day I'm
like Mom I don't think I said how
special this watch is and the fact that
you're getting it and she's like I'm
like what's more important the
spectacular or your parents she's like
my hair obviously yeah
I know I know my mom's so difficult
yeah okay so I had to sacrifice one
surprise that's cool that's good that's
good well played uh but at least yeah
she she said okay 11 30. well played
okay my mom was very stubborn so we had
a little the argument a little mini
friendly argument in the in the hotel
lobby and yeah honestly I was gonna
surprise her with the house first uh and
then second I told Patek that obviously
I have this very special day and that
I'd love to add a special watch to
commemorate it and as far as I know I
think I'm probably one of the first
people in the entire world to get
allocation for the new aquinol and yeah
basically I had to ruin the surprise and
I was like listen this is the only day
that Patek can do
um because she was like oh just moved
into another day I'm like Mom it's not
that simple and as I said I don't really
ruin the surprise at that point I'm like
Mom you're getting this watch which is
to die for like everyone wants this
watch every collector in the world wants
this watch
um so I was like please please just do
me a favor just please move your hair
and nail appointment so it took a lot of
convincing but we got there and then
July 2019 is that don't know when you're
watching this July 2019 was the first
month where I would actually managed to
hit a hundred thousand dollars profit
from the agency it just totally expanded
my perception of what was possible with
this agency business model
foreign
[Music]
so I think she has no idea
the way that we're going to try to do
this is basically say like Hey we're
filming like a little documentary not
releasing it now maybe just getting
clips for a future documentary uh and
and if we can go and record and touch a
little bit about my childhood and and
what a weird childhood I had so we're
gonna go record that and then
I'll surprise her with unfortunate my
childhood at home
[Music]
but the one two door is down yeah I
don't know I guess it just feels surreal
like
it's one of those very few things in my
life that I've thought about for so many
years and yeah I guess you don't know
how I feel when it happens
like bro I don't get flushing much
[Music]
one last step
hello hello hello
living here you wouldn't want to live
here I do look at the trees fresh air
Park
we're filming a little documentary thing
but not for now like it's gonna release
in like a year or two years okay but we
just need to start preparing it
uh so we're gonna go to just outside my
first school
let's talk about that and then just
outside
and talk about that a little bit and
talk about that real quick just two
quick things the other one we won't have
time for but would have been nice is
um the bookstore I always used to go to
like you know they used a bookstore in
Brixton
Brooks and bookmongers
the sacrificing handmade for that
I can't say you're in my view to today's
lens I'm sorry you have to cancel your
beauty treatments yeah
[Music]
wanna come
I have no idea
it's a big part of my life
it's pretty much the only home I know
it's at home yeah
as a family home yeah almost 20 years
and coming back it just makes me
emotional and I I just rather live yeah
no one knows me like the piano
in my mother's home
[Music]
and in my chest
you know me best do you remember when we
picked you up for lunch and I made a
comment I was like you're the queen
and you said yes the queen without a
castle and in my mind I'm like it's on
its way now I have the castle
[Music]
no one knows
obviously she was very shell-shocked I
think taking her to a very dark place
and then springing up that surprise on
her I mean she told me that on the day
off she didn't really take it in
properly and also you know with cameras
and stuff like that she she hates being
on camera and yeah we ended up looking
at the house and
then her and I had a private moment in
the bedroom we literally just sat back
against the wall just talked about yeah
growing up and obviously this was always
my dream to
give her her home back to be honest
so
yeah she cried she cried out
yeah we had a good little moment
[Music]
hello
oh you okay how are you
reminiscent good are you good done
signature signature you are now
the owner of a
Bugatti Bugatti
of a four bedroom your first home
okay crazy so let's find this
thank you