ladies and gentlemen in today's video
I'm going to share with you the 17
success secrets of the top one percent
now what this means is that I'm gonna
show you an insight into what makes
millionaires millionaires but in fact
even farther than that I've been a very
fortunate situation to make tens of
millions of dollars in my 20s and have
an incredible audience that Tunes in and
listens to me and because I've worked
hard but also been incredibly blessed in
this life that's also meant that I've
had anyone you could ever imagine try to
reach out to me connect I'm talking the
richest men in certain countries that
literally play paddle and tennis with
I'm talking some of the highest level
football or some of the highest level
Formula One drivers I'm talking
self-made owners of some of the biggest
companies on Earth so the reason I tell
you this is because what I'm going to
share with you are things that I've
personally learned in my time
accomplishing a fair amount definitely a
very respectable amount but nowhere near
what some of these people that I spend
time with on a weekly basis what they've
accomplished so even though the title of
the video is to share with you the
secrets of the top one percent this is
really stuff that applies to the top
zero zero one percent in any given
industry so with no further Ado let's
get straight into it now real quick
before we get into this video all of
these concepts are very conceptual and
are life lessons that you need to apply
but I know for a lot of people watching
they want that hey do this do that don't
do this don't do that to actually start
with their own entrepreneurial venture
and to start making money online this
year and there's tons of good ways to do
it and tons of bad ways to do it so
after you finish watching this video I'd
recommend you check out the most popular
video on my YouTube channel where I
basically compare all the most popular
business models and actually break it
down with an equation and a formula what
works and what doesn't work and what you
should probably try based on your unique
skill sets so if you think that YouTube
video may be of interest I'll leave that
as a first line in the description and
you can watch that after you're done
with this anyways so the first secret of
the top one percent is they realize that
the woman they choose will be the most
important decision that they ever make
outside of work as men the thing that
consumes most of of our time is usually
women whether I be chasing women having
experiences having fun whatever doing
your thing being single spreading your
wings all that stuff which by the way I
have done plenty of in the past it's a
lot of fun enjoy yourself do it if you
want to do it and also don't ever let
anyone shame you into thinking that's
wrong it's not wrong at all but it is
undeniably a distraction so obviously to
build a brighter future the best thing
you can have by your side is an
incredible woman but at the end of the
day most men don't choose the right
woman to have by their side most men
that want to accomplish something big in
life don't have a partner that
understands their grand ambition and
understand that they need a safe space
at home if they're going out and they're
conquering and they're doing all of this
for their future family for their wife
at home it needs to be a safe space it
needs to be a safe loving nurturing
caring environment or at least that's
what applies to extremely ambitious men
which if you're watching this I assume
is a category of men that you fall into
so either men choose women that are too
turbulent or or and I see this a lot as
well men choose women simply based on
their looks and at the end of the day
looks fade looks fade and so does
attraction and I'm talking about some of
the most beautiful women on earth I'm
talking your 10 out of 10s I'm gonna be
very honest with you for every you know
beautiful girl 10 out of 10 you see
there is a man at home who's been with
that person for years and no matter how
beautiful she is
he's bored of her attraction he's bored
of her looks and that's just kind of
what we're like as men but so many guys
are so stupid and they think oh just
because she's pretty okay cool you know
she'll be the woman by my side it's very
foolish because if you have grand
Ambitions in life it's gonna get
turbulent and you need a good person by
your side and that's really what I've
noticed with the most successful men and
for me the most respectable men that
I've ever seen is listen if they wanted
to they had their turbulence in the past
like they they enjoyed themselves they
had their experiences they did whatever
they wanted to do and some men that I
meet that I really respect and are
multi-billionaires they've only had one
partner their entire life and that's
beautiful as well but whether you go
down the path of high school sweethearts
or whether you you know have your
Playboy era the destination needs to be
the same which is an incredible woman by
your side and a woman that you choose
not based purely on looks or oh if I go
to a dinner party and you know I got a
beautiful woman by my side I'll have
more respect because listen I can tell
you high level men they don't respect
that I think when I see a guy and he has
a beautiful woman by his side and I know
that it's just a little bit of fun for
him sure that's great but when that's
his Queen like that's a Woman by his
side and she's pretty and that's it but
she has no social intelligence or
they're at a dinner table and you know
she's on her phone or she just doesn't
really know how to represent her and her
man
what respect is there in that so just
understand for the men watching this and
as you guys know I speak specifically to
men but still shout out to the 10 or 12
of women that watch this as a man the
most important decision you will make in
your life is a woman that you have by
your side the second success secret and
this is something that Percy comes from
me and I tell people this all the time
everyone deserves an opinion not
everyone deserves a say and here's what
I mean by that there are certain things
in life that I simply do not know I've
not done the research I don't have any
life experience and one of my favorite
things when someone asks me my opinion
on something that I'm just not very well
educated on I haven't really given much
thought or time or attention to it I
just love being able to say I'll be
honest I don't really have an opinion on
that or I just say I can't really make
an informed judgment on that so what I
mean by this is I believe everyone
deserves an opinion everyone can have an
opinion but not everyone deserves to say
it and you need to understand that this
applies to your parents to your friends
to maybe sometimes even in your business
I will always always take the opinion of
everyone in my business but some people
they deserve an opinion but they don't
deserve a say and I don't mean that to
belittle anyone because there's areas of
my life where I should definitely be a
louder opinion but maybe I don't really
deserve a say because I just I don't
have enough experience in that to really
bring anything meaningful to the table
so just remember this next time you're
letting other people's judgments Cloud
that inner direction that you know you
have because a lot of people around you
will give you their opinion you know
your friends your family all this and
let them have their opinions but they
shouldn't have a say in how your life
goes because who are they to tell you
unless it's someone who's extremely
successful of what you've done then yeah
they should probably have a bit of a say
in what's going on so from day one
always distinguish what is an opinion
and what is good advice those two things
are very different this third success
secret of the top one percent is once
they make money and especially when they
make money in a bulk amount because a
lot of people you know maybe they sell
their company maybe they have you know a
massive month in their business maybe
they sign a big contract unless they get
a big sum of money in they go and buy
assets and the reason that is is
especially in your first I would say
really even your first 10 to 20 years in
business or in your career you are a
massive liability to yourself if you
make a lot of money there's a high
chance a high probability that you will
spend it or maybe you have a rough
period in your life or maybe you just
have a core life or a midlife crisis I
mean these things happen so instead of
having all this cash instead when you
get a big lump sum of cash and go buy
assets go buy assets and go buy good
quality things that are a little
difficult to sell because the other
thing go invest a percentage of your
portfolio into stocks into crypto sure
do these things but at the end of the
day it's just one click of a button and
you can sell it whereas when you're
buying things like physical gold when
you're buying things like houses even
later down the line like I've been doing
a lot of in the last couple years buying
equity in businesses these aren't things
that you can just sell easily so once
you start making good amounts of money
just remember you will be the biggest
liability to yourself just remember that
you have a long career ahead of you and
there's always time to buy the Glamorous
things that you want and do this and do
that and you can do those things but
first go buy some assets go get that
money away from you now the next success
secret is do what's practical not what's
sexy the most successful people I've met
they haven't made their money by having
a you know an activewear brand or by
building this super complicated product
that took 73 million dollars in
investment to go off the ground no most
of them make money in really boring ways
really old traditional B2B Services
building software and then licensing it
out to Big corporations Import and
Export Logistics
Timber like honestly the richest people
I've met they don't do things that are
like that billion dollar unicorn company
they just find areas in the market where
there's inefficiencies or where they can
just do something even three percent
better and because of that they get more
of the market shares so yeah really what
it comes down to is don't think that you
need to build a billion dollar unicorn
company just understand that there's
money literally all around you and it
doesn't need to be as sexy as you think
it does the next success secret is that
the morning sets the tone for the rest
of the day I have friends of mine that
are multi-billionaires and some of them
wake up at 10 am and some of them wake
up at 6am and they're equally as
successful because I have friends of
mine that work in different time zones
so for them to wake up at 10 A.M makes
more sense and I have friends that have
physical offices and only work in one
country so they don't really need to
think about time zones so for them it's
nice to wake up at 6am wake up get a
training session in be in the office by
eight or nine so just understand this
whole like 5 a.m 4 a.m like you
don't need to wake up early necessarily
to be successful you just need to wake
up at a time that makes the most sense
for you and that can be different for
different people I personally wake up at
8am back when I used to live in London
you know five years ago I used to wake
up at 5 30 in the morning that worked
for me for a while until I realized that
like actually I'm not really a morning
person and then I stuck to 6 30 because
6 30 I wake up my personal trainer would
be at my house would be at the gym by
seven o'clock and that worked for me for
a few years and then now since I moved
to Dubai I have 150 employees and most
of my employees are in America or UK so
you know now eight sometimes even 8 30
that works a little better for me so
it's not about the time that you wake up
instead it's about having a set morning
routine a set thing that you do every
single morning and just understanding
that you can't crawl out of bed eat a
high sugar breakfast scroll on your
phone watch some YouTube and think that
that's going to be an impactful way to
start your day for me I wake up I wash
my face I get direct sunlight and do a
bit of stretching and warming up for 30
minutes and then I train for like an
hour and a half have some breakfast and
get to work and that's my schedule here
at my home sometimes when I'm traveling
and I'm not training as intensely
sometimes my morning routine will be
wake up have a coffee and get straight
to work it doesn't need to be anything
super crazy or 17 different steps the
next thing is the less you talk the more
they listen there's a lot of people out
here that spill too many secrets that in
negotiations are the first one to say
the price you should never ever be the
first one to say the price when you're
negotiating a deal and just in general
get themselves in way too much trouble
by talking too much so just remember the
less you talk the less mistakes you're
gonna make in sort of high stress
situations and usually the less you talk
the more other people listen and it's
just been my personal observation that
the most successful people I know they
usually don't talk too much they would
rather listen they'd rather analyze a
room and it's not always from this
Machiavellian you know trying to win a
war type thing a lot of times they're
just listening because they actually
want to get other people's opinions they
want to be questioned they want to get a
new perspective so just remember the
less you talk
the more they listen the next thing is
pick the right opportunity at the right
time and so many people have issues with
this and I feel like YouTube and social
media is a very uh terrible place for
this as well because one thing I see a
lot is people say don't do what someone
says do what they do or something along
those lines do you realize how stupid
that is because here's the thing if
let's say someone has been in an
industry for 10 years and they're
telling you hey if I was starting out I
would do this are you gonna be stupid
enough to think that you starting from
square one can do what someone else is
doing after 10 years in the industry no
don't be silly everything in life is
about doing things in the right order
it's not always about doing the right
thing it's about doing it in the right
order so just understand the things you
do today are nowhere near as impressive
as what you can do in three years ten
years 30 years in 30 years if you do
business right and if you have a good
career you should be able to make a
phone call and that same evening have
five million dollars in your bank
account just simply based off of
Goodwill and your reputation you can't
do that now in 30 years you should
probably be able to sell a hundred
thousand dollars a million dollars five
million dollars worth of a product or a
service before you even create it just
because you have so many loyal customers
over the years that understand whatever
you put out is quality so I wanted even
if it's not available yet you can't do
that right now there's businesses in 30
years that will cost you
four million dollars to start and in the
first year they're gonna break even but
within five years of running the company
it'll be a 40 million dollar a year
company but just remember you needed
that four million dollars to start in
the first place so you don't have that
so don't look at what someone else is
doing let's say you're a real estate
agent don't look at what a real estate
agent is doing in their 15th year as
being a real estate agent no look at
what they did when they first started so
pick the right opportunity at the right
time at what I call the correct point
when it comes to your career timing the
next thing is discipline over motivation
listen if you're going to become
successful most of the time you're not
going to be motivated to do it
motivation is kind of like Runners High
when you're running when you're running
a marathon you're only going to get
Runners high for some of it for a very
small portion you're gonna get that
feeling where you're running on clouds
and you've got this intrinsic energy and
all this stuff that's a very small
portion when you lose that feeling of
Runners High what you just give up on
the marathon no you just need to have
discipline you need to lock in and you
need to do it whether you feel like
you're not and that's the way having
this successful career is motivation is
great sometimes you're gonna get it but
it's fleeting you need to rely on
discipline instead the next success
secret of what I've observed and
witnessed from my wealthiest of friends
is they bought A1 assets as early as
they could in their career and they held
on to them a lot of these people have
property in London New York Paris La you
name it and they've had these properties
for 10 20 years and they've held on to
them and it's not just properties I'm
talking license plates I'm talking
hotels and I understand it's going to
take a bit of money to buy these things
so of course you've got to focus on
having a good career first but once you
have a good career buy these A1 assets
which aren't the most exciting
Investments you know you're not going to
make the craziest returns but you're
never going to lose money and it's stuff
that you can have throughout generations
and I know it's not important right now
but later down the line and it's one of
the next points that I will talk about
so in 20 years when you want to buy
something let's say you want to buy a
jet you're not going to be spending 20
million dollars on a jet no you're going
to put four million dollars down in the
other 60 million dollars the bank has
going to give you and when you have
incredible A1 Assets in your portfolio
stuff that isn't the highest returns but
there's basically zero risk the banks
will have absolutely zero issue giving
you money the next success secret is
that if you sleep on a win you're gonna
wake up with a loss and what I mean by
that is just because you won does not
make you a winner winning is a
continuous process I see a lot of people
in their teens in their early 20s and
I'd say this is probably the biggest
reason I'm in the position that I am is
because I made my first million dollars
cash at 18. but a lot of people in that
situation they buy their Lambo or lease
it or whatever they get a nice apartment
and then they're King of the castle
they're a winner and they had their win
and they're happy with that or they go
to bed with a win they hibernate with a
win and then they wake up a few months
later with a loss you need to understand
that it is so much harder to keep it and
multiply it than it is to get it getting
it is one thing so of course celebrate
your wins celebrate the times when you
said you were going to do something and
you stuck to your word but just
understand that if you stay in that
place if you keep revisiting the past
then the future is not going to look
very pretty for you now the next success
secret and I kind of alluded to this
earlier is build good relationships with
the banks from early on and the reason I
say build good relationships with the
banks early on is for a couple reasons
number one as much as I hate banks at
some point you will need them if you do
want to creatively Finance some of your
assets whether you want to creatively
finance a business acquisition you know
you want to buy equity in a new business
you want to start a new business you
name it banks are very useful and the
other thing is when it comes to making a
lot of money I know some of you guys are
literally sitting at home in your mom's
basement and you're going why do I need
to think about or start worrying about
you know me making so much money that I
need good banks on my side that aren't
going to give me troubles yeah listen
maybe this month you're not going to
make good money maybe next year you're
not going to make good money hey maybe
you're not going to make good money for
10 years but they will get to a point if
you keep working that you make enough
money that it raises normal Banks
eyebrows just normal banking eyebrows
and that's where premium banking is a
step above and then eventually you start
getting into some private Banks and then
it's a matter of where do you have your
private banking and stuff like that but
the point is from the age of 14 I
started reading Finance books I started
to understand how the world of banking
and finance works and I didn't need that
yet but at least I was aware and I knew
that hey once I have a lot of money I
need to be able to have good banking on
my side and by the way all of my assets
I don't have uh financing I don't have a
mortgage on any of my properties I don't
owe any Bank any money but it's good to
know that if I need 10 million dollars
by next week I have it there if I need
it it's good to know that when I need to
send a wire for a few million dollars
they don't give me headaches because if
you're dealing with normal banking good
luck they're gonna think you're a
criminal even if you've been in the
cleanest businesses and you have years
and years of track record
it's normal banking they want to make
your life as difficult as humanly
possible so at least if you can just
start thinking about these things from a
young age you don't need to apply it but
I just want to prepare you for it in the
same way I've prepared for it 10 years
ago well before I even made my money the
next success secret is keep your circle
small listen you can have a lot of
acquaintances you can have a lot of
business associates a lot of people can
know who you are but in terms of your
actual Circle the people that you will
tell things to the people that you will
confide in you have to keep that Circle
small because there's only a few select
amount of people that can keep up with
your pace with a pace that you're moving
forward and you're evolving in life
there's only a few select amount of
people that can keep up with it and the
other thing is loose lips sink ships the
more that you tell people things the
more loose ends that you're creating and
the more chances for that to come back
and bite you listen it doesn't matter
what you've done in life whether you've
lived the holiest of holy life or the
most sinful of life people shouldn't
know your private business your private
business should remain private to you
and when you keep your circle small you
know that it's safe whereas you know if
you want to be the person who's buddy
buddy with everyone and as I said be
play be friendly hey Network do whatever
you want to do but I'm talking don't be
the person that meets someone and in the
first or second dinner you know you're
telling them your deepest darkest
secrets and all this stuff because my
rule of things is I will never tell
someone outside of my inner circle you
know my trusted confidence I will never
tell someone something
that I wouldn't want other people to
know so if I tell someone something I
know full well unless they're in that
little small Inner Circle that I have
that they're gonna tell other people and
even if they don't tell other people at
least I mentally prepare myself for it
and that gives me a good filter of what
do I tell people and what do I not so
just remember keep your circle small and
keep your circle solid the next success
secret to talk one percent is radical
responsibility your marriage failed your
fault your business failed your fault
you know you got a knee injury the man
you couldn't uh play tennis for six
months your fault whatever it is it's
your fault because that is the only way
to properly look at your life and
analyze what are the inputs that could
have led to this final outcome you know
whereas if you just blame it on
externals and all this you're not going
to get very far in life the next success
secret is work like your new money but
act like you're old money and have the
values of old money from our early age
all I wanted to do was dress like old
money have financial literacy like old
money have old money principles values
and bear in mind I'm 23. I'm not perfect
I still show aspects to my life and I
still talk about money in a way that
probably you know the old money crowds
would hate but that's also just because
you know I've been uploading YouTube
videos for eight years I talked about
things openly and honestly when I was
broke and I talk about things openly and
honestly now that I've been able to have
a decent amount of financial success in
my life so just remember you want to
have that hunger of new money you know
old money they don't have that same sort
of hunger but what old money has is
wisdom so if you can match up that
hunger that drive that pushes you
forward but then have the wisdom and
always learn from old money then that
will be your secret to not only making a
lot of money but making sure that you
don't lose it once you get it the next
success secret and this may be a little
controversial is that you are not going
to change the world but you can make it
slightly better I'm so sick and tired of
these people who are like I'm Gonna
Change the World you know I'll give you
a perfect example I listen maybe some
people have different opinions I'm just
this is just my opinion Apple did not
the world because here's the thing I
love my iPhone I love my Apple ecosystem
but if Apple didn't exist I guarantee
you I would be more than happy with
Samsung there will be no void missing in
my life there'd be no you know my life
wouldn't be in shatters I would get used
to Samsung very very quickly all this
stuff so as a company realistically
you're not going to change the world but
you can make things slightly better and
that's the beauty of it for me I I just
love people that have things in their
life that don't seem like that big you
know for example a lot of these Japanese
sushi chefs you know you're not changing
anyone's life by sourcing the right Tuna
on the right day and spending 60 years
or 40 years in apprenticeship and
learning and practicing how to make the
right sticky rice and how to sharpen
your knife in the right way and how to
cut the fish at the right angle you're
not changing anyone's life but you are
making the world slightly better because
whatever it is that you're doing however
insignificant it may seem to you just do
it the best that you can and then that's
when the world changes when we all
rather than trying to be this Larger
than Life person of like like I'm Gonna
Change the World that to me that's
just so grandiose and self-absorbed just
realize listen whatever I'm doing I want
to be the best at it and I want to put
out the best service the best product I
want to put a smile on people's face I
don't care if I'm a waiter I want to be
the best waiter out there and you're not
going to change the world by doing that
but you'll make the world a better place
and if we all do that that's how we
change the world the next success secret
is that private victories lead to public
victories and you need to understand
this you need to understand that when
you see someone who gets on their jet or
they drive their Rolls Royce or whatever
it is there were so many private
victories that went into it just
understand the bigger the public Victory
the more private victories that went
into it you know for someone to go out
there and buy a Gucci or Balenciaga
hoodie they probably didn't need to have
that many private victories they
probably didn't need to have that many
years of just sacrificing putting your
head down discipline doing things that
you don't want to do because you have to
do it it really didn't take that many
private victories to create that public
Victory but for someone to buy a 60
million dollar jet you bet your ass
there was so many private victory you
will never comprehend you will never
understand you better ask them when a
boxer wins a boxing match at the highest
level that's cool but you know how many
private victories went into that how
much people don't see so just
understand whatever you want in life the
bigger the public Victory the more
private victories are going to need to
go into it and last and final success
secret of the top one percent is that
after 10 years of doing One Singular
thing it will start to look effortless
and I think sometimes people look at
someone's career or how good someone is
at something and they go I could never
do that they just make it look so
effortless they make it look so easy of
course when you work that hard it starts
to look easy it starts to look elegant
and you really start to have that effect
after 10 years onwards when someone has
been doing something for 10 years plus
it will start to look effortless and
just understand that shouldn't scare you
when you first start that's a part of
their process they had to go through
that process of things being clunky and
them being bad at things and they have
to do it so many years a decade plus and
then it starts to look effortless and
eventually when you find something that
you have respect for do you have
appreciation for and you go okay I'm
going to dedicate my life to becoming
good at this thing even if I wake up
with zero motivation for it or not when
you dedicate your stat eventually you
will start to make it look effortless so
ladies and gentlemen those are 17
success Secrets I have learned from not
only the top one percent but the top
zero zero zero one percent in many
different domains and verticals in life
I feel like this is one of those videos
you really need to re-watch again and
again and again to really let these
lessons sink in and as always I'm
watching you from afar and I'm rooting
for you