just pay more attention in my
[Music]
class it was a business
[Applause]
plan the book is still
[Music]
missing
he
[Music]
knows do you know what Socrates
Alexander the Great Plato Aristotle
Leonardo da Vinci and Marcus Aurelius
all had in common something beyond their
obvious
geniality well if you're like most
people you'll probably say something
along the lines of they were all
historical figures who all achieved
great things which is true or maybe you
said that they're all long gone which is
also definitely true but there's
something else you see although they all
lived hundreds if not even thousands of
years ago the life of every single one
of these individuals is greatly
documented in a few ancient writings
either written by them or their
followers and in those writings they all
left behind one of the greatest gifts
that one could fathom during my research
as I went through these ancient writings
trying to figure out the real secret
origins of education and what formula
they used to create so many Minds back
then I mean Minds that are still
remembered to this day I stumbled upon
something you see I noticed that every
single one of these men shared five very
specific principles that made them the
great figures that they are remembered
as principles that were somewhat common
back then but they were lost somewhere
along the way and today less than 1% of
the population has them and for a very
specific reason the conditioning Factory
is trying to keep you away from finding
out these because they know that those
who possess these five lost traits
they're going to break away from their
social conditioning and stop being a
product of the system and of course they
want to avoid that at all cost but the
truth is buried in these ancient
writings and my goal with this event is
to rescue these five lost long
principles that were once the
foundations of the greatest
breakthroughs Humanity has ever
experienced and this is what I'm about
to give
[Music]
you let's go back to the war that was
set in motion by the execution of
Socrates now you may not be aware of
this war but you can see its battles you
actually see them being fought every
every single day and maybe you even
fight some of these battles yourselves
let me tell you what I'm talking about
I'll give you an example have you
noticed how lately it's kind of becoming
more and more difficult to have a
diversity of opinions today if you say
that men and women are different you're
labeled as a sexist or intolerant and if
you say that we should care about
everyone independent of their race that
somehow makes you a racist you see the
fight for diversity somehow led us to
not have diversity of opinions anymore
and the fight for democracy somehow led
us to suppress free speech an open
debate and the fight for inclusion
created this cancel culture where
certain views are just excluded and I'm
sure you too have experienced this
yourself almost daily and you to have
probably asked yourself how do we get to
this point well it turns out that they
have been preparing the grounds for this
to happen for some decades now but
before I can expand on that you must
first understand this that all of these
battles are a symptom of a much bigger
War that's going on behind the scenes so
what is this war on then it's a war on
truth and their goal push civilization
to stage four conditioning where they
completely control what truth is now
what does that even mean war on Truth
controlling the truth what does that
mean in practice well for you to
understand this we first need to go back
in time back to the real origins of
Education not the education we know of
today I'm talking real education the
education that was responsible for
creating the greatest Outsiders that I
mentioned in the beginning of this video
the likes of Socrates Leonardo da Vinci
Alexander the Great and many more this
this is the real origin of
[Music]
Education it all started in ancient
Greece you see in ancient times the
approach to education was very different
from what it is today the Greeks really
cemented their name in history by
providing the foundations for what would
later be taught in Western universities
throughout an entire Millennium up until
the Rena Rance in the 1300s and it was
all based on one principle the search
for truth they believe that freedom and
Truth were the ultimate outcomes an
individual could seek and pursue and in
order for an individual to pursue such
freedoms they'd have to become critical
thinkers meaning they needed to be
capable of analyzing the world around
them and arriving at a clear
understanding of what the truth really
is and they even had a Latin phrase
that's still popular to this day to
describe this search for truth qued East
very
which means what is truth now why is
this so important why was The Pursuit Of
Truth such a fundamental concept for the
ancient Greeks well think about it right
and wrong good and evil your values your
objectives your culture all of these are
anchored to the understanding you have
about what truth is what you consider to
be right is what another person
considers to be wrong why because your
interpretation of Truth is different and
as a result your conclusions about the
world around you are different as well
well so your beliefs are different and
so are your values which in turn opens
up a series of interesting questions for
example how can you tell who is right
you or the other person who has an
opposing view how can you tell which
truth is the actual truth how can you
know your truth is factual have you ever
thought about why you believe the things
you believe and why you see them as
truth are there logical reasons based on
Cold Heart facts that support your view
of what is the truth and those are
questions that you probably rarely ask
yourself and there's a reason why
because this is how you get to the truth
and the ones above you they don't want
you to know about the truth they want
you to be a product of the system
someone who does what they're told and
nothing more and in order for you to do
that you can't find out the real truth
because if you did you wouldn't do what
they tell you you would question them
you wouldn't comply you would follow
different paths so the bottom line is
they don't don't want you to get to the
truth and this is exactly how they keep
you indoctrinated a product of the
system so f for the first time in your
life you truly want to get to the truth
and Peak into what the way to Freedom
not indoctrination actually looks like
then listen closely I'm not going to
give you a peek behind the curtains
instead we'll look to ancient texts
because what I just showed you is the
first of five principles hidden in the
ancient pages that have been written
over decades and centuries ago by the
greatest Minds that have stepped into
this world and what I'm about to show
you are the other four principles that
created some of the brightest and most
successful individuals in the history of
mankind people who succeeded outside of
the traditional realm or formal path
which they were expected to follow by
the establishment standards and that's
why I call them The Outsiders because
they were able to unwire all the social
conditioning that had been fed by the
conditioning Factory and to succeed
outside of the system they were able to
forge their own path in a world which
did everything to keep them at Bay and
it even cost some of them their life
like Socrates these men were Relentless
in their pursuit of freedom and if you
adopt their principles you can be too
you see by becoming an outsider you are
able to unlock something that less than
1% of the world's population has today
financial location and time freedom and
once you combine these five forgotten
principles you too will be able to
become an outsider so to recap the first
principle of the outsider is you must
establish what truth means for you or in
other words you need to find out what
truth you will Orient Yourself by
because the truth that you choose to
subscribe to will determine your success
listen if you choose to believe that
you're destined for failure if that's
your truth then you will be but the
opposite is true as well that's why it's
so important to establish what truth you
will Orient Yourself by what what truth
actually means for
you now ancient Greece cemented its name
in history not only for being one of the
first civilizations to pursue the idea
of truth but because they developed a
method to do so you see getting to the
truth is rarely easy especially because
you know truth can be such a loose
concept I mean after all two people can
recount the exact same situation in two
vastly different ways now is one more
true than the other or is either recount
true at all so the first person to truly
develop a method to get to the root of
what truth is was our friend Socrates
and the really interesting part of his
character is that he genuinely believed
in his own ignorance and this is exactly
how he developed a method to find out
what truth means how he used to
literally walk the street of Athens and
engage in conversations with people from
all walks of life I'm talking Craftsmen
Artisans vendors poets politicians young
Athen iions and all he'd do was ask them
questions questions about their beliefs
their philosophies and where their
beliefs came from and basically what he
tried to do was to help others recognize
their own ignorance as the first step
towards wisdom you see he believed that
by questioning and examining beliefs
critically one could actually move
closer to the truth he claimed to have
no wisdom of his own and often described
his role as that of a midwife helping
others give birth to their own
understanding now as he ate Ed Socrates
method and persistent questioning of
athens's values as well as influential
figures well that made him many enemies
and that series of questioning was what
came to be known as the Socratic method
this method allows you to get to the
real Foundation of your beliefs about a
subject do you want to know what the
method looks like in practice well you
already know it I mean just think back
to the series of questions I asked you a
few minutes ago the ones about the
opposing interpretations of truths that
is the Socratic method the exact same
one we used in the mission of episode 1
I've already taught you the Socratic
method in practice without you even
knowing it and let me tell you something
that is probably more than the modern
education system has ever taught you
about how to truly become a critical
thinker asking why you believe something
until you truly get to the root of your
beliefs and the second principle of the
outsider is to evaluate your current
beliefs and figure out where your
limiting beliefs come from remember what
I told you in episode one it does
doesn't matter how hard you work or how
many different new Ventures you try you
will keep failing until you unwire the
conditioning that makes you a product of
the system and it's only after you
unwire all of it that you can truly
succeed and this is exactly what we're
getting to here so in order for you to
evaluate your current beliefs and really
understand where they're coming from
just go through the same questioning
process using the Socratic method ask
yourself what are the limiting beliefs
you currently have that are holding you
back maybe you think you can't succeed
outside the the system maybe you think
no one can or perhaps you think you need
some secret knowledge to find this
success now think about it why do you
believe such thing is it because you
deeply researched and reflected on that
topic to get to such conclusion or maybe
it's because you've been conditioned to
believe it whether that be from your
parents your teachers or even your
friends then keep asking more questions
until you get to the bottom of your
beliefs to find out if they're rooted in
truth or they're rooted in and
conditioning did this entire sequence of
questions lead you to any conclusions
did it change any of your beliefs did
you realize anything new did you
actually make a change or is everything
just the same it is only through this
process that you are going to be able to
truly identify your limiting beliefs
that are a result from all the
conditioning the system has fed you your
entire life and it's only once you
identify these core limiting beliefs
that you can unwire them for good so
that you're finally ready to achieve
success this is the Socratic method of
getting to the truth now you want to
know the most interesting part about all
of this back in the day Socrates used
reason to discover and understand how
the world works and how to get to the
truth today the system aims to destroy
your reasoning because they don't want
you to find out how the world truly
works this is how they keep you a
product of the system but actually it's
not just today the as you already know
Socrates was executed and his execution
is often cited as a black stain on
Athenian democracy and used as a case
study of the tyranny of the State
against those who dare to challenge it
now what did he get executed for
corrupting the youth it was alleged that
he influenced the young men of Athens to
question and challenge traditional
values and beliefs I mean how big of a
crime is that right his method of
questioning everything including the
basis of Athenian traditions and beliefs
well that irritated many of the city's
leaders and thinkers he used to question
everything and everyone and some of the
most famous interactions were with the
prominent political figures of his time
you see by questioning them Socrates
often exposed that many of these
influential figures well they couldn't
adequately Define or understand the
virtues that they claimed to possess and
as you know by this point the last thing
that the rulers want you to do is
question the traditional values and
beliefs and above
else question them much less encourage
an entire generation of young people to
do the same and socrates's execution was
the starting point of the war that we're
still fighting to this day the war on
truth so what I want to do now is
exactly what Socrates did back then to
encourage the millions of people
watching this event I want you to
question everything because this very
same thing is happening today people who
encourage the young generations to think
for themselves and ask why certain
traditional systems and institutions
operate the way that they do they too
are getting digitally executed or
cancelled if you prefer and it is our
duty to fight against it so now it's
your turn to
[Music]
question 399 BC as you've seen one of
the most pivotal days on the war on took
place in that year socrates's trial I
mean his trial remains one of the most
famous judicial verdicts in history the
trial took place in a large Open Air
Hillside the pcks in the presence of a
jury consisting of 500 male citizens as
well as hundreds of citizens who were
there to watch one thing you may not
know is that one of those citizens
present was socrates's main Prodigy at
the time someone who you probably have
heard of before his name
Plato you see Plato was a student of
Socrates for almost 10 years at that
point he was introduced to the world of
philosophy through Socrates and was
deeply influenced by his method of
questioning you know the one I just
taught you Socrates was his mentor and
that day was the day that Plato's World
fell apart I mean really imagine this
Plato stood there and he witnessed his
mentor sticking to what he believed in
even in the face of death all because
Socrates had urged Athenians to think
critically about their beliefs and
values what a crime and very
understandably Plato was deeply affected
by the Athenian democracy's decision to
put his mentor to death I mean
everything he admired about Athens and
its political system was also killed on
that day which led him to do something
that changed the world as we know it
forever you see that was the end of
Socrates but that was the start of
something so much bigger so after the
tra atic experience of witnessing his
beloved Mentor be sentenced to death
Plato began to develop his ideas about
the nature of Injustice the role of the
individual within the state and the idea
of the good he went deep into physics
ethics psychology and education and this
ended up leading him to do something
that is still remembered to the state
the foundation of the academy in Athens
which would later be considered the
Western world's first University and
this really marked the real origin of
the education system and I'd say that is
what ignited the war for the truth I'd
say the biggest thing to notice here is
how the original education system
differed from the modern day education
system because it wasn't an education
system that came from the government it
was an education system that came from
the people it derived from their
frustrations towards the system now you
might be wondering but why is that so
important because it had your interests
in mind not the government's interests
and that's why its objective was to get
people to pursue the truth so that they
could become Outsiders themselves and
Achieve Freedom outside of the system
now compare that to the Prussian
schooling system from the 1700s the same
one that we still use to this day now as
you saw in the first episode education
is led by the government and if it's led
by the government whose interests do
they have in mind your interests or
their interests and this is where the
shift in power happened along the way
it's when education stopped being
educating yourself for your own
self-interest and started to be
educating yourself for the interests of
the ones in charge and today all
education is led by the government even
private institutions they still have to
follow a strict curriculum that is
imposed by the government and this is
really how they create an illusion of
choice for you oh you can choose this
course or this University or this degree
this is how they trick you because at
the end of the day if their education is
coming from the government it is all
different paths that lead to the same
destination which is you being a product
of the system and that is why we steered
away from education being based on the
pursuit of the truth because they don't
want you to know the truth now have you
ever heard the saying that history
repeats itself well it turns out that
Plato 2 became a mentor himself to
another very bright mind of the human
race which you probably have heard about
as well his name was Aristotle and
Aristotle 2 cre his own School the
lysium and it's interesting to note that
the search for truth was so ingrained in
the roots of their core values that each
generation created their own version of
the truth I mean it started with
Socrates and his whole concept that he
knew nothing and then Plato died deeper
into metaphysics which he considered to
be his truth and diverged from the
original ideas of his mentor he believed
that true knowledge can only be grasped
through reason and intellect and that
the true reality lies in the realm of
the ideas which exists beyond the
physical world Aristotle on the other
hand well he believed that knowledge
starts from the material world and he
really emphasized observation
classification and Analysis really
laying the groundwork for Empirical
research and the scientific method and
now we fast forward a few years here and
get to 343 BCE Aristotle was now one of
the most respected intellectuals of his
age and he received an invitation you
see King Philip II from Macedonia wanted
Aristotle to Mentor his son someone who
you most likely have heard about before
as well someone who later in his 20s
went on to conquer more cities more
countries and more territories than any
other man or Army had ever done before
him his name was Alexander but you
probably know him as Alexander the Great
now at the time King Philip II well he
already had the choice of sending his
son to school in Macedonia so why did he
choose to appoint someone as his son's
Mentor instead because he wanted to
provide an Elite Education for the
future heir to his throne and he knew
that the best way to do this was by
appointing a successful renowned
individual as the mentor for his son so
I told you this entire story to get to
this point which is do you see a trend
here Socrates Plato Aristotle Alexander
the Great you kind of notice something
here you know did they have something in
common well for one they were all
independent critical thinkers despite
the Deep influence of their mentors they
all diverged from the initial
philosophies that they were taught and
why is that because they were taught to
be critical thinkers first they put the
search for their own truth above
everything else and that as you know is
the first principle of the outsider
second I mean have you ever asked
yourself how come there were so many
Geniuses and incredible individuals back
then so why is that not the case anymore
nowadays it's because they all mentored
each other it's not as if they just
became great by themselves they all had
a great mind that taught them the ways
and forged their greatness it's very
simple greatness creates greatness I
mean history is super confusing so you
hear all of these names and you just
think oh my they were all Geniuses back
then thinking that they were all
separate people but no they were all
intimately connected I mean they were
all learning from each other it's not as
if these Geniuses these Outsiders were
just created out of thin air they were
created in part by the ones who mentored
them you see the way that education
worked back then was that you as a
father would entrust your child's
education to a mentor that you
personally considered wise and this
Mentor would teach the children what he
considered essential for them to become
wise citizens and critical thinkers
themselves and even after the the Romans
conquered Greece wealthy Roman families
would still employ educated Greek
intellectuals to Mentor their children I
mean think about it why would they let
their own War enemies Mentor their
children because they knew that having a
successful Mentor was not one of the
ways to make your child successful it
was the only way and this is the third
principle of the outsider have a mentor
because history shows us that's the
greatest way to ensure you'll achieve
success u in life and that's why every
single one of The Outsiders I mentioned
throughout this video had
mentors listen at the end of the day we
all want the same thing freedom to be
able to do whatever we want with
whomever we want now for you that might
mean to be able to wake up one day and
gather all of your best friends for a
surprise trip to the Swiss Alps in your
cozy Chalet to enjoy a week of skiing or
you you want to call the world your home
and you want to switch places every few
months a very tranquil Japanese zen
garden home in kiyoto a nice Chic
apartment in New York's upper east side
and a quaint Cottage in New Zealand's
Countryside or maybe all you want to do
is hire the world's best personal
trainers and nutritionists to get you in
the best shape of your life all while
enjoying gourmet meals tailored to your
pallet or maybe you decide to buy a
Vineyard in Tuscany and spend your days
tasting wines and enjoying the Italian
sun or you fund the building of a school
in a remote country like I personally
started doing in Nepal in 2019 ensuring
education for generations to come listen
whatever that experience may be for you
we all have different aspirations and
goals in life at the end of the day I
call it having financial location and
time freedom and today the reality is
that less than 1% of the world's
population have managed to achieve these
three types of freedom and if you want
to be part of this 1% yourself you need
to ask yourself how do you become truly
free is what you're doing today going to
lead you to becoming truly free if not
why are you doing it then maybe it's
something temporary maybe it's the only
option you currently have and that's
totally fine listen if you're not yet in
a path that will take you to True
Freedom it's not your fault as you
already know at this point the
conditioning Factory has conditioned you
to be there now the problem is when you
don't ask these questions when you never
realize why you're doing what you're
doing in the first place and if having
these three types of freedom is
something that you aspire to have you
have to ask yourself then what are the
things that I need to learn in order to
achieve such Freedom you see the reason
the ancient Greeks started to study
science philosophy mathematics was not
because they wanted to be mathematicians
or philosophers but rather because they
considered those as necessary
characteristics to make you a critical
thinker and as a a consequence make you
pursue and Achieve true Freedom
achieving true Freedom was always the
ultimate goal of Education ever since
ancient Greece now from the moment that
the system tells you what you need to
study this freedom is restrained you see
the first idea of a school curriculum
was developed during the Middle Ages
based on a lot the same principles that
they had in ancient Greece they called
it liberal arts the curriculum that they
developed back then which was taught in
Western universities that developed
civilization throughout an entire
Millennium up until the Renaissance and
the goal of it was pretty simple teach
people a group of subjects that would
allow them to achieve spiritual and
intellectual freedom and the freedoms
were divided into three inferior and
four Superior disciplines the inferior
ones also known as the Trivium were
grammar to decode the world we live in
and communicate through words dialectic
to compare different perceptions and
evolve in the search for truth rethoric
to express our observations and
conclusions in a persuasive Manner and
the superior ones also known as the
quadrum and these were arithmetic to
quantify the world we know geometry to
put quantities into space music to fit
the numbers in time and astronomy to
understand the influence of the stars in
space you see they developed a
curriculum that when followed would
create individuals who could pursue and
Achieve Freedom so if you two want to
become free what do you need you need
need to follow a curriculum and
obviously not the same curriculum that
they followed back then because times
have changed a lot and so have the means
through which you achieve freedom but
you need to follow a curriculum that is
based on the same principles and I know
what you're going to say now oh eeman
but there's no such thing as following a
curriculum and becoming free and that's
true the curriculum itself won't make
you free but it will instill in you all
the knowledge you need to have about
yourself and the world you live in in
order for you to be able to pursue
freedom and here's the thing if you
think that there's no such thing as a
curriculum that you're going to follow
and that will make you free just think
about this in the 1700s the prussians
created a curriculum that was able to
First indoctrinate entire generations to
obey comply and believe what they were
told without ever even questioning them
then they use that same curriculum to
create a legion of mindless obedient
Factory workers to work in Rockefeller
oil industry then they use that same
curriculum to get millions of people to
happily get hundreds of thousands of
dollars in debt just to get a useless
piece of paper that doesn't even
guarantee them any type of work or
income this is how they got ahead in the
war on truth so trust me that's the
power of following the right curriculum
I mean really think about it which one
do you think is harder to accomplish to
completely remove the Free Will of
entire ire Generations around the world
creating Legions of mindless obedient
Factory workers and getting them to pay
hundreds of thousands of dollars for the
privilege to do so or getting someone to
make $10,000 a month listen the truth is
as long as you follow the right
curriculum you can achieve whatever you
want whether that's for your best
interest or someone else's interest and
that is the fourth principle of the
outsider find out what curriculum will
set you free and I mean really find out
exactly what you need to be able to do
how you need to think and what you need
to do in order to be free analyze the
world around you look to the successful
people of our time how did they get
there and to make that easier for you in
episode 3 I'm going to reveal exactly
how I crafted the curriculum that Set Me
Free as well as tens of thousands of
others now interestingly enough the
fifth and last principle of the outsider
doesn't come from ancient Greece but
from their biggest Rivals the Spartans
you see around the same time that all of
this was happening in ancient Greece a
guy named lerus of Sparta reinvented the
Spartan Education and Training System he
called it the ago this was the system
that led the Spartans to dominate
everyone who they met in the battlefield
and allowed them to remain undefeated
for over 150 years and this entire
system was based on one principle that
healthy disciplined able-bodied
individuals are the key to a successful
and functional society and here's how
the system worked one man was chosen to
be in charge of the boys as their ponis
as they called it their mentor and it
was his job to make sure that the
Spartans became loyal resourceful
disciplined and accustomed to extensive
physical activity and the Spartans also
understood that if they wanted their
citizens to become the most successful
and unbeatable individuals there was
only one way to achieve that by having
mentors guiding the way for their entire
generation that's why being aonomus was
considered an incredibly important role
for the Spartans because at the end of
the day they were responsible for
bringing up the next generation of
Spartans that's why this position was
only open to those who were eligible for
election to the highest offices you see
they wouldn't choose anyone to be the
mentors of their next Generation they
would only choose their most talented
Spartan individual ual to take this role
because they knew that only greatness
can create greatness so if they were to
have any mediocre citizens to be the
mentor of their next Generation Well in
that case what would their next
Generation turn out to become a
generation of mediocre Spartans they
understood that the level of success an
individual achieves is directly related
to how successful the people mentoring
them are now at this point as an
outsider in developing yourself you
already understand this principle but
that's not why I brought of the Spartans
here you see the system that Sparta
created had another very interesting
concept the concept of enduring through
intense hardship and the second step of
the ago system was all about turning
students into individuals who can endure
hardship they would only give students
one cloak for the entire year and made
them walk Barefoot to strengthen their
feet you see they believe that if their
feet were properly accustomed they could
run faster and jump higher than anyone
in Footwear they were also taught on how
to not fight with weapons and March in
full silence and the mentors would
ensure that they were always hungry to
some degree as well why to put them into
a Perpetual state of discomfort because
discomfort breeds discipline and
discipline forges greatness it was all
about being a strong and disciplined
individual a disciplined individual who
can resist the Temptations that life
throws their way and live a life of
delayed gratification instead of instant
gratification and has an extremely high
likeliness of becoming successful and
listen history proved this not only with
the Spartans but with so many different
cultures and societies that operated
under this same principle and that is
why this is the fifth principle of the
outsider seek intense hardship to forge
discipline and self-control because it
is only through intense hardship that
you will be able to create the best and
most successful version of yourself and
on episode 3 I will show you the the
exact protocol I use to ensure that I
develop and maintain the highest levels
of discipline and self-control that's
needed for me to be able to properly
manage my portfolio of eight and multi-a
figure companies now the ago system was
focused specifically on young adults why
because they saw the young adults of
Sparta as the city's greatest assets and
they were the ones that led Sparta to
150 years without defeats and I know
that more than likely you are a young
adult yourself so truly understand that
these are your greatest years the years
that will either make you successful or
ENT trap you into mediocrity for the
rest of your life so please make sure
you make the most out of them because
your time is
limited and all of this brings us back
to today and it begs the question aren't
those principles outdated and the answer
is today they're actually more relevant
than ever they're not only Timeless
principles they're the principles that
are most needed in today's world and the
ones who apply them in their lives will
experience the same levels of success
that The Outsiders who applied them back
in the days did but you don't have much
time left to apply them in fact this
might even be your last chance and if
that sounds very intense or over
dramatic let me tell you why we are one
step away from the war on Truth taking
its final form don't get it twisted our
side is losing and we're only a few
chess moves away from the worst possible
outcome which is stage 4 conditioning
you'll remember that stage four
conditioning is what the conditioning
Factory has been aiming for this whole
time stage four conditioning is when
they have complete control over the
truth and you are stripped of all
freedom and all Choice and then it won't
matter if you find out what your truth
is because they will completely control
the truth it doesn't matter if you
decide to follow a curriculum that that
has the potential of setting you free at
Freedom is not a thing anymore and the
conditioning Factory is working at Full
Steam to make that happen now you might
think that this dystopia is a product of
Science Fiction that something like this
would never happen in real life I mean
surely the government can't have total
control of the truth but they can and
it's already happening not once not
twice but many times and it's about to
happen again I mean just think about how
every dictator runs their country
is through stage four conditioning and
soon this dystopia may become reality in
the west communist China and these other
regimes weren't simply based on Marxism
they were also authoritarian States and
the first step towards authoritarianism
is limiting Free Speech which is exactly
what we're seeing today according to a
recent survey conducted by the KO
Institute over 60% of people today say
that they are afraid of saying what they
believe because of the current political
climate does that look like free speech
to you if majority of people are not
comfortable in saying what they believe
to be true and this is how it all
relates back to what we're living today
right now you see the new philosophy
that is sweeping across our society has
its roots deeply fastened in Marxist
ideology it's the new wave of wokeism
that you see everywhere and this is
exactly what led us here because in
efforts of creating a culture of
inclusion they have created a culture of
intolerance the very thing that all of
these groups swear to fight against
diversity of thought has been replaced
by exclusion of ideas and freedom of
speech has eroded entirely and if you
don't conform if you don't say the right
thing you will fail that class or you
will be fired and this is the essence of
cancel culture it is a world based on
fear no different from communist China
fear is the control mechanism and it's
enforced by Wall Street the universities
and the cult-like followers of these
ideologies because if you don't conform
you will be ostracized and once you
cross that line there's no going back
long story short it might look like a
far-fetched example but know that today
if you live in a country like USA Canada
Australia Germany UK or any other
American or European country in fact we
really are all one conditioning stage
away from a country like China we are
already in stage three and making leap
towards stage 4 conditioning and there
is only one thing that can stop that
from happening the truth education was
originally based on finding the truth
Aristotle Plato Marcus aelius they all
lived in a system where the search for
truth and thus Freedom was the number
one goal the problem is somewhere along
the journey there was a shift in powers
and the ones who got to power they
stopped caring about the interest of
their people and they started to put
their self-interest first they didn't
care if that meant destroying the very
principles that produce citizens that
push Society forward because that's not
what their goal was their goal was
simple to grow and perpetuate their
power and control and they figured
something critical having their
population know the truth was the
greatest risk to their power because if
the population was able to think for
themselves and figure out what the truth
is well then they wouldn't be able to
lie and manipulate people and that is
how they plan to impose stage 4
conditioning upon us where you won't
even be able to control your own truth
anymore because you won't have choices
on the other hand if we manage to take
back control over the truth and get it
to as many people as possible we will
experience the great rescue where the
principles that once created the
greatest Minds that have ever stepped in
this world will be brought back to life
and with it we'll get back to the
origins of education education from the
people to the people with your own
interest in mind instead of the
government's hidden interests and it all
depends on us they were fighting the
same war and followed the book on how to
win it so much must we we have the
principles laid out by the greatest
Outsiders that have come before us so
now it's our turn to become Outsiders
ourselves by rescuing the same five
principles and adopting them into our
own lives I have given you the five lost
principles to become free and Achieve
success in whatever you do and on
episode 3 I will show you exactly how I
rescued these principles myself and
implemented them in my own personal life
which ultimately led me to the success
that I have today and how you you too
can rescue them in your life so if
becoming a top 1% man is something that
you aspire to what I need you to do is
to turn on the alarm Bell for the
premiere of the third episode by
clicking the link in the pin comment
it's going to go live on Monday at 5:00
p.m. UK time in my opinion this will be
the best video of the entire series
because it will show in practice what it
takes to become an outsider revealing
exactly how I did it until then I have
one mission for you these are our five
lost principles number one establish
what truth means for you the second
evaluate your current beliefs and figure
out where your limiting beliefs come
from number three have a mentor number
four figure out what curriculum will set
you free and number five seek intense
hardship to forge discipline and
self-control we already tackled how to
find your truth and establish your
beliefs so what I want you to do now is
to think about the third principle think
about this Who currently is your mentor
whether you want it or not you are
always learning from someone and your
success will always be limited by the
level of success from who you're
learning from so who are you currently
learning from do you even have a mentor
and if not even Plato Aristotle and
Alexander the Great needed mentors what
makes you think that you don't need one
and is your current Mentor going to lead
you to the level of Freedom you aspired
to get to or do you need a new one so
with all of that being said I'll see you
on
Monday