listen to me very closely because you
have two choices when it comes to AI you
can either adopt it or you can get left
behind but here's the problem with all
the news coming out about AI seemingly
every new AI will be the next big thing
that will take everyone to the next
level but that's simply not true here's
the reality of the situation most of the
AI tools that everyone swears by will
not help you in any meaningful way I
mean sure they're cool they're nice to
have but besides that they're not really
gonna help you now
here's what I mean an AI tool should
either make you more money or it should
save you more time AI tools should make
your workflow seamless not add
complexity to them so in today's video
I'm going to give you the seven AI Tools
in order to do that now the first AI
tools that have the potential to make
you lots of money and save you lots of
time are 10 web.io and durable.co now
back in the day creating a website
required a lot of skills and training I
mean you need to be proficient in
several coding languages and you also
had to design everything and then you
needed to write each piece of code
manually and only then would you be able
to actually fill in a page with your
copy I mean this entire process could
take weeks sometimes even months
depending on the complexity of the
website it was a long arduous and most
importantly expensive process and in the
late 90s even the most basic website
could cost upwards of twenty thousand
dollars then came tools like WordPress
and later Wix and Shop Shopify and these
tools drastically brought costs down and
all of a sudden most people could build
at least a very basic website but even
since these came out in the 2000s one
problem has still remained time no
matter how you put it building a good
website however simple will still take a
long time I mean sure nowadays you don't
have to code everything yourself you can
kind of just put in whatever you want
into a website builder but even then it
still takes time it takes time to get
the design right it takes time to write
the copy it even takes time to learn how
to use the website Builders themselves
so much so that agencies and contractors
will offer to do it for you and let's be
honest lots of the custom websites are
actually just slightly improved versions
of basic Wix templates so that's really
all to say that building websites isn't
easy and it isn't quick and that's
really where AI comes into the picture
with tools like 10 web.io and durable
you can use AI to build your entire
website for you and I will design it
build it write copy and even source and
insert the imagery and in a matter of
minutes you can go from having no
website to having a fully functioning
and aesthetically pleasing website all
you need to do is give AI some basic
information and that's it a few minutes
answering prompts if that and you'll
also be able to take advantage of
features like built-in SEO and AI
Recreation AI Recreation allows you to
feed the AI websites you like and it can
recreate similar websites for you now of
course once made you can edit whatever
you want and even have the tool
regenerate the site until it's to your
Perfection and your liking so you can
either use these AI Tools in your own
business or you can even start
businesses around them you see tons of
people are paying Freelancers a few
hundred dollars to make really basic
websites and with these tools you can
blow those Freelancers out of the water
in a matter of minutes and even command
higher prices while doing so these are
perfect examples of how AI tools can
both save time and make you money now
over the years our attention span has
gone in shorter and shorter and creators
have to grab attention faster and faster
and that eventually led to our current
reality where short form content is King
now there's multiple ways to go about
short form and I would know because over
the last year I've had 20 full-time
editors full full-time strictly doing
short form content for me now obviously
that's super expensive we have a full
department for it we have a department
lead and it's simply not an option for
most people and that's where a tool is
like Opus clip become extremely useful
you see Opus clip is able to take any
long-form video and with one click turn
your long form content into short form
content now the best part about this
tool is that the AI is able to find the
best hooks in the video and piece them
together with the relevant highlights to
pretty much cut out all of the boring
stuff and that means that your chances
of virality are much much higher and the
AI copilot also allows you to clip parts
of a video based on keywords now this is
easily one of the highest Roi tools on
this list especially considering how
prevalent short form content is and you
know as well as I the short form is not
going anywhere tools like Opus clip can
not only save you time in editing and
money in hiring but you can also build a
business around it of course by now the
industry is no stranger to short form
agencies but just because there are
plenty of them doesn't mean that they no
longer work that means that tools like
Opus can actually make you tons and tons
of money and attract millions and
millions of eyeballs now the next AI
tool helps you save time and actually
simplifies your workflow using chat gbt
writer now chat GPT writer is so simple
yet such a no-brainer and here's why
you'll remember that when chat gbt first
became the Talk of the Town one of the
Prime use cases for AI was to do simple
writing tasks but there's one slight
problem by the time that you get an
email open chat gbt copy and paste the
email write the prompt to read and reply
to email you know once you set up all
the Fundamentals by that time frame it
probably would have been quicker to just
reply email yourself and that's where
chat gbt writer comes in it's a simple
chat GPT based Chrome extension that
alleviates all of that friction with
using AI to reply to emails it's
incredibly simple yet very effective in
saving time in a long
now next I want to talk about tidio now
tidio's ai lero has the power to either
assist or entirely replace your support
team and doing all that whilst boosting
sales on your website and obviously this
means that you either save money by
hiring less staff or make more money by
providing a better customer experience
and both of those lead to the same
outcome which is more net income in your
pocket now tidio ai is essentially an AI
powered chat bot that can do two things
it either replaces lengthy frequently
asked questions and answers customers
questions in a matter of seconds so that
means that you can easily increase your
site's conversion rates by making the
customer Journey so much more seamless
because listen instead of clogging the
website with tons of frequently asked
questions and still having loads of
questions unanswered you can now feed
all of that information into AI which
can then answer all of your customers
queries the AI can also answer more
advanced queries like order fulfillment
or restocks by tapping into the database
now the second thing the AI allows is
for human customer support team to work
faster and better you see here's the
thing tidio is a text-based AI which
means it can take your support agents
quick and rough replies and turn them
into full sentences that are on par with
your company's branding but if your
customer asks a question that's beyond
the scope of the ai's knowledge base
then it will automatically refer them to
a human agent now here's the interesting
part lero can answer 70 of your
customers questions that means that your
support system can service more people
in less time and as I said the result is
happier customers and ultimately more
sales so the next AI tool will be useful
for just about anyone and have the
potential to save tons of time now have
you ever read through a seemingly
endless contract or some other lengthy
document now maybe you have to do some
reading for a class or maybe you need to
read some other brief or report for work
well well if you've ever been in a
situation where you have to read a long
document then doc you ask can save you a
ton of time because with Doc you ask you
no longer need to read those long
arduous documents you see there are
plenty of tools that summarize text chat
gbt can even do that but the issue with
the summaries is that they're only that
summaries that means that you will
inevitably miss important fine details
but if you know what to look for well
then you can use a doc you ask because
docu ask takes any document and analyzes
it so you can simply ask questions about
it in a chat box listen here's the thing
extracting information from documents
literally could not be easier so you no
longer need to spend hours and hours
scouring through documents you can
simply use AI now the next AI is one
that I've mentioned in a previous video
but it may just be the most useful AI on
this list and that's Microsoft's
co-pilot copilot directly complements
Microsoft's entire Suite of products
that means it's a able to do everything
from analyzing Excel spreadsheets to
making full-blown PowerPoints I mean
copilot can even transcribe notes during
a Microsoft team meeting and provide you
with a summary of the key points and
action items and even execute on the
actions itself so let's say one of those
action items was to make a presentation
copilot is able to create a tailor-made
presentation to your desired branding
guidelines I mean we've all made a
PowerPoint presentation before that
alone could literally save you hours
copilot also knows your calendar and
therefore can prepare you for upcoming
meetings it can even generate reports
and other word documents based on
previous work and of course it can also
reply to all of your emails for you
copilot is one of the best examples of
AI making your workflow more seamless
and more efficient it's an AI tool that
anyone can take advantage of regardless
of their occupation and especially if
you ever use one of Microsoft's products
well then copilot will be useful to you
whether you need to make a pitch deck
for your clients or analyze last
quarter's profitability co-pilot can
help the last tool I want to talk about
is Adobe Firefly because Adobe Firefly
is one of the craziest AI tools yet you
see most of the other tools on this list
simply save you time or money by doing
tasks for you for example 10 web and
durable make websites for you tidio
answers your customers questions and
they basically give you leverage
Leverage is really what makes AI so
powerful to begin with you see prior to
AI you'd have to spend hours on a task
or spend money to hire someone to spend
hours on that exact task now well now
you essentially have an employee for a
fraction of the cost but Adobe Firefly
doesn't fall under that same
umbrella you see Adobe Firefly actually
allows you to do things that otherwise
would never have been possible and in
the process of that this AI is
incredibly valuable not only can you
make it make your work easier but you
can also make it a hundred times better
which of course will make you more money
so let me explain how it works Firefly
is a generative AI powered content
creation tool that means it can simply
create things so let's look at three
examples and how it can help you fire
fly can create realistic images from
detailed text and this is incredibly
useful if you need any sort of product
photography or any other scenario where
you need to depict something now
normally you need a whole team of
graphic designers and artists whereas
now you can simply ask the AI to do it
for you and that means you're able to
elevate your work drastically without
elevating your costs the second thing is
Firefly has something called generative
fill and that means that it can either
draw in or erase objects in a photo so
if you want to wear a different outfit
in a certain photo this AI can do that
for you it can do things that would
otherwise be impossible or would have
taken a Photoshop expert to do even then
Firefly does in a way that looks
completely natural it can also turn your
sketches into photorealistic images and
so much more so if you work with any
sort of content creation Firefly will be
a must-have tool both for easy fixes and
for exploring completely new ideas and
soon Firefly will even be able to
generate images from 3D elements now
here's the bottom line This AI
Revolution we're in is no different from
any other technological Revolution and
as with any boom there will be an
inevitable bust the key here is to be
able to discern what's to stay and what
isn't and then to capitalize on the
trends that are here to stay and now
that you have these seven tools to help
you make money and save time all you
need to do is get to work and as always
I'll be watching from afar
and I'm rooting for you