bro I literally follow all your like
content you're literally like everything
I've done is because small little
donations I hope you don't take it the
wrong way but thank you for uh
[Applause]
you can explain why we took the
chocolate we took the chopper because I
don't want to sit in the car for four
hours
and yeah we're here in Bolton actually
that's what we're going we're seeing uh
represent we're gonna go see my buddy
George who's one of the Heaton Brothers
we're gonna take a tour of the HQ and
then he's gonna run me through a workout
which I'm not looking forward to this
dude's [ __ ] unit and the student is a
beast and then after that we're gonna
have a quick little lunch
about it you're flying from London yeah
yeah nice to helicopter yeah four hour
drive I was like yeah it's not bad come
on I'll show you around anyway but this
is wild so how many people do you have
in here uh now we're on 68 we should be
at uh by the end of the year so 68
people in here yeah
[Music]
just in this area
my favorite speaker
there's only three companies on there
that would ever be response bye Laura
piano
Laura friada represent with you guys of
course I've bought some of the other
stuff and I like your guys jeans yeah I
love all the trainers and stuff like
that but the 247 is like where it's at
for me because I just love the
Simplicity of it I know a lot of other
people want to wear stuff that's just
very minimal if if not if even no
branding the stuff that fits nice yeah
it's funny because like what sells
really well in 247 is the Big Brand and
stuff yeah which is kind of like
annoying but it is what it is pants are
by far my favorite the shorts the first
one is yeah straws yeah the two in one
[ __ ] love those basically loves all
the stuff that doesn't sell
is that really all the stuff yeah yeah
like the stuff that sells is like the
big logo heavy stuff because people want
to feel like they're part of the club
yeah
[ __ ] up the world excuse me but is that
your girl if she tell that's a good
referral I know after we leave today and
you've seen all this yeah
but you want what you can't have right
or what you think you can't have like
I'd love to not have an office so I can
go anywhere in the world yeah like I'm
in these four walls five six days a week
that's good that's that's a discipline
and culture like bro we have an
incredible culture like even just one of
our companies got all 75 of that company
on zoom and I was like raise your hand
if you want to do it and every single
person raise their hand but also we
don't hire fat people that's a rule
I should he's like I should have invited
him you can hire fat people but it's
your obligation to change them that's
exactly number 100 no we have people who
are not in the best shape yeah but they
can suddenly change them by making them
fit that will change their lives change
their work that'll change their family
that'll change everything maybe it'll
end up meaning they'll leave their
family or whatever yeah but it's a
[ __ ] good thing it's bad for them not
100 so the workout is 3K role to start
with and 100 push press then eight to
hand cleans then after that it's six to
HD sit-ups 40 deadlifts and then 20
double press and then we're going back
up yeah uh everything's split evenly
sort of impairs but everything's close
and just watch how to flick the bars up
and like keep the bars as close as they
can to them yeah it makes it so much
easier but the thing is even in the
middle of winter I'll wake up at the
same time and nothing nothing changes
don't feel tired or anything really at
all just [ __ ] get up but I've always
been like that even when I was like six
years it's just like rock music just
starts playing in his head you know when
you've got to do yeah like I wake up
excited every day
got so much to do it's not like [ __ ] I
need to open the water you need to go to
the gym don't even think about it
I feel like we should just let it in
Indonesia yeah just you know what I
trust you just do Case by case but yeah
a lot more sense they haven't slept to
come to everyone then yeah
yeah all right okay see you in a bit all
right cheers brought my social battery
so tight I don't think most people
realize I'm an introvert yeah and so I
can do it I enjoy I've seen meeting
people's a lot of fun
to back and it's um yeah bro the fact
that like people make an effort like
flying from all over the world and [ __ ]
like that
incredible anything like what I saw it
in my office for a week after just
talked to no one
they're gonna spot you now man oh [ __ ]
that's crazy
[Music]
the next four to five minutes I'm gonna
have to start clearing everyone out so I
can keep the rotation going as you know
we've got about 500 people outside so if
you take your pictures and meet and
greet happy days we've got to keep the
rotation and keep it fair for everyone
else
excuse me well done on the event thank
you welcome
here okay
and so far it's a success
hey
thank you
trying my best to say hi to everyone oh
wow this is so sweet is your mom thank
you so much wow look at that that is
really special
um I'm speechless thank you yeah guys
we'll try my absolute best obviously we
have a six o'clock cut off so but yeah I
just want to say if I don't get a chance
to say hi just Jenny means the world to
me that you guys took hours out of your
Sunday to to come and say hi and show
support and love it thank you thank you
very much I really appreciate it
[Applause]
[Music]
big man
what's the plan we are taking the tube
and going to Brixton bookmongers it's
like [ __ ] full circle for me we're
going uh
yeah we'll go full circle I'll continue
in the tube all right it's about money
or is it about girls either way I'm
threatening men see just text their
diligent yeah cause the outfit's making
sense I told him it costs
flies the same expense and we just went
triple platinum check the digits so it
just jumped off Victoria line which is
always so aggressively hot but yeah I
used to connect at Green Park and then
go Victoria line from Green Park to
Brixton which is always relatively quick
uh bricks and bookmongers is just down
there and yeah I used to hang around
this area used to spend my Sundays at
bricks and bookmongers yeah I've had a
good week I'd treat myself to a coffee
there's a little Plaza with like a bunch
of little restaurants and stuff like
that and yeah man this is basically
Sunday ritual Friday I used to do Subway
Friday with my friends yeah is that
Subway Fridays or if like once again if
I was killing it you know Domino's is in
UK they have a two for Tuesday just to
rinse out with my friends you still get
like three four of my buddies we'd split
it and just get a Domino's two for
Tuesday yes
all right so today we're bricks and
bookmongers there's somebody else this
guy probably doesn't even remember me uh
the owner Patrick but yeah I always used
to be there every Sunday to sit down
take five six books read for three four
hours never kicked me out never said hey
you can't read those unless you buy the
books and yeah I mean it's pretty
incredible the place is still here today
and if you go watch back my Vlogs back
in 2015 2016 you can see me all the time
I'll just take the tube take the bus go
spend my Sundays alone at Brixton
bookmongers reading and then yeah buy
two or three books for 10 pounds and
yeah that would be me set for uh for a
couple weeks so anyway I thought I'd
come back today basically just thank him
and give a small little donation to the
bookstore maybe help out with a couple
bills yeah make sure the place stays
alive and hopefully is a nice safe space
for a lot of other young kids that just
want to go learn read so I'll always be
very grateful to that spot yeah
good thanks how you doing
this is it how do you feel good well I
used to sit right here
really yeah you should chill here stack
of books it's got character huh
oh uh Alex I'm getting you this
hopefully you can finally find the [ __ ]
I think I need that so yeah how many
years just come here say like two years
oh much only two years but it's not a
lot of time I spent a lot of time in
this section I mean not like this
onwards not as much but less less so the
sexual erotica more though more so to
self-help
[Music]
what's up Jesus
certified killer bro owns the shop bro
I literally follow all your like content
you're literally like everything I've
done is because the agency everything
bro appreciate that bro everyone tells
you you can't do it like even on my
stage people were telling me you need to
focus on school you need to do this and
something inside of me telling me well I
want to be like self-made and no one
actually like helped me reach that and
then I saw your videos and then they
made me realize this guy's done it from
like listen the one thing you have is
time you know and I'm gonna be honest
you could pretty much do anything in
life and if you throw [ __ ] at a wall
long enough for 10 years Something's
Gonna stick your wisdom's actually like
long living like because of you I
started my agency in around September
October zero clients for like months
literally three days ago I signed a
client and I literally got off the phone
and called my mom I said mom like I've
signed the client I literally said well
if I didn't actually come across in my
gazi on YouTube or nothing how would I
have known about this this business
model I would have just continued you
know wasted so much time of my youth and
then I came across you and it's just
changed everything hey how are you yeah
perfect that's you you probably don't
remember me a little bit yeah he used to
sit in the back quite a bit I just in
the back correct yeah I used to come
here on the weekends and pick up three
or four books for the same price what
you guys have is incredible thank you
thank you thank you guys have been here
for so long it's very special a lot of
young men come in and they kind of
reference you and they head to certain
sections that's very sweet so how long
are you guys in London for perfect thank
you very much so yeah Patrick I hope you
don't take this in the wrong way um
obviously this place is quite near and
dear to my heart I have a lot of good
memories here as I said probably
insignificant to you but to me this is
almost a very safe space for me and yeah
you know it's felt like the minutes
turned into hours here so I thought I'd
give you a little gift um hopefully keep
keep the lights on for 30 more years
small little donations I hope you don't
take it the wrong way
yeah
so yeah it makes me very happy to hear
that love love young gentleman are
welcome to the door and picking up a
book that was really nice
big thank you for having such an open
space and not kicking someone out when
they spent three four hours reading
youngsters up back there but I've never
really okay I appreciate you thank you
very much thank you so much
thank you so much thank you appreciate
it
[Music]
foreign