they do not want you to think too
[Music]
much you have better wake up and
understand that there are people who are
guiding your life and you don't even
know
it
the truth is you've been brainwashed and
this is how we got here you see it All
Began on the afternoon of January 15th
1902 a secretive meeting that changed
the course of history as we knew it was
about to take place in none other of
course than the Rockefeller townhouse in
Manhattan and the records state that a
middle-aged man walked into a meeting
room full of lawyers bureaucrats and in
the presence of one of his Clos CL
advisers sign the deed of trust that
formly established an organization that
would deeply impact the lives of
generations to come that man was John D
Rockefeller and his closest adviser a
particular man with a deep Connection in
Washington on that afternoon in 1902
they founded what would later be known
as the general education board an
organization whose goal was the
promotion of Education within the US
without distinction of race sex or Creed
which sounds like a very noble cause at
least that's what it looked like from
the surface you see the name and the
promise of the secret initiative well
they were very carefully chosen what
comes to your mind when you hear the
name general education board well it's
probably one of those dozen different
government initiatives that overview
education I mean surely that would be
part of the Department of Education
after all it is the government that
handles education
right wrong they came up with a name
that would make them look like an
official government organization but in
reality this board was not government at
all there were no government officials
on the board nor was it backed by the
government whatsoever its purpose one
thing and one thing only to
systematically infiltrate the education
system and promote its own secret agenda
and I'll reveal that secret agenda in
just a second but here's the most clever
part of this whole initiative its
promise and the name of it almost
pressured politicians into backing the
cause because going against the cause
with a name like that wouldn't look good
for any politicians in the public eyes
after all it was a cause for the less
favored people all in the name of
diversity and education and it worked
exactly as planned only one short year
later in 1903 the US Congress granted a
formal Charter to the board providing it
with a national mandate little did they
know that they had just set in motion
one of the biggest tails of mass control
and manipulation in the history of the
world the idea was simple to provide
free public education to every single
child in America that would create an
environment where every single person
would have access to the same
opportunities and would have a fair
start with real chances of achieving
success in Life or at least that was the
idea that they sold to the public fast
forward to today and here's where we're
at the people who built the schools were
consciously aiming at eradicating the
will of the students who were part of
the system because they wanted the to be
obedient now education at this point is
a racket I mean most people will never
recoup the cost of a college degree and
Harvard could afford to pay their
$50,000 a year tuition for their 6,000
students you know for how long not 10
years not 30 years not 50 years
120 years for free and not asking for
another
Penny over half of recent college
graduates are unemployed or undery
employed and the sole reason why
colleges are so expensive in the first
place is because of the loans themselves
that was their plan all along the
unpayable student debt the new wave of
wokeness invading the floors of
universities to Fortune 500 companies
the job crisis the bull corporate agenda
all of it was part of a much bigger plan
and a web of hidden interests spun over
the course of 300 plus years with one
single ultimate objective a ating the
Free Will of an entire generation and
turning you into a Mindless obedient
worker and those are just the tip of the
iceberg of my findings over the last few
months and it really all started with me
trying to figure out how this recent
woke culture invaded our society across
all the social media apps to the biggest
initiatives of the biggest investment
firms in the world but what I found was
a much bigger story here that's not
being told a very carefully crafted plan
A a plan that connected all of these
problems together a plan that has been
kept secret for a long time dating back
to over 250 years ago a plan that if
people were aware of the existence would
rock the foundations of the current
system and expose the side of the system
that is hidden in the shadows a plan
that is crafted by three notorious
individuals over the course of three
centuries and broken down into four
stages of social conditioning and how
you can Implement them to control the
masses as you wish all of it was laid
out in the pages of an old book that
started to be written in
1763 and you are about to see for the
first time what's in the pages of this
[Music]
book it all dates back to 1806 there was
one specific event that changed the
course of the world forever and it
created a Cascade effect that still
deeply affects us to this day back then
the territory in Europe that is known
today as Germany was a part of Prussia
now Prussia had somewhat of a fearsome
reputation as one of the most powerful
armies of Europe and they managed to
quickly expand from Germany and Conquer
territories of the current Day Poland
Denmark Belgium Lithuania Luxembourg and
even a big chunk of Russia now here's
where it gets interesting in 1806 that
was the year that the Prussian Empire
faced Napoleon's France during the
Napoleonic Wars and as you may know that
marked the fall of Berlin to the hands
of Napoleon meaning the supposedly
unbeatable Army Of Prussia Was Defeated
and that put the intellectuals of
Prussia in crisis mode I mean how could
such a better trained Army from the
feared Prussian Empire lose to
Napoleon's weaker forces they could not
digest the defeat of Prussia so the
intellectuals came to one conclusion the
reason as to why the Prussian Army Was
Defeated was because the Prussian
soldiers were Thinking by themselves in
the battlefield Napoleon soldiers on the
other hand were only following orders
soldiers thinking for themselves was so
deadly it costed Prussia an expensive
price you see they were forced to sign a
peace agreement they gave away about
half of their territory and they also
had to pay very Hefty indemnities to
France and support their army which of
course ended up creating a lot of
economic instability so they needed to
make sure that that would never happen
again and this is where the conditioning
Factor book started to be written you
see the prussians planned something that
was quite frankly ingenious evil but
ingenious you see the problem was clear
they needed soldiers who followed orders
and did as they were told without ever
questioning anything and what was the
way that the prussians found to do that
indoctrination so they created an 8-year
education system the sole purpose of it
to indoctrinate children and teach them
to obey comply and do as they're told
this newborn education system would
teach them to follow orders to comply
without questioning to respect the
authority of their superiors the
Prussian leaders would teach the kids
just enough so they could follow orders
and be useful to the ones to the top but
not too much that they started thinking
for themselves and I'm going to show you
exactly how this new system accomplished
that in chapter 3 now the system was
also the perfect solution to another
problem that the Prussian Empire had
been facing you see a few years earlier
the Prussian Empire had just invaded and
conquered a huge part of Poland which
was great but also created a massive
challenge how would they get the Polish
people to accept them as their rulers I
mean after all they were their enemies
they were the colonizers and now they
needed to get the very people they were
Waging War against to give up their
polish roots and accept and embrace the
Prussian imperialism so the prussians
got to one conclusion you see the adults
were too proud of of their polish roots
and nothing would Chang their minds they
were simply a lost cause but the
children the children were different you
see the children could be indoctrinated
into a proud Prussian imperialist and
what better way to do that than
brainwash them through their entire
childhood and that is how the Prussian
education system was born and it worked
I mean kids would come in as bright
creative enthusiastic children and come
out as Obed iian mindless and not
capable of thinking for themselves and
most importantly convinced that the king
is just and his decisions should never
be questioned and these kids well they
made for perfect soldiers and after only
a few short years the masses had no
independent thinking left inside of them
and that was the Prussian model of
obedience and it was the first chapter
of what I like to call the conditioning
Factory and I'll explain in detail what
I mean by that over the next few
chapters because and I know this is hard
to believe
it gets so much
[Music]
worse the secret origins of the modern
day education system now there is
something really important for you to
understand here virtually all of the big
problems that we face today are a direct
consequence of what I'm about to uncover
right now and this is the reason you
fail to succeed not because you're a
failure but because the system has been
set up for you to fail from the get-go
and the thing you need to understand is
you will keep failing until you
understand the root of the problem and
more importantly address it otherwise
every single thing that you try every
single new job every single new Venture
every single new business every single
new side hustle will just be different
paths that lead to the same destination
failure and you might think that if you
are not currently in college or if you
dropped out of school this doesn't
really apply to you and that is another
way that they keep you indoctrinated
because listen you may have skipped a
few steps of their indoctrination plan
but at the end of the day if you follow
the traditional path and end up in some
soulless corporate career then you're
still a part of their system because it
goes Way Beyond the education system
itself and I'm going to show you exactly
how in the next chapters so if you don't
want failure to be the final result of
every single Venture you try in life pay
very close attention because I'm about
to show you the root of the problem and
then I'll show you how you can address
it I should reply that the very
recognition of an Reliance upon Free
Will in the pupil is the first mistake
of the old system you have to remember
that the reason the Prussian created its
education system in the first place is
because they belied that individuals who
had Free Will were a threat to their
imperialist regime they imposed risk to
the system the Prussian intellectuals
saw Free Will of their people as the
number one risk to their empire and all
of this hatred towards Free Will derived
from the school of thought of one single
philosopher one philosopher in
particular who was the biggest influence
to the Prussian education system this
guy was responsible for turning their
system into a conditioning Factory that
strips citizens of their Free Will and
turns them into obedient and Mindless
citizens he went by the name of Johan
gotle Fitch and here's what he
envisioned for their education system in
his own words education should aim at
destroying Free Will so that after
pupils are thus schooled they will be
incapable throughout the rest of their
lives of thinking or acting otherwise
than as their school Masters would have
wished when this Tech te has been
perfected every government that has been
in charge of education for more than one
generation will be able to control its
subjects securely without the need of
armies or policemen he has literally
written that down in his books and
notice how from the get-go the system
was built with the interest of its
creators in mind rather than the
interest of the students that go through
the systems themselves and you'll soon
see how this is a very common theme that
repeats many times but before that I ask
you the question what are the odds that
some someone going through a system
built on these principles and turning
out to be successful in life becoming a
free independent individual how more
likely are they to turn into a mere
product of the system very likely now
you probably don't even suspect it but
if you're watching this chances are you
went through this system
yourself
1843 that was a very pivotal year that
set the foundation for the modern day
Education System enter a man that goes
by the name Horus man you see Horus man
was a notorious American Congressman
part of the US House of Representatives
of the American Congress who later will
be known as the father of American
public education just a short 5 years
before he had been nominated the head of
the newly created Board of Education of
Massachusetts and he had one mission to
reform the American education system for
years he had been researching different
education models in European countries
to find successful case studies that he
could export back to the USA and finally
he found what he was looking for and yes
of course you guessed it the Prussian
education system and he had one goal in
mind implementing the same system in the
US I mean after all if that system
managed to remove every ounce of
nationalism from the people of a country
that was brutally invaded I mean what
could it do for the interests back in
America well it was definitely easy to
say that Horus man had big plans for the
newly discovered conditioning Factory I
mean education system and he was so
impressed with the results that the
prussians were getting that he decided
to Pur personally traveled to Germany
with a board of Educators so that way he
could learn in person the inner workings
of their system and after returning to
the US he went on a campaign and lobbied
heavily in Congress for this exact same
system to be adopted in the US and it
really didn't take too long for his
efforts to start creating results over
the next three decades multiple American
dignitaries traveled to Germany to get
degrees directly from the Prussian
system they would then come back to the
US and staff the universities and
schools AC across the country and by the
1900s all of the phds in the US were
trained in Prussia in just a few short
years Horus had the system streamlined
he had the people in place he had the
funding from the government and the
support from the public who backed his
Noble idea of making education public
widely available he had successfully
implemented what's described as the
first stage of conditioning in the
conditioning Factory book and now he was
on to the second stage the goal maximize
the reach of the system
and he came up with a very clever way to
do that have you ever asked yourself why
is education mandatory well Horus is to
blame for that too his 10th annual
report in 1846 led to the first state
law that made it mandatory for kids to
attend school in the state of
Massachusetts so now you have two
options you either give your children to
the government to let them indoctrinate
them with their ideals or the second
option is you get thrown into jail and
it's no wonder that attendance raids
started to Skyrocket and that same year
he supported the government governor of
Massachusetts in adopting the Prussian
model of education for the entire
State and how did he do that let's just
say that the governor of the state at
the time was the very first to receive a
PhD from Russia once the system was
completely implemented in Massachusetts
the game was on the system started to
spread itself throughout the US in
record time it spread to New York and
then other states soon followed slowly
but surely parents children and society
as a whole started to accept C the
Prussian model as the only sensible way
of educating children without ever
suspecting the true motives behind it
and by the end of the 1800s the Prussian
system had dominated America to make
sure they'd killed any remaining traces
of other education systems by 1864
Congress made it illegal for Native
American kids to be taught in their
native language instead they'd be sent
away to boarding schools to go through
the same conditioning Factory from then
on every single American child grew up
under the Prussian system of obedience
now listen if you're not from the US
you're probably thinking right now well
I'm not from the US so that doesn't
really affect me what does this have to
do with me well I'm sorry to tell you
but at this point the influence of the
Prussian education system it was already
growing internationally with the help of
prussians and Horus man himself you see
soon after the Canadian superintendent
of schools well he came to Horus to
learn more about the system himself and
also ended up travel to Prussia to go
through the same process that Horus did
and on the other side of the ocean the
Prussian Empire grew its influence in
Europe more and more and with that their
system started to spread accordingly
across the entire continent and it got
even worse after World War II but more
on that later for now what you need to
understand is this if you went to school
either in the US Canada South America or
a country from Europe you have been
indoctrinated through the Prussian
system and if that's the the case you
need to understand how this system has
impacted you and what it is doing to you
[Music]
today let's go back to our favorite
Prussian philosopher Johan gotl fit the
new education must consist essentially
in this that it completely destroys
freedom of will in the soil which it
undertakes to cultivate and produces on
the cont strict necessity in the
decisions of the will the the opposite
being impossible such a will can
henceforth be relied on with confidence
and certainty now how would they achieve
this level of social conditioning for
that they needed an effective method
Well turns out that Johan not only
developed the philosophy behind the
Prussian education system but he also
developed the method through which it
would accomplish his goal of destroying
the Free Will of students and making
them lifelong slaves of their school
Masters combined John Lock's view that
the human mind at Birth Earth is a blank
slate and ru's ideas on how to write on
that blank slate he established a
scientific method on how to indoctrinate
children and strip them of their Free
Will and the method consisted of first
carefully choosing the subjects that
students must learn what they should
think about and for how long instead of
allowing them to discover what they like
and are naturally talented at
standardized books that would have
students believing the sides of history
and philosophy that was most convenient
to the states interests then they would
also standardize testing across all
schools and made sure that the right
answers were the answers that they
wanted to hear from the students in case
the students were thinking for
themselves instead of thinking how the
system wanted them to think they'd
simply get punished through their grades
and talking about punishing they'd also
punished children who misbehave the
entire system was set in a way to
enforce discipline in obedience children
would have to ask for permission to talk
to drink water and to go to the bathroom
to stand up to do anything and I'm not
sure if you've noticed this but they
purposely made the schools look like
prisons that's why they put the children
sitting in rows that's why they had
alarm Bells that's why they had strict
timings for classes and intervals had
children in classes based on age groups
as well as have the children listening
to what a teacher says with little to no
interaction and a very important part of
the method as well was having the
teachers themselves not realizing that
what they were doing was indoctrinating
the youth you see from the teachers
perspective they're just doing their job
by educating the youth and most
importantly having a Time intensive
curriculum that took the children away
from their families for majority of the
day lowering their family time to a
minimum so that way that the families
wouldn't have a chance to teach them
their own values and they would learn
their values the way the system wanted
them to instead now let me ask you
something how oddly similar is this
system to the one that we have across
the world today how many of those things
have you experienced yourself when you
were in school and this is why I'm
telling you this is not a mere
coincidence and it all comes from the
three secret figures who wrote the book
on how to create a conditioning Factory
and turn free individuals into obedient
mindless Factory workers Johan himself
now the big question is why does no one
know about him why do we not learn about
the true secret origins of our education
system well maybe that's because the
model was designed with the interests of
the Elites in mind instead of the
interests of the individual and they had
to keep that fact hidden so that the
masses wouldn't suspect of their most
effective tool of mass control oh and
maybe it's also because one of the other
small details I forgot to mention about
our very forward thinking philosopher
Johan you see after Berlin was occupied
by Napoleon in 1807 Johan actually gave
a series of very famous addresses to the
German nation and on them he actually
spoke about the superiority of the
German people above all others and he
would fervently call for United German
nation and preach them as a unique
culture and spiritual entity and the
content of these speeches was a catalyst
for the Prussian education system does
that does that ring a bell to you maybe
about I don't know another Infamous
movement that happened in Germany you
know that preached about the superiority
of Germans above all other races and how
they should act as one United Nation
something like that like I feel like
there was a guy who used to talk about
that now if that still doesn't ring a
bell for you let me just go ahead and
make it even easier for you in other
early Works Johan also called Jews a
state within a state that would
undermine the German nation and he
openly expressed a desire to expel Jews
from Germany so he basically preached
German superiority he called for United
German nation and he wanted to expel
Jews from
Germany yeah I I feel like I've
definitely seen this before well it
turns out that Yan had a deep influence
on the rise of the Third Reich and his
addresses to the German Nation contained
elements of a cultural and linguistic
nationalism that the Nazis would later
heavily draw upon and most importantly
historians point out that one of the
greatest social factors that allowed
Nazism to achieve Mass adoption in
Germany was because of how German people
were bred from birth to be obedient and
to respect authority without ever
questioning all because of their
indoctrination based education system
that was implemented decades earlier
from the work of Johan still to this day
y is seen as one of the biggest
influences of Nazism and neo-nazism
which means that the current day
education system employed all around the
world is based on the System created by
one of the biggest influencers of the
Nazis yeah no wonder they don't want you
to know about the true origins of the
education system and it also begs the
question why would the father of modern
education make it a law that every child
spend their youth in a System created by
the father of neo-nazism and how are we
setting ourselves up knowing that the
entirety of the population from North
America to Europe today were raised in
the same system adopted by pre-nazi
Germany I'm going to give you a spoiler
it is directly related to the woke
culture and the war on free speech that
we are experiencing today and I'm going
to cover this in detail in episode two
that goes live on Thursday now are you
convinced yet that the education system
you went through was never actually
created to make you a critical thinker
and a free successful individual but
rather turn you into a brainwashed
prisoner of the system if not don't
worry this is still just the tip of the
iceberg it gets so much worse you see
this system wasn't complete yet despite
the efforts of horse man he never
managed to push America to stage two of
conditioning you see at this point
America and the other countries that had
recently implemented the Prussian model
well they were still in stage one of
conditioning they obeyed and believed
everything that their government would
say meaning their Free Will was already
gone which was wonderful for the
government itself but not everyone was
completely happy with it that's because
the recent industrial revolution had
caused a shift in Powers the government
wasn't the biggest man on the Block
anymore America had new kings that
quickly ascended to the positions of
power these were the corporate Titans
and one in particular had a big need
that he wanted to fulfill John D
Rockefeller you see at the time his oil
Empire was growing so much that his
biggest bottleneck
was one thing and one thing only Factory
workers he needed a herd of mindless
obedient workers to work in oil rigs
extraction Transportation refineries Etc
and he saw in the Prussian education
system the perfect opportunity to create
that much-needed herd of mindless
obedient Factory workers to slave away
for his Empire he too had read the
conditioning Factory book on how to turn
regular people into products of the
system and he noted that Horus man had
missed a few key steps that if were
implemented would create the exact type
of brainwashed workers that he needed
the biggest one was the public education
system that Horus had implemented still
didn't have a standard curriculum to
follow and that was one of the key
pillars for the Prussian model and in
rockefeller's mind the deal was simple
the kids weren't learning anything that
were of any use in any oil refinery mine
or factory it didn't matter how obedient
the masses were if they couldn't work in
his oil Empire to expand his operations
further so Rockefeller also saw the need
of indoctrinating the American
population into the narrative that work
would set them free this way they had a
reason something to work for their life
would now have meaning so what did
Rockefeller do he came up with a plan to
infiltrate and take over control over
the public education system and he
teamed up with one of his closest
advisor Frederick Tates to turn that
plan into reality
and this is how we go back to the
meeting from the beginning of the
episode the plan they had was simple yet
very effective create a board that
sounded like an official government
board for Education get the board
officially approved by the government
and then push the agenda of promoting
education without the distinction of
race sex or Creed in order to get the
government funding and approval to
massively scale the school network and
then instill in the masses the idea that
only work could set them free and in
order to get a high-paying job they
needed education and here's the plan in
Frederick's own words in our dream we
have Limitless resources and the people
yield themselves with perfect docility
to our molding hand we shall not try to
make these people or any of their
children into philosophers or men of
learning or men of science we're not to
raise up among them authors orators
poets or men of letters we shall not
search for embryo great artists painters
musicians nor will cherish even the
humbler ambition to raise up from among
them lawyers doctors preacher statement
of whom we now have ample Supply and
that plan is what led to the creation of
the general Board of Education as I
mentioned at the beginning of the video
by 1903 Rockefeller and Gates had
successfully secured the government
approval for their board alongside 3.5
billion in funding to build thousands of
schools across the country in a few
short years this absolutely transformed
the amount of schools in the United
States of America and after that every
new generation will go to school ready
to learn and become critical thinkers
only to come out of school as an
obedient factory worker with no big
aspirations workers who are perfectly
happy working a factory job with no
Prospect of ever being truly free in
their life I mean after all they believe
that only work could set them free and
that's what they were doing turning you
into a product of the system someone who
gets treated like a product that at the
end of the day can be easily replaced
they will never do more than what it was
manufactured to do and that it has an
expiry date and with that Rockefeller
successfully turned America into stage
two conditioning by simply following the
steps that was laid down decades earlier
by the Great Prussian philosopher and
secret figure Johan Gauntlet fit that's
exactly what Rockefeller had just
accomplished and that's how John D
Rockefeller himself also wrote his name
as co-author of the conditioning Factory
book and became the Third secret figure
that created the modern day education
system or conditioning Factory should I
say soon enough other industry tycoons
were jumping into the education ship
Andrew Carnegie started to sponsor
public education I mean he too needed
more machine workers Engineers mine
operators railroad workers repairmen the
list goes on you know who else jumped on
this bandwagon Ford himself in just a
few years they had the entire system
streamlined from state sponsored
textbooks and standardized tests to
indoctrinating teachers under this new
Prussian Rockefeller model of Education
rockefeller's plan had worked and in his
own words I don't want a nation of
thinkers I want a nation of workers can
you now see why you haven't succeeded
even though you've put in a lot of
effort into everything you've been told
that would make you successful going to
school getting good grades getting a
good degree working a safe job it was
all a setup from the GetGo it was never
me for you to succeed in the way you
want to but rather for you to experience
success in their terms it was only meant
for you to become a product of the
system but that wasn't enough
Rockefeller was an extremely ambitious
man and he wanted to take things a step
further so here's what he did instead of
only focusing on high schools he started
investing heavily in universities this
way instead of indoctrinating people
only until their teenager years he could
keep indoctrinating them throughout
their adulthood turning them into even
better brainwashed mindless Factory
workers selling the idea of college to
the masses was pretty easy I mean they
had already believed the narrative that
work would set them free and that the
only way to get good work is by being
educated so now what did he do he
conditioned them into thinking that
education equals College something that
the majority of people around the world
still believe to be true to this very
day and that is the power of a narrative
and I personally think that Rockefeller
himself didn't even realize what he had
just created as a byproduct of that he
had just set up the foundations for one
of the biggest Mass control tools that
is still used by governments and
universities to this day and this was
the start of our modern-day abusive love
relationship with college
degrees
[Music]
1957 one of the most iconic moments of
the Cold War had just unraveled you see
Russia launched the first man-made
satellite to the orbit of the Earth with
Sputnik one and this had very big
consequences to the Americans why
because it meant that using the same
technology Russia could potentially
launch nuclear Rockets into American
Terr
so American politicians came to one
conclusion if America wanted to win the
war then they needed more College grads
to build such Technologies and Factory
workers weren't enough now they needed
highly specialized Engineers but the
problem was even though tuition was way
cheaper than it is today it was still
expensive to the standards of the time
and that's when Dwight Eisenhower
president at the time decided to take a
page out of rockefeller's book and make
higher education widely available to the
population how through widely available
student loans now after getting the idea
approved on Congress he signed a
National Defense Education Act and that
created the National Defense Student
Loan program I mean after all who could
go against a National Defense Initiative
especially in the height of the Cold War
and that was the beginning of something
huge why because all universities
realized something with the right
approach to this they would never have
to worry about money ever again because
the government was willing to spend an
unlimited amount of money on them and
here's where things take a turn you see
after a few years the government had
broken through a100 billion in student
loans which would be equivalent to $1
trillion today and that presented the
government with a little bit of a
problem they started to question for how
long would this be sustainable knowing
that students would only be paying this
back 4 years later and in small portions
over multiple years so they decided to
do something they asked the bankers for
help and that was the nail in the coffin
because they had just pushed America
into stage three conditioning how
through the modern student loan system
in 1965 Congress passed something called
The Higher Education Act and it
basically got almost every single
student a guaranteed loan and how did
they do that through Federal guaranteed
loans the government set up guarantee
agencies that would guarantee the loans
made by Banks were always paid back and
what you really need to understand is
how they made that happen the Banks
would give out the student loans just as
normal but here's where the twist is for
every single student loan that the bank
gave out the government would give
around 80% of the total value of the
loan to guarantee agency then if a
student didn't pay back their loan the
government agency would buy the loan
from the bank and attempt to collect on
it so this really shifted the risk of
the default from the banks to the
guarantee agencies but the weird thing
is that the guarantee agencies were also
guaranteed and that's because the
federal government
agreed to reimburse the guarantee
agencies for 90% or more of the loans
that they couldn't collect now this
created a very interesting situation
because kids had access to money that
wasn't theirs so they were willing to
spend it no matter what the price was
and if the kid drops out the government
is still going to pay the bill meaning
that there was no risk for universities
and they knew that which also meant that
no matter how much they raised tuition
the government would still pay it off
because they had the goal of making
America the most educated country in the
world and the money was also not coming
from the government's pocket so they
didn't really care how much was being
spent and that created a situation where
the colleges were incentivized to rack
up their prices so what did colleges do
they started to Rack it up in the' 60s
alone they increased tuition 30% above
inflation and this led to a Snowball
Effect colleges started expanding to be
able to accommodate more and more
students which really created a
self-fulfilling cycle more students
would apply to college so the colleges
raised their tuition and with higher
tuition more students needed loans now
the more loans they gave out the more
money the lenders make off of you and
that turned the entire conditioning
system to a whole new level now they
were able to indoctrinate you through
your entire childhood create a herd of
mindless obedient Factory workers
through college and also make hundreds
of thousands of dollars off of every
single student throughout the entire
indoctrination process they had finally
managed to implement something that not
even the prussians managed to do stage
three conditioning they brainwash you
then they make you a product of the
system and to top it all off they make
you pay cop amounts of money to do so I
mean listen if you think about it that's
even better than slavery because at the
end of the day slaves don't pay you
students on the other hand they pay you
for that privilege and here's the most
interesting part about the entire loan
system the loans themselves became the
reason as to why people needed loans in
the first place because the loans are
why colleges are so expensive so now you
needed a loan to go to college but
without the loan tuition would have just
stayed the same I mean you can clearly
see it by first looking at how steady
tuition used to be before student loans
were widely available now look at the
increased intuition rates after they
became widely available and now compare
them to how much the inflation rate and
income increased during that same period
and you can see how this created a
vicious cycle of the average citizen not
being able to afford tuition to send
their kids to college because tuitions
have grown 1200% while their salaries
only grew a fraction of that then that
CA es the need for student loans which
in turn makes colleges even more
expensive it is a NeverEnding cycle to
make even more money off of your back
colleges have turned into a money-making
machine for the administrators the
debtors the bankers and the board
members some people even call it
history's biggest scam and just so you
really understand I want to put it into
perspective just how much money colleges
truly have here's how much money some of
the biggest companies in the world have
in their cash and short-term investment
balance McDonald's $1.6 billion
Starbucks $3.2 billion Disney $1.5
billion Coca-Cola $15.7 billion meta $
53.4 billion now let's take a look at
how much the top 10 private universities
just in the us alone have in their
endowments Washington University $12
billion the bottom of our list here
already has 10 times more than
McDonald's and three times more than
Starbucks Columbia university1 13
billion
more than Disney by the way Northwestern
University $14 billion University of
Notre Dam $16 billion which by the way
is the same as Coca-Cola University of
Pennsylvania $20 billion MIT $24 billion
Princeton University $35 billion
Stanford University $36 billion Yale
University $41 billion Harvard
University $49 billion Harvard has more
cash than most Fortune 500 companies and
just in the us alone there's over 130
universities with more than $1 billion
in their endowments and coincidence or
not the one with the highest amount per
student you guessed it the Rockefeller
University who has over $35 million in
their reserves for every single student
in their University I mean what else
could you expect from the family of the
man that quite literally created this
entire system right now how do these
universities make that much money you
may ask is it all from tuitions and
here's where things get a little fishy
you see if you check their financial
reports tuition only amounts to around
20% of their yearly revenue and that
seems quite odd doesn't it I mean how
else would a university make that much
money well they have another 10% that
they make from federal sponsored
researches meaning by the way that if
you're a taxpayer you are paying them
directly out of your pocket but that's
not the interesting part the interesting
part is that if you were to look at
Harvard's financials from 2022 you would
see that the biggest chunk of their
revenue comes from philanthropy 45% to
be exact but if you dig a little bit
deeper you're going to see that almost
all of the money under philanthropy that
comes from something called the net
endowment distribution now you probably
know this but universities don't pay any
taxes I mean after all they're not a
for-profit organization right all they
do is create critical thinking citizens
and improve the quality of the
population yeah we both know that those
two could be further from the truth
here's the thing once universities start
to really rack up student loans they
start to just have a lot of cash laying
around and I mean a lot so what happened
was Hedge funds started approaching them
and saying hey instead of keeping all of
these billions of dollars in your
checking accounts why not just create
your own hedge fund and multiply this
money through Investments well there was
just one problem they couldn't have
their own hedge funds because they're
not a for-profit company right so their
genius solution let's just call it an
endowment instead then we let a hedge
fund manager manage this money exactly
as they do in their hedge funds but
instead it's tax-free now you might
wonder why this falls under the category
of philanthropy in their financials well
you've probably seen those multi-million
dollar donations from Rich individuals
going to Harvard Yale and other
universities like that one hedge fund
manager who donated $150 million of his
own personal money to Harvard well where
do you think all that money goes do you
think it goes to infrastructure or to
cover student loans or to their staff no
no no no that money goes directly to
their endowment but here's the real
kicker that money is managed by an
endowment manager who invest the same
money in hedge funds and other
investment products which in turn have
their own managers who make money
through management fees meaning at the
end of the day that donation may or may
not go back to the original donor
through management fees of a string of
financial instruments but with a little
added bonus the money invested is
taxfree because the universities don't
pay taxes I mean how genius is that and
this could be a 1hour long video on its
own but what's important for you to
understand here is this they use
universities to further indoctrinate you
into a product of the system and while
they do that they also turn you into a
debt slave to make money off of you
risk-free and tax-free and most
importantly this system is not
sustainable eventually there will be no
money left to lend and bankroll the
system and what do you think happens
when the system runs out of money well
that's what you're going to find out
[Music]
next
2023 and finally we get to what's
happening today today for every dollar
the government loan through student
loans to tuition goes up by 60 on the
other hand Harvard has enough money to
pay the tuition of every single one of
their students for the next 20 years in
a row so that begs the question why do
they still make their students get into
hundreds of thousands of dollars in debt
to get a college degree and it's also a
very well-known fact that 60% of
graduates today won't be able to pay
back their student loans if that is the
case why are the government and Banks
still lending this money and most
important importantly what happens when
the majority of the students don't pay
back their loans looking at the price
increase in tuition over the last few
decades and comparing to how quickly it
grows compared to inflation income and
all other metrics I can only come to one
conclusion this is unsustainable and
eventually this system will collapse
which means that there's a bubble now
it's not the regular type of financial
bubble that we're used to seeing I see
it more of a personal bubble and here's
why the job market has changed it's not
dominated by a few tight end companies
anymore the internet has really
democratized the game to a certain
extent and majority of those companies
need employees who are critical thinkers
and they value the skill of solving
problems over the skill of following
orders but right now we're still pumping
mindless obedient workers who don't know
how to solve any real world problems and
demand for such people is shrinking
rapidly so it begs the question is
getting a degree actually worth the
investment today and you can probably
imagine my answer by now now and to be
honest this is where I'm going to catch
you off guard slightly because my answer
is yes getting a degree is still worth
the investment but there's a catch
there's still a lot of big corporations
that pay six figures to developers
Engineers data analysts even lawyers and
doctors usually positions that are stem
or lawyer slm medicine related so if you
want to follow one of those careers it
still makes sense for a certain period
of time but here's where things take a
different turn because there's also
another big caveat here there's one big
question that I'm sure sure we've all
asked ourselves before is Success based
on Merit well if you go into the formal
job market the truth is it's probably
not for majority of these big
high-paying companies they don't hire
based on merits they don't hire the
better and most qualified candidates
they hire the ones who graduated from
the best universities and it doesn't
really matter how good or bad you are
skill set wise the only thing that
matters is the University name stamped
on your diploma so listen if you're not
going to one of those ivy league
universities you don't even have a
chance against your your competition in
fact it is a very common practice for
big tech companies to hire all of the
talent available from such universities
even if they don't need them and that's
just to keep the pool of talent empty so
that way that they competitors they
don't have anyone to hire and this is
why I don't know if you've seen it
before there's thousands and thousands
of these Tik toks and YouTube shorts and
all this stuff you know all these like
day in the Liv of a Google software
engineer and all they do the entire day
is eat exercise and just wander
mindlessly around the HQ apparently
without ever actually doing any work and
it's because they actually are not doing
any work now if you're not a graduate
from one of those universities you're
just kind of left out of the party no
matter how good you are because as I
said in that World the game is not based
on Merit which then brings us back to
the point of the personal bubble because
here's the thing if these big
corporations are only hiring based on
your diploma a majority of those
employees don't necessarily bring any
value to the company how sustainable is
that and the answer is very obvious it's
not sustainable at all and that's why
over the last 12 months we've seen Mass
layoffs from Big corporations like
Google meta Uber Etc the bubble is not
about to burst it already started
bursting so now the obvious question is
how does this affect you and what should
you be doing well the way that I look at
this is that we're in a very similar
situation to what happened back in 2008
during the housing bubble if you don't
remember let me jog your memory what
happened back then was this everyone and
their mom was getting loans to invest in
real estate even though it was obvious
the ma majority of people getting the
loans had no way of ever paying back
such loans I mean you had waiters and
maids and bus drivers with two mortgages
on houses but all the lenders they
thought it was fine why because real
estate was considered the safest
investment in existence I mean no one
would ever dare bet against Real Estate
and because it was the safest investment
everyone knew it until it wasn't anymore
and now I see us in a very similar
situation everyone and their daughter
got approved to student loans that they
simply cannot pay back but that's not
even the worst part in my opinion the
worst part is that 99% of the population
today is betting their entire careers on
what everyone sees as the safest bet go
to school get a degree work a safe job
in my opinion today this is one of the
riskiest paths you could take exactly
because how the system is set up I have
just showed you the system is not built
for you to succeed the system is built
to strip you out of your critical
thinking and turn you into a brainwashed
thoughtless obedient modern-day worker a
product of the system so what used to be
considered the safest route has now
turned into one of the riskiest because
at any moment this won't be sustainable
anymore and when that happens everyone
who's a part of the system will have
nowhere to run so what's the solution
well you have two the first one is to
succeed within the system and as I said
this is actually still a viable solution
as long as you carefully pick the right
career and make your way through one of
the top 1% universities today this is
the only safe way I see of succeeding in
the system the other option is to
succeed outside of the system and how do
you do that the first step is to remove
and unwire all of the conditioning you
have been fed ever since you were 4
years of age because listen at the end
of the day if you're watching this you
most likely live in a country at stage
three conditioning and this is such an
insane level of conditioning for failure
that you have been fed throughout your
entire life that there is no way you
could ever succeed without first
addressing the thing that's stopping you
from succeeding listen if you feel like
you have put a lot of effort into your
work and your studies and you have done
everything that you were told would lead
you to a successful life but you still
haven't achieved success yourself that's
why the system was set up for you to
fail from the GetGo and all of the
condition you have been fed growing up
is like a 100t wall in your way to
success and if you don't remove this
wall from your way you're going to keep
bumping your head on it mindlessly for
as long as the wall is still there it is
only once you remove this that you can
truly experience success in life the
people who can unwire all of the social
conditioning that they have been fed
from the conditioning Factory and manage
to succeed outside of the system is
someone who I call an outsider now if
succeeding in life and truly becoming
free as an individual is something that
you Aspire for in your life then the
question you should be asking is how do
I become an outsider myself and the
answer is actually quite simp simple
because the path to becoming an outsider
has already been written tested and
proven a long time ago long before the
Prussian education system became a thing
you see the Prussian education system
dates back to the late 1700s and humans
were around long before that thousands
of years before that and so was
education I mean education didn't start
in the late 1700s it started centuries
before that and here's the thing the
ideals and principles that education was
originally built upon were the ideals
that make a successful critical thinking
free individual they were the ideals
that created some of the most brilliant
individuals and brightest minds of the
world has ever seen we're talking Plato
Aristotle Alexander the Great Leonardo
da Vinci Shakespeare Marcus aelius
Socrates they all learned and followed
these principles and ideals principles
that can still be applied to this day
and they all became Outsiders in their
own fields of work and what I found out
is that there are five specific
principles all of these great
individuals followed to become some of
the most successful individuals to ever
step foot on this Earth and those five
lost principles are documented and have
been lost in ancient writings that date
back to 700 BC which the conditioning
Factory has purposely tried to suppress
and hide from you why because just like
there is a step-by-step book that the
elites followed to indoctrinate you turn
you into mindless factory worker and
keep you a product of the system there's
also a step by step that teach teaches
you how to become a truly free
successful individual the content in
these ancient writings hold the secret
to Breaking Free of Decades of
indoctrination that the system has
injected into your brain the same
secrets that the brightest Minds in the
world used throughout history to make
breakthrough scientific discoveries that
changed the world created the biggest
Empires the human race has ever seen and
most importantly become critical
thinkers that achieved success and
freedom in their own ways and what you
need to do if you want to succeed today
is rescue those principles that are
described in detail in these ancient
writings and this is why this event is
called the rescue my mission here is to
help rescue these five long lost
principles that were the foundations to
the greatest breakthroughs Humanity has
ever experienced so with all of that
being said the question now is do you
want to know what are the five lost
principles in these ancient writings you
will but not today you're not ready for
it yet you see in order for you to be
ready you have to complete a mission
that's because these principles will
only make sense if you apply what you
have learned today so here's what I need
you to do I know that when I tell people
about the indoctrination Factory and
explain that they've conditioned them to
think in a certain way well a lot of
people are very skeptical about that so
I don't want you to take my word for
this I want you to ask yourself a few
questions and then based on the answers
of those questions you choose what you
want to believe in do this right now if
you are the person who is serious about
success
or you just want to prove me wrong grab
a pen and paper and let's go through
these questions the first question are
you afraid of renouncing on the formal
path whether that be dropping out of
college or quitting your current job
even if you know that deep down in your
heart that's what you want really think
about this now if you're afraid of it
where do you think that this fear comes
from I mean after all you have seen
people succeeding outside of the formal
path time and time again yet you're
still afraid to take the leap so why is
that now my next question is do you
subconsciously think that following the
formal path is your only choice you know
your only chance and not ending up
homeless on the streets and my follow-up
question is that if that fear is that
intense where do you think that comes
from do you think it's something
rational or a disbelief that has been
seeded into your brain by the people
around you maybe your parents maybe your
teachers maybe your peers now I have a
few more questions for you to think
about but you can find them inside of
the WhatsApp group for the rescue the
link for it is in the description of
this video now inside the file you're
also going to find Space to answer those
questions because I want you to actually
write down your answers because this is
the only way that you'll truly think
about your answers and then on Thursday
at 5:00 p.m. UK once you're ready I'm
going to reveal the five lost principles
hidden in the ancient writings so make
sure to mark your calendar and come back
with your missions completed and with
that I'll see you on Thursday this is
the
rescue