it has never been harder to win than
right now why because every single day
you are frying your brain you are
killing your attention span and you are
killing your focus you're killing your
testosterone and because of all of that
you are killing your success the average
person has a worse attention span than a
goldfish and that's who you're competing
against so on the good news that means
that just with the tiniest bit of
discipline and work ethic you are
already ahead of 90% of people and
before we even begin you need to
understand that your ability to control
your urges is directly correlated to
your success or lack thereof if you
cannot control yourself if you cannot be
disciplined you will never be successful
it is simply impossible and that is why
it's so important for you to master your
urges and all of that starts with
desexualizing your brain so that you are
no longer ruled by your primate brain so
today I'm going to give you the only six
steps you need to desexualize your brain
and regain control of your life because
it's having that very control over your
mind your body and your life that will
ultimately lead you to success now
here's the interesting part truly
desexualizing your brain actually has
very little to do with sex and has
everything to do with something else but
I will get to that a little later in the
video so for now let's get into it the
first step is to stop watching porn
first and foremost you need to stop
watching porn now listen this may sound
obvious yet 99% of young people simply
cannot stop I would say that watching
porn is by far the worst way which you
sexualize your brain and let me explain
to you why you see the problem isn't
just the amount of time that you spend
watching porn I mean sure if you stopped
you'd have an extra hour per week or or
something like that but that's just a
very minuscule side effect compared to
the rest you see porn literally fries
your brain and robs you a focus don't
believe me just look at the science
there have been multiple studies that
link porn usage to the erosion of your
prefrontal cortex you know that part of
your brain that regulates your emotions
your actions and more importantly your
impulse control and willpower but that
is just the tip of the iceberg there is
a laundry list of negative side effects
that have been linked to porn use why
because porn use has similar effects on
the brain as substance abuse porn has
been linked to issues like decreased
focused and increased anxiety and
depression now as if these problems
weren't big enough porn has also been
linked to trouble in long-term
relationships and of course impotency in
fact there is an epidemic of young men
who are experiencing sexual issues like
erectile dysfunction because their brain
has been rewired it's unfortunate
because these young men have consumed so
much porn that their neural Pathways
have literally changed I mean they've
effectively trained themselves to be
aroused by watching others do the deed
instead of doing it themselves and porn
users even reported that they are less
satisfied with their lives than their
counterparts who don't watch porn now
the second step in desexualizing your
brain goes hand inand with quitting porn
and that is you need to stop pleasuring
yourself look I understand it's
addictive and I understand that it's
been normalized in today's day and age
but there is nothing healthy or normal
about it and not even because the very
Act is so terrible as it is with porn
it's actually just because the
consequences of it you see every time
you do it your dopamine surges I mean
you're pretty much signaling to your
brain that you have accomplished what is
supposed to be man's highest goal to
procreate you are essentially telling
your brain that you've done the most
most important thing you'll do all day
now of course you and I both know that
that's not true but the neurons firing
in your brain do not and that is why you
are rewarded for it that is why it's
cheap dopamine because you are tricking
your own brain into giving you dopamine
you have not earned and that's why your
ability to focus and your ability to do
hard things plummets because how do you
think that the real world will stack up
to the dopamine and other chemical
releases that you're getting from doing
the the very thing we have been
evolutionarily designed to do well the
answer is it won't stack up at all I
mean no wonder you can't focus when your
dopamine receptors are so fried this is
why you can't focus I mean listen of
course everything else will feel boring
when you've just done the dirty business
and this is why you need to stop so you
ask yourself why do so many young men
keep doing it because they are addicted
they are addicted to cheap dopamine in
the exact same way that people get
addicted to drugs I mean in fact port
and masturbation are the most difficult
addictions to break why because of the
insane dopamine Spike that is caused by
it so real quick let's just look at the
data if you eat a delicious burger or
some other carb filled meal your
dopamine levels will Spike by 100% now
if you smoke or get some other form of
nicotine your dopamine will Spike by
200% whereas porn and masturbation
boosts your dopamine by over
250% the exact same is sex now here's
the key difference porn and masturbation
will then make your dopamine levels fall
way below Baseline and that's where
those lethargic feelings come from after
that's the exact same dopamine curve you
get from drugs so then that really
starts to beg the question how the hell
do you stop and here is where it gets
interesting you see an addiction to por
and masturbation isn't actually rooted
in anything sexual at all and that leads
us onto the Third step of how you can
desexualize your brain number three
purpose now they actually did a study
where they tried to figure out what
causes these addictions and the answer
may surprise you you see it wasn't
actually any form of perversion it
wasn't childhood trauma it wasn't
extraordinary libido instead it was
something far simpler far more
rudimentary it was meaninglessness
simply put if you don't have a purpose
if you don't have a goal if you don't
have something that you are striving
towards then you are more likely to
devolve in these addictions now the good
news is it's fixable every man should
have that purpose that North Star that
drives him forward you simply need
something better to do with your time
than giv to your urges what that
something is will depend on the person
now from an early age we are taught that
we need a good college education and a
corporate job as though that's somehow
going to fulfill us but we both know
that that's definitely not not true is
it in fact that's not true at all and
from October 30th to November 6th I'm
going to expose how and why you have
been indoctrinated to believe this and
most importantly I'm going to show you
how to escape their indoctrination and
earn back your freedom so if you want to
be a part of that free online event then
sign up with the link below anyways we
all need something to guide us for some
it'll be starting a business for others
it might be something entirely different
I can tell you that for me personally my
North Star was to be able to take care
of my mom and my loved ones and that is
why I went into business because I had
that North Star to guide me and honestly
without that North Star I can
confidently say that I would have given
up because the money isn't enough to
keep you going you need that North Star
you need that why that purpose but even
then once you have your purpose you may
still slip up why because there are
triggers out there that cause you to do
so and this leads into our fourth step
in desexualizing your brain step number
four stop watching soft porn you see
soft porn can be just as bad as porn
because it's everywhere everywhere you
look there are half naked girls I mean
you scroll endlessly through Tik Tok and
Instagram and the algorithm is
reinforced by your desire to look at
these girls and that is why I need you
to unfollow all of the Instagram models
unfollow all the Tik Tok girls to do
their little dances because they are
eating away at your focus they are
destroying your future and it may seem
minuscule to you but it's not you see
most of the time you don't just randomly
decide to watch porn there is a trigger
and that's why the best way to quit porn
is by eliminating the triggers that make
you watch it and that means you need to
also stop watching soft porn and every
time the algorithm shows you half naked
girls simply click not interest Ed train
the algorithm to not show you those
things and listen of course the best
case scenario is you just quit Tik Tok
and Instagram alog together because
really at the end of the day you have no
business looking at memes or whatever
else if you are not where you want to be
in life and if these social media
platforms don't directly help your
business but in any case The Next Step
you need to take in order to desexualize
your brain is to focus Inward and not
outward you see the biggest problem with
the sexualization of your brain
stems from the changes that are
happening in your dopamine system the
sexualization of your brain impairs your
ability to do hard work because your
brain becomes so used to cheap dopamine
and that's why the next step requires
you to learn delayed gratification
instead of constantly looking outwards
for stimulus and dopamine you need to
learn to look inward now you might be
asking what does that actually mean it
means that 99% of people get their
so-called Happiness by doing fun things
whether those things be a Sinister as
porn or as innocent as chocolate but if
you truly want to be successful that
cannot be you now I'm not saying that
you need to cut every single source of
dopamine from your life but you
definitely need to think about what's
helping you and what's hurting you and
over the years I routinely do a dopamine
detox this is where for a certain amount
of time usually between 24 to 72 hours
you do nothing no food no phone not even
books or music and certainly no porn
just complete Stillness you need to
become used to finding peace without
these external stimuli because the goal
is for you to be so fulfilled by your
work that you eventually get those same
dopamine releases by doing hard things
you see dopamine is nothing but a reward
system it's the way that your brain has
evolved to reinforce behaviors that will
increase your chances of survival and
that is why sex spikes your dopam so
much because without procreation I mean
we wouldn't exist but in today's world
social media and food has hijacked those
same systems and that is why it is your
job to regain your control over them so
stop seeking cheap dopamine externally
and instead look Inward and that is how
you desexualize your brain and realign
your actions with your goals now the
final thing is you need to stop chasing
women and build yourself first listen
you will never be able to truly Focus
inward if you are constantly chasing
women if you're texting this girl
meeting up with that girl all while
thinking about some other girls you will
never be focused that is not how you
desexualize your brain which is exactly
why I always say that you need to stop
chasing women and build yourself up
first the best part is when you do
eventually build yourself into man of
substance the women just inevitably come
to you but until you get to that level
chasing women is just a massive waste of
time unless it's your day one girl
unless you know hey this girl this will
be my future wife but if that isn't you
it's a waste of time for two reasons
number one the quality of women you can
get at the beginning of your journey is
nothing compared to what you'll be able
to get later down the line you see women
date up in the social hierarchy which
means the best quality women will
inevitably end up with the best quality
men so that's why you need to spend time
molding yourself to be the best version
of yourself that you could possibly be
and I'm not only talking about just
money here by the way now the second
reason it's a waste is because if you
somehow manage to get a highquality girl
the amount of effort and time that it
will take you is massive so you really
need to analyze the opportunity cost
here because going on a date with a girl
spending $100 or a few hundred bucks to
try to impress her has far greater
complications look I'm not saying you
should be an antisocial weirdo but you
need to set your priorities straight
listen in the same way that they tell
you to put on your own oxygen mask first
in the plane you need to be able to hold
your own before you let someone else
into your life because listen at the end
of the day dating is a massive
distraction and when you're first
getting started in your business or your
career you'll need all the time and
focus that you can muster because no
step of the journey is harder than the
first one and that is why you need
undivided attention I mean listen after
all you just need 1 to 3 years of pure
focus and then you can live a normal
life again but you need to be willing to
make that sacrifice because let me tell
you something if you are constantly
thinking about this girl and that girl
and which girl to see tonight there's no
way that you will be able to desexualize
your brain and channel your focus into
what really matters and once you Channel
your focus into what really matters
everything else will fall into place so
just focus on yourself first so
gentlemen pick yourself up focus on the
right things and as always I'll be
watching from afar and I'm rooting for
you